<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><ROOT><CourseInfo><title>Técnicas Microscópicas de Caracterización</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Science</subject><school>University of Barcelona</school><language>Spanish</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-27</session><session>2016-06-27</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>El recorrido por el apasionante mundo de la microscopía nos permite ver a una escala muy alejada de mundo macroscópico al que estamos acostumbrados. Las diferentes técnicas microscópicas nos ayudan a entender el reino atómico y la estructura de los organismos vivos, así como también de los diversos materiales. Es una herramienta imprescindible para desarrollar nuevas funcionalidades en el campo de la nanociencia y la nanotecnología con aplicaciones biomédicas, en computación y telecomunicaciones, y en energías renovables, entre otras muchas.

Al completar el curso los estudiantes tendrán una visión detallada de los elementos básicos del que están formados los microscopios que utilizamos en las diferentes técnicas, su funcionamiento y operatividad, la preparación de muestras así como los objetivos y resultados de estudio.

El curso está pensado para profesores de secundaria que quieran tener una aproximación a las técnicas de microscopía así como para estudiantes tanto de secundaria como de primeros cursos universitários. Pero es apto para cualquier persona interesada en el mundo nanométrico y sus aplicaciones.
Syllabus
INTRODUCCIÓN AL MICROSCOPIO ELECTRÓNICO
Te damos la bienvenida al curso de microscopia para la caracterización, en este curso el estudiante aprenderá las partes esenciales y el funcionamiento de los diversos microscopios y sus técnicas, componentes, funciones, así como los diversos dispositivos y aplicaciones. El curso está diseñado para desarrollarse a lo largo de 5 semanas, con una dedicación de 3 horas semana. Al finalizar cada módulo el alumno encontrará un cuestionario el cual deberá aprobar con un 80% de puntuación para la obtención de un certificado de aprovechamiento.

Módulo 1: Microscopía Electrónica de Barrido (SEM)
En este módulo se pretende mostrar la estructura y los principios básicos de funcionamiento del Microscopio Electrónico de Barrido (MEB o SEM en su acrónimo en inglés). Veremos qué tipo de fenómenos se producen dentro del microscopio al interaccionar el haz de electrones con la muestra y de qué manera se aprovechan las diferentes señales generadas para proporcionar, con gran resolución, información morfológica, topográfica y de composición, siendo muy útil para una gran variedad de aplicaciones científicas y industriales.

Módulo 2: Microscopía Electrónica de Transmisión (TEM)
En este módulo se presenta la configuración de un microscopio electrónico de transmisión (TEM). Mientras en un microscopio SEM, las imágenes se forman con electrones secundarios arrancados de la muestra, o con electrones del haz primario que han sido retrodispersados al interaccionar fuertemente con los átomos del material, en un TEM las imágenes se forman con los electrones que han atravesado la muestra. Veremos los modos más fundamentales de operación para obtener una imagen ampliada de la muestra, incluso con resolución atómica, o para obtener diagramas de difracción de electrones que contienen información sobre la estructura cristalina de los materiales observados.

Módulo 3: Microscopía Electrónica de Transmisión de Barrido (STEM)
En este módulo presentamos el microscopio electrónico de transmisión y los modos de operación básicos con haz paralelo para obtener imágenes y patrones de difracción de electrones. En este tercer módulo, se presenta la posibilidad de trabajar con un haz convergente y de pequeño tamaño, que además barre la superficie de la muestra por la acción de bobinas electromagnéticas deflectoras, dando lugar al llamado modo de barrido – transmisión (STEM). La señal de interés en este caso, proviene de la interacción quasi-elástica de los electrones con los núcleos de los átomos de la muestra para obtener imágenes cuyo contraste depende del número atómico de los mismos, o bien de la interacción inelástica con la nube electrónica de los átomos de la muestra, para medir la pérdida de energía que ha sufrido el haz de electrones primario y extraer información sobre la composición del material y el estado de oxidación de los elementos que lo componen.

Módulo 4: Microscopía de Fuerzas Atómicas (AFM)
En este módulo analizamos el Microscopio de Fuerzas Atómicas que significó un hito a principios de los 80 para la evolución y consolidación de la nanotecnología ya que permite la medida de todo tipo de nanoestructuras de una forma rápida, sencilla y no destructiva. Durante el curso veremos su esquema y funcionamiento y podremos comprobar su gran potencialidad y alta versatilidad. El objetivo principal del curso es dar las herramientas básicas para la utilización práctica de un AFM de manera autosuficiente.

Módulo 5: Microscopía Óptica Avanzada (MOA)
En este módulo hablamos del gran avance que la Microscopía óptica ha experimentado en los últimos, consolidado con los nuevos equipos de Microscopía Óptica Avanzada que ya son capaces de trabajar en la nanoescala. Uno de estos equipos es el microscopio Confocal, el cual será presentado y explicado durante el curso para saber su esquema, composición, funcionamiento y posibles opciones de uso. La microscopía confocal permite la medición topográfica de superficies con una amplia gama de texturas (desde superficies muy rugosas a superficies muy lisas) mediante el escaneo en pasos de la muestra verticalmente.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6473/coursera-tecnicas-microscopicas-de-caracterizacion</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Photography Techniques: Light, Content, and Sharing</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Visual Arts</subject><school>Michigan State University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-27</session><session>2016-06-13</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>Welcome to Course FOUR! In Modules 1-4 you will cover the final elements of the Specialization necessary to round out this introduction to the fundamentals of Photography, and prepare you for creating your own exciting project in the Capstone! You have come a long way since the beginning of this journey from Smartphone Basics to DSLR and Beyond. Just think of all the information you have absorbed and put to use in your assignments and quizzes, and the confidence you have gained that you CAN control the camera to make pictures you are proud to share.

Here in Course Four you will start by gaining knowledge related to content in photography, from fact to fiction, documentary to purely expressive. Next you will learn principles, tips, and techniques for using the essential element of Light in Ambient/Natural settings.

The flash/strobe unit, whether it is built-in to your camera or an add-on "hotshoe" model, will finally be something you, not the camera, controls! You will prove to yourself that those former mysteries of Controlled Continuous and Strobe lighting will no longer be mysterious, as you apply your knowledge to creation of assignment photographs in various situations. Sharing those pictures in Peer Review will give you the opportunity to learn from your fellow photographers' solutions to lighting challenges, and to gain insight into your own work and creative approaches too.

There is an important word to share about Peer Review assignments for this course. As photographers who have accomplished the quiz and photography requirements of Courses One through Three, you have the knowledge and capability to create quality photographs at a much higher rate of success, and in a much shorter time, than when you began. You have also proven that you are a dedicated Learner, someone who has a passion for photography and is willing to put forth the extra effort necessary to accomplish your goals. This Course is the last before the Capstone Course, in which you will be tasked with creating a project over a 2-month period of dedicated photography. The Peer Review photography assignments have been structured with both your advanced capabilities and dedication in mind...in other words, they will require both! Be prepared to allocate more time than you have in previous Courses for the assignments, because they will take more time and because you will really enjoy them!

Course Four ends with an overview of methods for finalizing your pictures in print form, including simple but effective matting techniques, and in web page designs as well. The pleasures and perils of sharing in social media sites are also yours to discover. Protecting your copyrights by understanding that concept and the ways that you can assert them, being careful about blogs and other outlets, and recognizing you are part of a community that respects the individual's creative effort, well that is important knowledge to have in preparation for the Capstone too! Let's get started with Module One!
Syllabus
The Content of a Photograph
What are the broad areas of content that are most closely associated with photography? Why is photography well suited to image-making in these areas, and where do your interests synchronize with those of photographers past and present? You will gain a greater understanding of those and other questions, and knowledge of a range of typical pictures in a variety of categories too, in this set of lessons. Understanding these broad categories will help you to form your own projects, including the Capstone Project in Course 5, with confidence that you are part of a stream of tradition, building on a foundation that you as a photographer are a part of!

Light Fundamentals 1.0: People, Places, Things under Ambient Light
In this Module you will begin with an overview of light itself, and learn to recognize the characteristics of typical "ambient," aka continuous light natural to the environment. From photographing early in the morning, through midday to evening, in exterior and interior environments, you will learn to recognize typical light/subject situations and be able to use new tips and techniques on how to get the best results. People, places, and things each require nuanced approaches, even under similar lighting, and you will learn to recognize opportunities in each category.

Light Fundamentals 2.0: People, Places, Things under Controlled Light
In this Module you will learn about essential light and exposure principles that are critical to your success in photography that is made with lights that you can control. From continuous-light to built-in-camera flash to auxiliary "hotshoe" strobes, you will establish a solid foundation of light and lighting principles and practices, especially related to the flash. With a built-in flash in most digital cameras, it is essential to have a full understanding of that important device. You will have much better control of the flash with the information you gain in this Module. Rounding out this module are lessons on practical photography activities that you will be able to apply to addressing your own individual needs for specialized picture situations, even with a Smart phone!

Finishing Pictures: Options for Showing and Sharing
In this Module you will survey the ways that you can bring your digital images out of the world of zeros and ones that are stored in your computer, and bring them into the world through various means of sharing. Whether your interests are in producing prints of your photographs or quality web-based displays, you will have the knowledge to control their appearance through calibration that is essential for a professional presentation. You will also learn about the pitfalls and dangers of sharing in social media and other sites, and how to take precautions to protect yourself, your family and friends, and your photographs. You will also gain an understanding of standard options for dissemination of your photos in print form, on sharing sites, and even in your very own website.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6478/coursera-photography-techniques-light-content-and-sharing</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Introduction to Neurohacking In R</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Programming</subject><school>Johns Hopkins University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-27</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>Neurohacking describes how to use the R programming language (https://cran.r-project.org/) and its associated package to perform manipulation, processing, and analysis of neuroimaging data. We focus on publicly-available structural magnetic resonance imaging (MRI). We discuss concepts such as inhomogeneity correction, image registration, and image visualization.

By the end of this course, you will be able to:

Read/write images of the brain in the NIfTI (Neuroimaging Informatics Technology Initiative) format
Visualize and explore these images
Perform inhomogeneity correction, brain extraction, and image registration (within a subject and to a template).</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6420/coursera-introduction-to-neurohacking-in-r</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>SmartGrid.x: Smart Grids: Electricity for the Future</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Civil &amp; Environmental Engineering</subject><school>IEEE</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-29</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Ever wondered why you hear the term “smart grid” so often these days, and what it’s all about? This engineering course will explain the essential nature of the smart grid, an electricity network based on digital technology, and the importance of grid modernization.

This course will provide high-level insight into a smart grid’s many aspects such as distributed energy, energy storage, transmission and distribution automation, microgrids, demand response, data analytics, and cyber security.

This course builds an understanding of key smart grid technologies both from a utility and customer perspective. It delivers a business perspective through cost-benefit analysis, market adoption, and industry mega trends.

It concludes by laying out a typical roadmap for the progression of smart grids, along with an implementation methodology for realizing it.

No previous power systems or utility industry knowledge needed. Simply sit back and enjoy your journey through the world of Smart Grid.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6481/edx-smartgrid-x-smart-grids-electricity-for-the-future</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>DAT210x: Programming with Python for Data Science</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Data Science and Big Data</subject><school>Microsoft</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-04</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Python is the language of choice for many data scientists.

In this practical computer science course, you will build on your existing Python skills and learn how to manipulate data using Pandas, and build machine learning solutions in Python using the scikit-learn package.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6471/edx-dat210x-programming-with-python-for-data-science</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Big Data Modeling and Management Systems</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Data Science and Big Data</subject><school>University of California, San Diego</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-04</session><session>2016-06-20</session><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Once you’ve identified a big data issue to analyze, how do you collect, store and organize your data using Big Data solutions? In this course, you will experience various data genres and management tools appropriate for each. You will be able to describe the reasons behind the evolving plethora of new big data platforms from the perspective of big data management systems and analytical tools. Through guided hands-on tutorials, you will become familiar with techniques using real-time and semi-structured data examples. Systems and tools discussed include: AsterixDB, HP Vertica, Impala, Neo4j, Redis, SparkSQL. This course provides techniques to extract value from existing untapped data sources and discovering new data sources.

At the end of this course, you will be able to:
* Recognize different data elements in your own work and in everyday life problems
* Explain why your team needs to design a Big Data Infrastructure Plan and Information System Design
* Identify the frequent data operations required for various types of data
* Select a data model to suit the characteristics of your data
* Apply techniques to handle streaming data
* Differentiate between a traditional Database Management System and a Big Data Management System
* Appreciate why there are so many data management systems
* Design a big data information system for an online game company

This course is for those new to data science. Completion of Intro to Big Data is recommended. No prior programming experience is needed, although the ability to install applications and utilize a virtual machine is necessary to complete the hands-on assignments. Refer to the specialization technical requirements for complete hardware and software specifications.

Hardware Requirements:
(A) Quad Core Processor (VT-x or AMD-V support recommended), 64-bit; (B) 8 GB RAM; (C) 20 GB disk free. How to find your hardware information: (Windows): Open System by clicking the Start button, right-clicking Computer, and then clicking Properties; (Mac): Open Overview by clicking on the Apple menu and clicking “About This Mac.” Most computers with 8 GB RAM purchased in the last 3 years will meet the minimum requirements.You will need a high speed internet connection because you will be downloading files up to 4 Gb in size.

Software Requirements:
This course relies on several open-source software tools, including Apache Hadoop. All required software can be downloaded and installed free of charge (except for data charges from your internet provider). Software requirements include: Windows 7+, Mac OS X 10.10+, Ubuntu 14.04+ or CentOS 6+ VirtualBox 5+.
Syllabus
Introduction to Big Data Modeling and Management
Welcome to this course on big data modeling and management. Modeling and managing data is a central focus of all big data projects. In these lessons we introduce you to the concepts behind big data modeling and management and set the stage for the remainder of the course.

Big Data Modeling
Modeling big data depends on many factors including data structure, which operations may be performed on the data, and what constraints are placed on the models. In these lessons you will learn the details about big data modeling and you will gain the practical skills you will need for modeling your own big data projects.

Big Data Modeling (Part 2)
These lessons continue to shed light on big data modeling with specific approaches including vector space models, graph data models, and more.

Working With Data Models
Data models deal with many different types of data formats. Streaming data is becoming ubiquitous, and working with streaming data requires a different approach from working with static data. In these lessons you will gain practical hands-on experience working with different forms of streaming data including weather data and twitter feeds.

Big Data Management: The "M" in DBMS
Managing big data requires a different approach to database management systems because of the wide variation in data structure which does not lend itself to traditional DBMSs. There are many applications available to help with big data management. In these lessons we introduce you to some of these applications and provide insight into how and when they might be appropriate for your own big data management challenges.

Designing a Big Data Management System for an Online Game
In these lessons we give you the opportunity to learn about big data modeling and management using a fictitious online game called "Catch the Pink Flamingo".</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6466/coursera-big-data-modeling-and-management-systems</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Introduction to Complex Analysis</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Mathematics</subject><school>Wesleyan University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-04</session><session>2016-06-05</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This course provides an introduction to complex analysis which is the theory of complex functions of a complex variable. We will start by introducing the complex plane, along with the algebra and geometry of complex numbers, and then we will make our way via differentiation, integration, complex dynamics, power series representation and Laurent series into territories at the edge of what is known today. Each module consists of five video lectures with embedded quizzes, followed by an electronically graded homework assignment. Additionally, modules 1, 3, and 5 also contain a peer assessment.

The homework assignments will require time to think through and practice the concepts discussed in the lectures. In fact, a significant amount of your learning will happen while completing the homework assignments. These assignments are not meant to be completed quickly; rather you'll need paper and pen with you to work through the questions. In total, we expect that the course will take 6-12 hours of work per module, depending on your background.
Syllabus
Introduction to Complex Numbers
We’ll begin this module by briefly learning about the history of complex numbers: When and why were they invented? In particular, we’ll look at the rather surprising fact that the original need for complex numbers did not arise from the study of quadratic equations (such as solving the equation z^2+1 = 0), but rather from the study of cubic equations! Next we’ll cover some algebra and geometry in the complex plane to learn how to compute with and visualize complex numbers. To that end we’ll also learn about the polar representation of complex numbers, which will lend itself nicely to finding roots of complex numbers. We’ll finish this module by looking at some topology in the complex plane.

Complex Functions and Iteration
Complex analysis is the study of functions that live in the complex plane, that is, functions that have complex arguments and complex outputs. The main goal of this module is to familiarize ourselves with such functions. Ultimately we’ll want to study their smoothness properties (that is, we’ll want to differentiate complex functions of complex variables), and we therefore need to understand sequences of complex numbers as well as limits in the complex plane. We’ll use quadratic polynomials as an example in the study of complex functions and take an excursion into the beautiful field of complex dynamics by looking at the iterates of certain quadratic polynomials. This allows us to learn about the basics of the construction of Julia sets of quadratic polynomials. You'll learn everything you need to know to create your own beautiful fractal images, if you so desire. We’ll finish this module by defining and looking at the Mandelbrot set and one of the biggest outstanding conjectures in the field of complex dynamics.

Analytic Functions
When studying functions we are often interested in their local behavior, more specifically, in how functions change as their argument changes. This leads us to studying complex differentiation – a more powerful concept than that which we learned in calculus. We’ll begin this module by reviewing some facts from calculus and then learn about complex differentiation and the Cauchy-Riemann equations in order to meet the main players: analytic functions. These are functions that possess complex derivatives in lots of places; a fact, which endows them with some of the most beautiful properties mathematics has to offer. We’ll finish this module with the study of some functions that are complex differentiable, such as the complex exponential function and complex trigonometric functions. These functions agree with their well-known real-valued counterparts on the real axis!

Conformal Mappings
We’ll begin this module by studying inverse functions of analytic functions such as the complex logarithm (inverse of the exponential) and complex roots (inverses of power) functions. In order to possess a (local) inverse, an analytic function needs to have a non-zero derivative, and we’ll discover the powerful fact that at any such place an analytic function preserves angles between curves and is therefore a conformal mapping! We'll spend two lectures talking about very special conformal mappings, namely Möbius transformations; these are some of the most fundamental mappings in geometric analysis. We'll finish this module with the famous and stunning Riemann mapping theorem. This theorem allows us to study arbitrary simply connected sub-regions of the complex plane by transporting geometry and complex analysis from the unit disk to those domains via conformal mappings, the existence of which is guaranteed via the Riemann Mapping Theorem.

Complex Integration
Now that we are familiar with complex differentiation and analytic functions we are ready to tackle integration. But we are in the complex plane, so what are the objects we’ll integrate over? Curves! We’ll begin this module by studying curves (“paths”) and next get acquainted with the complex path integral. Then we’ll learn about Cauchy’s beautiful and all encompassing integral theorem and formula. Next we’ll study some of the powerful consequences of these theorems, such as Liouville’s Theorem, the Maximum Principle and, believe it or not, we’ll be able to prove the Fundamental Theorem of Algebra using Complex Analysis. It's going to be a week filled with many amazing results!

Power Series
In this module we’ll learn about power series representations of analytic functions. We’ll begin by studying infinite series of complex numbers and complex functions as well as their convergence properties. Power series are especially easy to understand, well behaved and easy to work with. We’ll learn that every analytic function can be locally represented as a power series, which makes it possible to approximate analytic functions locally via polynomials. As a special treat, we'll explore the Riemann zeta function, and we’ll make our way into territories at the edge of what is known today such as the Riemann hypothesis and its relation to prime numbers.

Laurent Series and the Residue Theorem
Laurent series are a powerful tool to understand analytic functions near their singularities. Whereas power series with non-negative exponents can be used to represent analytic functions in disks, Laurent series (which can have negative exponents) serve a similar purpose in annuli. We’ll begin this module by introducing Laurent series and their relation to analytic functions and then continue on to the study and classification of isolated singularities of analytic functions. We’ll encounter some powerful and famous theorems such as the Theorem of Casorati-Weierstraß and Picard’s Theorem, both of which serve to better understand the behavior of an analytic function near an essential singularity. Finally we’ll be ready to tackle the Residue Theorem, which has many important applications. We’ll learn how to find residues and evaluate some integrals (even some real integrals on the real line!) via this important theorem.

Final Exam
Congratulations for having completed the seven weeks of this course! This module contains the final exam for the course. The exam is cumulative and covers the topics discussed in Weeks 1-7. The exam has 20 questions and is designed to be a two-hour exam. You have one attempt only, but you do not have to complete the exam within two hours. The discussion forum will stay open during the exam. It is against the honor code to discuss answers to any exam question on the forum. The forum should only be used to discuss questions on other material or to alert staff of technical issues with the exam.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6418/coursera-introduction-to-complex-analysis</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>How to Validate your Startup Idea</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Entrepreneurship</subject><school>University of New South Wales</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-04</session><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Starting a new business begins with an idea that needs to evolve through experimentation, iteration and interactions with people. This course is for existing and potential entrepreneurs who are looking for guidance and support to make their ‘great idea’ a reality. In addition to reviewing the basic principles of entrepreneurship, this course guides you through the process of actively validating your idea in the market. We encourage you to identify and communicate good opportunities and to create and capture value from these opportunities. By working through the course and completing the activities you’ll learn how to get feedback that systematically tests different parts of your business idea. You will learn how to do this through interacting with potential customers, suppliers, partners and investors outside the course. Along the way, you will also become more confident in pitching your idea. By the end of the course you should have a validated business idea that you can start right away.
Syllabus
How can you learn entrepreneurship?
In the first week, you'll be learning about some basic concepts in entrepreneurship. Specifically we're going to introduce the business canvas and the lean method, two key frameworks that will be used to structure your activities throughout this course.

How is your idea valuable?
This week you'll learn to articulate and test your value proposition by drawing on three concepts: the strategy canvas, persona and minimum viable product (MVP). The strategy canvas emphasizes the uniqueness of your value proposition. The 'persona' represents who you think your typical customer is, which is useful for identifying real customers. The MVP is a simple prototype, which is a key tool to to get feedback from potential customers about the value you are providing them.

How will you reach more customers?
This week we'll help you think beyond your first customers, to scaling up your business across multiple segments of customers. The core concepts for this module are the diffusion of innovation and developing partnerships.

How profitable is your idea?
This week is an introduction to financial literacy. We'll show you how to build an income statement, how to develop financial models and financial forecasts. We'll also introduce you to some metrics to track the viability of your business that complement the traditional accounting metrics.

Is investment capital right for you?
This week you'll learn some basic investment capital strategies for new ventures, illustrated using a simple capitalization table.

How will you pitch your idea?
This week pulls together all the elements and evidence of your business idea so far to develop a coherent and succinct business pitch</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6449/coursera-how-to-validate-your-startup-idea</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Composing for Public Audiences: Writing, Rhetoric, and Research</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Grammar &amp; Writing</subject><school>Ohio State University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>7 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-11</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Interested in refining your writing skills to appeal to, influence, or inform public audiences about a social or political cause? This course provides instruction in and resources for creating persuasive print and visual texts to reach diverse audiences.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6496/canvas-net-composing-for-public-audiences-writing-rhetoric-and-research</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Fast Track Finance #1</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Finance</subject><school>University of Michigan</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-11</session><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>.
Syllabus
Chapter 1: Time Value of Money
In this chapter, we introduce the framework of time value of money (TVM) in a carefully structured way, using relatively simple applications.

Chapter 2: Time Value of Money - Applications
In this chapter, we build on Chapter 1 and move quickly to more advanced applications of TVM focusing on situations we confront on a daily basis.

Chapter 3: Decision Criteria
In this chapter, we develop an understanding of alternative decision criteria - Net Present Value (NPV), Internal Rate of Return (IRR), Profitability, etc. - that are commonly used in the real world, with a focus on a critical evaluation of their strengths and weaknesses.

Chapter 4: Decision Making &amp; Cash Flows
This chapter contains a basic introduction to the key determinants of cash flows using accounting principles.

Chapter 5: Bond Valuation
This chapter introduces you to the most common vehicle of investment/financing: bonds. Though introductory, we attempt to cover a fair amount of content and with real world applications.

Chapter 6: Stock Valuation
This chapter provides an exposure to the characteristics and the valuation of stocks, again with an eye toward real world applications.

Chapter 7: What is Risk?
In this chapter, we will develop a theory of risk based on the intuitive concept of diversification. Since knowledge of Statistics is key to understanding risk, we will introduce some important concepts of applications.

Chapter 8: Diversification and CAPM
In this chapter, we will introduce one of the most widely known models called CAPM (Capital Asset Pricing Model), which provides a simple and powerful relation between risk and return.

Chapter 9: Leverage, WACC &amp; Valuation
This Chapter attempts to put together a cash flows and risk and return in a world with leverage financing. The content is our first exposure to valuation with a full-blown application.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6404/coursera-fast-track-finance-1</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Antimicrobial resistance - theory and methods</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Disease &amp; Disorders</subject><school>Technical University of Denmark (DTU)</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-11</session><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>The course will cover the topics related to antimicrobial resistance with basic definitions and overview on antimicrobials their use and the emergence and spread of resistance. The course will guide you through the concepts and the importance of resistance spread and dissemination and how that happens. It will show you how bacteria become resistant and which mechanisms they might use for this. And as part of the course you will also receive some training in methods for antimicrobial susceptibility testing (AST) and detection of specific resistance in the microbiological laboratories with the basic methods available and with focus on the obtention of good quality results which can be interpreted and used for different purposes.
Additionally, it will show you how to use genomic analysis tools to analyze whole genome sequencing data to detect resistance genes (and or other genes of interest) in a simple and easy way using online tools freely available.

After this course you should be able to:

1. Describe the most important families of antimicrobials and mode of action
2. Understand the basic concepts of antimicrobial resistance from several perspectives (clinical, research and microbiological)
3. Enumerate and describe how bacteria can become resistant and the mechanisms that may be involved in that process
4. Describe how antimicrobial resistance emerges and spreads around the world including concepts of antimicrobial resistance transfer, selection and dissemination
5. Enumerate the methods used for antimicrobial susceptibility testing (AST)
6. Compare dilution and diffusion methods and know the basic techniques of agar disk diffusion, broth dilution and agar dilution methods
7. Have detailed theoretical knowledge on how to perform the main methods in a laboratory
8. Know the basic concepts about analysis and interpretation of results of AST, including different breakpoints, cut-off setting and their applications.
9. Understand the importance and related concepts related to quality management and quality assurance method standardization, applied to AST
10. Relate the information obtained in this course with real cases of resistant bacteria spreading in patients, the community, animals or the environment
11. Relate the phenotypical results with results from genotyping using molecular techniques for detection of resistance mechanisms
12. Understand the concept and be able to apply genomic analysis tools used to detect resistance genes and other relevant genes from Whole Genome Sequencing (WGS) data (with demonstration of selected online tools)

Disclaimer: Please note that the guidelines and methods referred or links included in these materials are updated when the videos lectures are produced and before the course is released, however these might become outdated with time.
Syllabus
Welcome to the course
This module is basically a welcome to the course were you can find information on the Course structure, the contents you will be learning in the next modules, the grading, and introduction to the instructors and to the teaching material.

Module A- Antimicrobial and antimicrobial action
Antimicrobials and antimicrobial action ( includes two lectures and one quiz). Here you will learn a lot about antibiotics/ antimicrobials and you will know more about:what they are, where do they come from, what are the major groups and how can we classify them, how do they have an effect, how do they act on the bacterial cells

Module B - Antimicrobials and resistance
This module containd information about antimicrobials and the development of resistance in bacteria including causes for resistance and their mechanisms, as well as an insight in how resistance disseminates and how it can be selected.

Module C- Antimicrobial susceptibility testing
This module deals with antimicrobial susceptibility testing in the laboratory: its importance and use, descriptions of the methods and their applications and detailed descriptions of the procedures applied for the main methods.

Module D- Interpretation
This module gives practical insight on how to interpret antimicrobial susceptibility results.

Module E- Quality assurance
This module is dedicated to Quality management and Quality assurance (QA/ Quality control (QC) procedures and use of QC strains to assure the qulaity of results of antimicrobial susceptibility testing: importance, elements and principles.

Module F- Alternatives to AST- Genome analysis tools
As alternative to the phenotypical methods, the researcher might decide to use genotypically based methods to identify genes of interest. in the lectures of this module we present the Resfinder tool which may be used to find resistance mechanisms ( genes and in the future versions also specific point mutations)from Whole genome sequences of bacteria of interest. The second Lecture is a demonstration of the My DB Finder which can be used to identify genes of interest defined by the user from Whole genome sequence data.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6448/coursera-antimicrobial-resistance-theory-and-methods</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Preventing Dementia</title><provider>Independent</provider><subject>Disease &amp; Disorders</subject><school>University of Tasmania</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-12</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Preventing Dementia is a Massive Open Online Course (MOOC), offering university-quality education about the latest research in dementia risk and protective factors. The free 5-week course provides an opportunity to engage with the perspectives of a global community, without requiring exams or assignments.
With the ageing of the world’s population, dementia is looming as the public health issue of the 21st Century. Is it possible to modify your risk of dementia? A substantial proportion of risk is associated with advanced ageing as well as genetic risk factors, but the latest research has indicated there are modifiable risk factors which may decrease your susceptibility to dementia. The Preventing Dementia MOOC investigates the best available evidence about dementia prevention, drawing on a range of global experts.
You will have the opportunity to engage in online discussions, and can also participate in new research in this field, to help us determine the most effective ways to help people reduce their dementia risk. At the end of the Preventing Dementia MOOC, there is also the opportunity to undertake an assessment of your individual risk.
Preventing Dementia is designed to be accessible and appealing to people from diverse backgrounds including
Health and allied health professionals
Community and residential aged care staff
Health policymakers
Social scientists
Individuals with a general interest in brain health and/or dementia
The course runs for 6 weeks in total. The first week of the course is an orientation period. Content will be delivered during weeks 2 to 6. To obtain the most from this course, participants should expect to spend approximately 2 hours per week engaging with the course content and activities. After successfully completing the final quiz, participants will be eligible to download a free certificate of completion.
Syllabus
Course Outline
  Module 1 – Can dementia be prevented?
Key concepts in dementia prevention
Definition of dementia and introduction to the diseases that cause dementia
Important factors influencing the numbers of people with dementia across the globe
The impact of dementia on the health care system
  Module 2 – Risk factors for dementia
How we study dementia risk in populations
Non-modifiable vs modifiable risk factors
The major modifiable risk factors
How dementia risk is measured at individual and population levels
  Module 3 – Dementia risk – it’s not all in your head
Evidence supporting links between key vascular and medical risk factors with dementia
  Module 4 – A healthy and active life
Evidence supporting links between key lifestyle factors and risk of dementia
mpact of depression on dementia risk
Impact of education on dementia risk
Concept of ‘cognitive reserve’
  Module 5 – Interventions for prevention
Key strategies for prevention at the individual and population level
Encouraging healthy behaviours
What you can do to reduce your risk of dementia
Current research initiatives</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6565/preventing-dementia</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>SAP Digital Boardroom in a Nutshell</title><provider>openSAP</provider><subject>Business Analytics and Intelligence</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-12</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>One of the most critical activities for companies is to leverage innovation as fast and easily as possible. With SAP BusinessObjects Cloud and SAP Digital Boardroom, we offer an end-to-end analytics solution in the cloud that enables our customers to use innovation directly.
SAP BusinessObjects Cloud for BI, SAP BusinessObjects Cloud for planning, and SAP BusinessObjects Cloud for predictive analytics are the main solutions in SAP BusinessObjects Cloud. SAP Digital Boardroom itself is an application that sits on top of them.
Value driver trees, planning and predictive scenarios, and visualizations are prepared in SAP BusinessObjects Cloud. Together, you can put them in stories that are the basis for SAP Digital Boardroom.
SAP Digital Boardroom contains 3 screens: The Overview screen, Content screen, and the Context screen. The main aim of SAP Digital Boardroom is to give you a 360° view of your enterprise in real time. High-level as well as detail-level information is available to (executive) management members at all times (24/7). The capabilities of SAP BusinessObjects Cloud and SAP Digital Boardroom allow you to drill down directly into the details, and if something changes at line item level, you can see the impact on the aggregated view in real time. It gives you the chance to align executive decisions on one single source of truth using intuitive visualizations based on business units.
In this course, you’ll learn the steps you need to take to prepare a board meeting using SAP Digital Boardroom.
Syllabus
Unit 1: Introduction to SAP Digital Boardroom
Unit 2: Enhanced Capabilities of SAP Digital Boardroom
Unit 3: Collaboration Scenarios
Unit 4: Board Meeting Leveraging SAP Digital Boardroom</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6415/opensap-sap-digital-boardroom-in-a-nutshell</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Access to Capital for Women: Capturing Opportunities to Grow Your Business</title><provider>NovoEd</provider><subject>Entrepreneurship</subject><school>+Acumen</school><language>English</language><course_hours>4-5 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-12</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Businesses generally require money in order to grow. This 5 module course aims to equip you with the mindset and skills needed to access the capital to support the growth of your business. In this course you learn to interpret financial statements in order to understand the capital needed for growth, the types of capital available, and the process for connecting what you need with what is available. This course was built in partnership with Goldman Sachs 10,000 Women and Babson College, a world leader in entrepreneurship education.
The course will begin with an opportunity for introspection. You'll reflect on what it means to be a business owner with an entrepreneurial orientation. Then, you will learn the basics of financial statements and understand how to use them in strategic planning and communicating to potential capital providers. You'll learn from case studies and examples of how other women business owners have applied these skills to grow their business. Finally, we will walk you through how to develop growth projections, a form of storytelling built on numbers that you can leverage as you develop your entrepreneurial vision and seek funding.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6486/novoed-access-to-capital-for-women-capturing-opportunities-to-grow-your-business</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>DAT102x: Data Science Professional Project</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Data Science and Big Data</subject><school>Microsoft</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-18</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Showcase your data science knowledge and skills, and solve a real-world data science problem in this project-based learning experience. The project takes the form of a challenge on the Cortana Intelligence platform, where you will develop and deploy a solution that is tested and scored to determine your grade.

For challenge platform details, see the Cortana Intelligence Competitions page.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6422/edx-dat102x-data-science-professional-project</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Whitman’s Civil War: Writing and Imaging Loss, Death, and Disaster</title><provider>NovoEd</provider><subject>Literature</subject><school>University of Iowa</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-18</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Welcome! On July 18, 2016, the International Writing Program at the University of Iowa will open the new MOOC Whitman's Civil War: Writing and Imaging Loss, Death, and Disaster. This free open online course will embark upon a journey through Walt Whitman's writings on the American Civil War. Through Whitman's lens, we will explore how writing and image can be used to examine war, conflict, trauma, and reconciliation - in Whitman's time and today. Join us!</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6487/novoed-whitman-s-civil-war-writing-and-imaging-loss-death-and-disaster</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>IDB12x: Políticas efectivas de desarrollo infantil</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Social Sciences</subject><school>IDB ( Inter-American Development Bank )</school><language>English</language><course_hours>7 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-19</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Descripción del curso

***Este curso será impartido en español***

La evidencia científica documenta que los efectos de la adversidad durante la primera infancia perduran en el tiempo y tienen consecuencias sobre el aprendizaje, la trayectoria escolar, los comportamientos de riesgo, el empleo, la salud y otras variables claves para la acumulación de capital humano y el bienestar de las personas.

En la última década los países de América Latina y el Caribe han demostrado un compromiso político y financiero para fortalecer las políticas de desarrollo infantil. Sin embargo, a pesar de estos esfuerzos, todavía existen retos significativos. Por ejemplo, hay muchos niños y familias de los estratos más pobres que no reciben servicios de desarrollo infantil. Además, se sabe que la calidad de estos servicios en la región es baja.

Este curso pretende fortalecer las capacidades de quienes diseñan, implementan y evalúan programas y políticas de desarrollo infantil, con énfasis en aspectos relacionados a la calidad.

Está comprobado que la calidad es indispensable para que los programas de desarrollo infantil resulten en cambios en la trayectoria de desarrollo sostenible en el tiempo.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6407/edx-idb12x-politicas-efectivas-de-desarrollo-infantil</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>DAT101x: Data Science Orientation</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Data Science and Big Data</subject><school>Microsoft</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-05-16</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Learn what it takes to become a data scientist.

This is the first stop in the Data Science curriculum from Microsoft. It will help you get started with the program, plan your learning schedule, and connect with fellow students and teaching assistants. Along the way, you’ll get an introduction to working with and exploring data using a variety of visualization, analytical, and statistical techniques.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6405/edx-dat101x-data-science-orientation</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>How to Ace Your Online Course</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Education &amp; Teaching</subject><school>JER Online</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Reach your true potential in your online course by adopting the educational models, learning strategies, and discussion techniques instructors want you to use.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6426/canvas-net-how-to-ace-your-online-course</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>BL-103: Teaching Each Student</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Education &amp; Teaching</subject><school>Relay Graduate School of Education</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>In a blended/personalized classroom, data can be overwhelming. This course will give you the tools you need to focus your data analysis, so you can provide a more personalized experience for each student.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6427/canvas-net-bl-103-teaching-each-student</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>BL-201: Extending Your Blending</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Education &amp; Teaching</subject><school>Relay Graduate School of Education</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>You’re currently blending your curriculum and have seen how personalization helps push student growth, agency, engagement, and much more. Now it’s your turn to start sharing your best practices, become a blended leader, and extend your reach.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6428/canvas-net-bl-201-extending-your-blending</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>BL-101: Beginning to Blend</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Education &amp; Teaching</subject><school>Relay Graduate School of Education</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Have you ever wanted to have more one-on-one time with students, to engage students in their own learning, or to give students choice around path and pace? If you answered yes to one or more of these questions, this course is for you.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6424/canvas-net-bl-101-beginning-to-blend</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>BL-102: Rolling Out Blended</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Education &amp; Teaching</subject><school>Relay Graduate School of Education</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>When rolling out blended/personalized learning in your classroom or school, there are three key pieces: space, routines, and culture. This course will give you concrete strategies to start rolling out theses key components and blending your practice today.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6425/canvas-net-bl-102-rolling-out-blended</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>PHP Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>If you're new to PHP, this course will give you an overview of many of the language's core concepts.
Syllabus
What is PHP? 
Personal Home Page, Preprocessor, and 80% of the Internet? Let's Learn about PHP. We will go over the basic usage and get started using workspaces.
PHP Data &amp; Structure
Let's learn about PHP variables, statements, comments, and more!
PHP Datatypes 
There are several different datatypes in PHP that you will use on a regular basis. We will begin our introduction to these datatypes here.
PHP Operators
PHP Operators
PHP Conditionals &amp; Loops 
PHP Conditionals &amp; Loops are so common in PHP you will wonder how you ever got by without them.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6433/treehouse-php-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Django Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>4 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>What you'll learn
Django
Django's project and app structure
Django's ORM and migrations
Syllabus
Say Hello to Django
Before we can build anything, we need to get Django installed, start our project, and learn some key concepts.
What a View!
With Django installed and a project started, we'll dive into views, URLs, and how to start an app.
Model Administration
We want to be able to hold data in our application so we need to create at least one model. And once we have a model, we're going to want to be able to create instances of it. Django's ORM and Admin to the rescue!
Django Templates
No application is complete without some sort of user-facing interface. Let's see how to add and use HTML templates in our Django projects. We'll also explore using CSS assets in our project.
Final Details
Our app could use another view and a bit more information for each step. We can add those and finally get some things linked up with a handy new tag.
Test Time
Good applications work. Great applications work and have tests to prove it. Let's see about testing our models, views, urls, and templates.
   </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6438/treehouse-django-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Basic PHP Website</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>5-6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>This project will show you how to build a simple website using the PHP programming language. The web site, a media library, will let you organize and display your Books, Movies and Music. You could easily use this project to create a website that lets you organize and display any type of item: Branch Locations, Products, Services, Events, even Courses like we have here on Treehouse.
What you'll learn
Organizing and Displaying Inventory
Reusing Code
Email and Form Data
Syllabus
Building a Media Library in PHP 
Our media website will have a number of pages, but the pages share a few common elements like the top navigation menu and the footer. We’ll build these shared elements into a set of template files, using basic programming concepts like variables and conditionals to make it all work.
Listing and Sorting Inventory Items
Our media library contains quite a bit of information, too much to fit in simple variables. A PHP array will be perfect for the task, and we’ll explore all the ins and outs of working with arrays to store sets of related data. We’ll also use the data from the array to populate our category pages that shows a list of all the media in our catalog.
Adding a Basic Form
PHP does more than just make a set of HTML files easier to maintain. It also adds advanced functionality to a site that HTML and CSS alone cannot achieve, like sending an email. We’ll create a suggestion form for our website, allowing users to enter a media suggestion into an HTML form and then using PHP to process the form submission.
We want to have separate pages for the different categories of media items, but the layout should be the same on each of these pages. We’ll work with PHP functions, blocks of code that can be called from other blocks of code, to make sure that media items are displayed the same across all list pages. PHP comes with a large number of native functions, but it also provides a way to create our own.
Enhancing a Form
Our suggestion form currently checks that the information submitted by visitors to our site is valid, but we need to improve how validation errors get displayed. We’ll enhance the flow of our code that handles form submissions, displaying error messages within the context of the form and carefully avoiding a common security vulnerability by escaping our output.
   </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6440/treehouse-build-a-basic-php-website</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Simple Ruby on Rails Application</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>8-9 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>This project will walk us through creating a social networking web application with features similar to Facebook. Ruby on Rails is a web application framework which makes it easy and quick to build dynamic web sites.
Syllabus
Getting Started with Rails 
There are many things involved in creating a complicated web application. There are clients, servers, and all of the things in between. This stage walks us through what web applications are and the process of installing Ruby on Rails.
Frontend Development
A large part of creating web applications is designing what the user sees when they view a page. This includes the HTML markup and CSS that styles the pages. This stage introduces views in Ruby on Rails, and how they let us shape the content.
Creating an Authentication System
A common feature of web applications is to allow people to sign up and create an account, and then be able to log in with an email address and password. There are many security concerns that need to be taken into account when implementing such a feature. Fortunately, Ruby on Rails has several pre-built tools to make implementing a login system easy.
Customizing Forms
Forms are an important part of any web application because they are how the user interacts with the app. Creating forms that are easy to use is simple to do with Ruby on Rails when you use the built-in tools and some other popular tools built for Rails.
Writing Tests
Automated testing is a powerful tool that every developer should master. By writing tests that verify your code works as expected, you can reduce the number of unexpected bugs that make your app fail. Writing these tests also helps ensure you don’t break some other part of your app while building a new feature.
Designing URLs
Ruby on Rails includes powerful tools for customizing and routing URLs. We'll show you how to define which URL will point to which page in our app.
Testing the Whole App
In addition to testing small, specific functions of the web application, we also need to test that larger use cases are working properly, by writing higher level tests. We use these tests, called integration tests, to make sure common features like logging in and creating an account work for the user.
Building the Profile Page
The profile page is the foundation of our social network application. Each user will have their own profile page with their own custom URL based on their username. This profile page will initially just show the status updates that the user has posted.
Deploying
The most important step of creating our application is deploying it to the internet. While developing, we run the app locally to test it, but its final home is on the internet. There are many different ways of deploying a web application, but one of the easiest ways is Heroku, which lets you deploy your app for free.
   </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6445/treehouse-build-a-simple-ruby-on-rails-application</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>CSS Foundations</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>12-13 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) is a language used to describe the visual look of a web page. Using CSS, it is possible to change colors, margin, padding, fonts, and much more. This content will consolidate the previously released CSS Foundations and CSS3 in a brand new and updated series.
Syllabus
Getting Started with CSS 
Learn fundamental CSS concepts and how to add CSS to a page.
Selectors
Selectors allow for styling to be applied to particular page elements. This critical concept makes it easy to choose a specific page element and assign CSS.
Advanced Selectors 
Many advanced CSS selectors help keep our markup clean, semantic and flexible by targeting specific elements without the need of a class or an ID.
Values and Units
Every CSS property has a type of value it can accept, such as a predefined keyword, a length unit, or a URL. In this stage, we'll cover common values and units CSS properties accept.
Text, Fonts, and Lists
Text has a significant effect on how we view a web page, and CSS has many options for defining text styles. Font properties also enable us to change the appearance of text by assigning a font family, font size, thickness and more. In this stage, we’ll learn common font properties we can use to enhance our text, along with ways to style our HTML lists.
The Box Model 
Every HTML element, no matter how big or small, can be thought of as a rectangular box made up of content, padding, borders and margins. The Box Model is the basis of CSS layout and positioning, and it dictates how elements are displayed and interact with each other.
Backgrounds and Borders
With CSS, any element can have a background and border applied, and certain properties affect how they appear. In this stage, we'll explore common CSS background and border properties, along with ways to add drop shadows and inner shadows to HTML elements.
Web Typography
Web typography is an exciting and rapidly evolving area of CSS, wherein layout engines like webkit are pushing beyond W3C standards. In this stage, we’ll cover topics such as best practices for choosing a typeface, text layout, responsive text and vertical rhythm. We'll also explore font resources like the @font-face rule, and other detailed font features and techniques that will enhance our text.
CSS Gradients
CSS gradients allow us to display smooth transitions between two or more colors. In this stage, we'll explore linear and radial CSS gradients, along with the differences in browser syntax.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6434/treehouse-css-foundations</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Simple Dynamic Site with Node.js</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Node.js is a versatile platform for building all sorts of applications. In this course, we're going to make a dynamic website that displays a Treehouse student's profile information by creating a server that will dynamically generate content, handle URLs, read from files and build a simple template engine.
  What you'll learn
Creating an HTTP Server
Reading Files
Handling HTTP Methods
Customizing HTTP Headers
Syllabus
Creating a Simple Server in Node.js 
Node.js has awesome APIs that allow you to build all types of applications. Traditionally you'd need to install a server like Apache or NGINX if you wanted to run a static or dynamic website – but Node.js allows you to write your own web server with a simple API call.
Handling Routes in Node.js
When you type in a web address a request is sent to a server. After a domain name, there's a forward slash and then a path to a resource on the server. Sometimes, this is called a route. In this stage, we'll take a look at how to programmatically handle routes in Node.js.
Creating a Basic Template Engine in Node.js 
A lot of our HTML contains the same content so we're going to use a principle called DRY, or Don't Repeat Yourself and separate out the unique content in separate files. We'll also write some code that combines all of this content and put in dynamic values – in other words, we're creating a Template Engine.
HTTP Methods and Headers
Creating your own HTTP servers and web applications requires you to know some of the ins-and-outs of how an HTTP client and HTTP server talk to each other. In this stage we'll take a look at some HTTP headers and HTTP methods.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6439/treehouse-build-a-simple-dynamic-site-with-node-js</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Simple Android App</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Mobile Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>4-5 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>This project covers the very basics of Android development. We will build a simple app that will serve up some fun facts when you tap on a button. We introduce the Java programming language, a tool for Android development called Android Studio, and some very basic concepts of the Android Software Development Kit, or SDK. By the end you will have a good idea of how a basic app works, and you will be armed with the knowledge to start building more.
  What you'll learn
Android Studio
Using an emulator or device
Java basics
Screen layouts
Android Views and Activities
Syllabus
Getting Started with Android 
Making an Android app is easier than you think, and we'll show you how! Learn how to set up and use a few free tools to make a simple Fun Facts app that you can test on your computer. You don't even need an Android phone!
Creating the Screen Layout
Before we start writing any code, let's create the simple screen layout we will use to display our fun facts.
Basic Android Programming
Android apps are typically written in a programming language called Java. Let's take a deeper look at the Java concepts we need to make our button do something.
Coding the Fun Facts
Everything is set for us to add the fun facts to our app. In this stage we'll update the button to pick a new fact and change the color.
Improving Our Code
In this stage we will take a moment to "refactor" our code, which means we'll change a few things and organize it a little better without changing how it works. Then we'll add a new class to help us change the background color for each fact.
Testing and Debugging
We can't always see what's going on behind the scenes of our app, so in this stage we'll learn how to use a few tools to monitor how the Fun Facts app is working and to troubleshoot problems. We'll also see how to run it on a real phone.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6441/treehouse-build-a-simple-android-app</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Introduction to HTML and CSS</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Get started creating web pages with HTML and CSS, the basic building blocks of web development. HTML, or Hypertext Markup Language, is a standard set of tags you will use to tell the web browser how the content of your web pages and applications are structured. Use CSS, or Cascading Style Sheets, to select HTML tags and tell the browser what your content should look like. Whether you are coding for fun or planning to start a career in web development, learning HTML and CSS is a great place to start. 
What you'll learn
Define HTML and CSS
Add and change HTML tags
Modify CSS attributes
Learn the structural foundation of web pages and applications
Syllabus
Getting Familiar with HTML and CSS 
Learn the basic structure of a web page, how HTML and CSS are used to change the structure and appearance of web pages, and how HTML and CSS fit into the larger world of web development.
HTML: The Structural Foundation of Web Pages and Applications
HTML is a series of tags that tells web browsers how to render, or display, a web page. You will wrap the content in these tags to describe the elements on the page and how they should be structured. Learn some useful and commonly used HTML tags and how to use them to start building your web pages.
Make It Beautiful With CSS
CSS, or Cascading Style Sheets, is a system for selecting HTML tags and defining their appearance. From the text, color and alignment, to the height, width and space between them, learn a few different ways to select and style HTML elements using CSS.
Adding a New Web Page
By adding a resume page to the example project, you will get a quick and simple introduction to setting up an HTML document and linking a CSS stylesheet.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6446/treehouse-introduction-to-html-and-css</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Problem Solving with Advanced Analytics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><subject>Business Analytics and Intelligence</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>The Problem Solving with Analytics course provides students with the foundational knowledge to use data analytics to create business insights.
You will learn:
To apply a useful framework to solve a business problem
To determine which analytical method to apply given the nature of the problem and available data
To use linear regression to generate business insights

Throughout this course you’ll also learn the techniques to apply your knowledge in a data analytics program called Alteryx. At the end of the course, you’ll complete a project based on the principles in the course.

This course is part of the Business Analyst Nanodegree.

Why Take This Course?
Using advanced analytics is less about being a statistics wiz and more about understanding how to approach problems and knowing what tools to use. In this course you will be introduced to predictive analytics, a powerful tool to help businesses analyze data and predict future outcomes and trends. You’ll learn a scientific approach to solving problems with data, a foundational skill for anyone interested in making data driven decisions in a business context. You'll be introduced Alteryx, a data analytics tool that enables you prepare, blend, and analyze data quickly. This course is ideal for anyone who is interested in pursuing a career in business analysis, but lacks programming experience.
Syllabus
Lesson 1 - The Analytical Problem Solving Framework

In this lesson you’ll learn a Problem Solving Framework that is useful to approaching any data analytics problem. The framework includes six key steps: business problem understanding, data understanding, data preparation, analysis and modeling, validation, and visualization.

Lesson 2 - Selecting an Analytical Methodology

In this lesson you’ll learn how to determine which analytical approach is most appropriate given the context of the problem and the nature of the available data.

Lesson 3 - Linear Regression

In this course you’ll learn apply the Problem Solving Framework to a business problem using linear regression, a predictive model used to predict numeric outcomes. You’ll first be introduced to regression using just one predictor variable, then how to add more variables to improve the accuracy of the model, and finally how to interpret and use the results.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6458/udacity-problem-solving-with-advanced-analytics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Classification Models</title><provider>Udacity</provider><subject>Business Analytics and Intelligence</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>The Classification Models course provides students with the foundational knowledge to use classification models to create business insights. You will learn:
How classification modeling differs from modeling with numeric data
To use binary classification models to make predictions of binary outcomes
To use non-binary classification models to make predictions of non-binary outcomes

Throughout this course you’ll also learn the techniques to apply your knowledge in a data analytics program called Alteryx. At the end of the course, you’ll complete a project based on the principles in the course.

This course is part of the Business Analyst Nanodegree.

Why Take This Course?
Predictive analytics has proved to be a powerful tool to help businesses analyze data and predict future outcomes and trends. In this course, you’ll learn how to use classification predictive models to solve business problems such as predicting whether or not a customer will respond to a marketing campaign, the likelihood of default on a loan, or which product a customer will buy. You'll learn this through improving your fluency in Alteryx, a data analytics tool that enables you prepare, blend, and analyze data quickly. This course is ideal for anyone who is interested in pursuing a career in business analysis, but lacks programming experience.
Syllabus
Lesson 1 - Introduction to Classification Modeling

In this lesson you’ll learn the key terminology used in predictive modeling, such as the difference between target and predictor variables. You’ll learn key things to consider when choosing variables to use in a model. You’ll also have some practice in preparing a dataset for modeling.

Lesson 2 - Binary Classification Models

In this lesson you’ll learn how to use binary classification models to predict categorical data with two potential results. You’ll learn how to use logistic regression, stepwise logistic regression, and decision tree models; how to compare the models; and how to interpret the results.

Lesson 3 - Non-Binary Classification Models

In this lesson you’ll learn how to use non-binary classification models to predict categorical data with more than two potential results. You’ll learn how to use decision tree, forest, and boosted models; how to compare the models; and how to interpret the results.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6460/udacity-classification-models</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Weather App with Swift</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Mobile Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>In this project, we're going to build a weather app together and broaden our understanding of Swift and Cocoa Touch frameworks. We will start by learning foundational concepts like networking and concurrency while building on our existing knowledge of data modeling, Auto Layout and more. We’ll even take a look at how we can structure our code better and construct decoupled classes and structs that lead to greater code reuse. By the end of this project you will have built your second iOS app and be well on your way to becoming an iOS developer.
  What you'll learn
Networking
Concurrency
JSON
NSURLSession
Syllabus
Simple Data Structures
In the first stage of this course, we’re going to start by using external weather data loaded as a property list. We’ll learn about what property lists are, their advantages and disadvantages and how to use them in our app. We’ll also create a custom model to utilize the data from the plist in our app. Finally, we’ll display information in our view and learn about how we can make our UI conform to different devices using iOS 8’s new feature - Size Classes.
Interacting with Data From the Web 
Even though we use the Web in lots of ways in our daily lives, communicating with the Web and interacting with the information we get is not a trivial task. In this stage we first take a look at some basic networking concepts like making HTTP requests. Then we learn about the notion of concurrency - a property of our system that lets us execute blocks of code simultaneously. This allows us to write networking code that doesn’t keep the user waiting.
Managing Complexity
Our network code works, but our app is somewhat muddied in terms of structure. We could do a better job of making our code more reusable and in this stage we’re going to take what we’ve done so far and split into different classes/structures. This way each object has clear responsibilities.
Adding Weather Icons
Now that we have most of the work done, let’s improve the user interface by adding icons to display the different kinds of weather. We’ll go over how we can use an enumeration to handle Icons rather than dumping it in the CurrentWeather struct.
Refreshing the Data
We have a fully functional weather app that allows our users to check the weather of a specific location whenever they want! Unfortunately, with our current implementation, they cannot refresh the weather to get new information while the app is still open. Let’s add a refresh button and method to allow our users to do this.
     </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6465/treehouse-build-a-weather-app-with-swift</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Creating an Analytical Dataset</title><provider>Udacity</provider><subject>Business Analytics and Intelligence</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>The Creating an Analytical Dataset course provides students with foundational knowledge to input, clean, blend, and format data in preparation for analysis. You will learn:
The common sources and types of data
To identify and correct common issues with data
To format data in useful ways for analysis
To blend data from multiple sources together

Throughout this course you’ll also learn the techniques to apply your knowledge in a data analytics program called Alteryx. At the end of the course, you’ll complete a project based on the principles in the course..

This course is part of the Business Analyst Nanodegree.

Why Take This Course?
Ever heard of the term garbage in, garbage out? This is as true in analytics as it is anywhere else. In this course, you’ll learn how to prepare data to ensure the efficacy of your analysis, a foundational skill for anyone using advanced analytics. You'll learn this through improving your fluency in Alteryx, a data analytics tool that enables you prepare, blend, and analyze data quickly. This course is ideal for anyone who is interested in pursuing a career in business analysis, but lacks programming experience.
Syllabus
Lesson 1 - Understanding Data

In this lesson you’ll learn the differences between structured, unstructured, and semistructured data. You’ll also be introduced to the most common data types: string, number, date/time, boolean, and special characters.

Lesson 2 - Data Issues

In this lesson you’ll learn how clean dirty data and prepare it for analysis. You’ll learn how identify and correct for common data issues like missing data, duplicate data, special characters, and outliers.

Lesson 3 - Data Formatting

In this lesson you’ll learn the impact of the format of the data can have on your analysis. You’ll learn how to use common formatting techniques such as transposing, aggregation, and cross tabulation.

Lesson 4 - Data Blending

In this lesson you’ll learn how to combine data from multiple sources into a single dataset. You’ll learn how to use common blending techniques such as joins, unions, fuzzy matching, and spatial blending.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6459/udacity-creating-an-analytical-dataset</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Making the Transition to Open: The Easy Way to Create, License, and Share Free Materials</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Education &amp; Teaching</subject><school>Scottsdale Community College</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Faculty in any discipline will be initiated into the mysteries of open educational resources (OER): what they are, where to find them, and how to use and share them.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6461/canvas-net-making-the-transition-to-open-the-easy-way-to-create-license-and-share-free-materials</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Node.js Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>In this course we will create a command line application to retrieve user's profile information from the Treehouse website. We'll be writing our application in JavaScript to run on the Node.js platform.
  What you'll learn
Write command line applications in Node.js
Talk to an API with Node.js
Organize your code with modules
Deal with streams
Handle with errors
Syllabus
Introduction to Node.js 
Node.js is a JavaScript environment that allows you to perform a multitude of tasks and build all sorts of exciting applications.
In this section we'll discuss, what node is, why you'd use it and how to use it.
Building a Command Line Application 
Node.js can be used to make all sorts of applications. In this section we'll build our project, a command-line application to retrieve student's profile information from the Treehouse API.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6430/treehouse-node-js-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Java Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Programming</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>In this course you will gain all the knowledge you will need to build an interactive command line program in Java. No prior programming experience is required. You will create an interactive game that prompts users for different parts of a sentence and then generates a story using those words.
  What you'll learn
Write programs in the Java programming language
Use the console to interact with users
Use basic data types to store and name data
Use conditionals and looping to control program flow
Syllabus
Getting Started with Java 
In this stage you will familiarize yourself with Workspaces, your programming environment for this course. We will learn about how to interact with the user using the console object. We will learn about variables, and more specifically, Strings.
Using your New Tools 
In this stage, you will learn how to add multiple formatters to a format string, and we will have a finished prototype. We will also cover what happens if and when you encounter errors.
Perfecting the Prototype
In this stage we will apply feedback we received and add feature enhancements to our prototype. We will add an age restriction and make sure that certain words are not allowed. We will explore branching and looping to solve common problems.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6435/treehouse-java-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build an Interactive Story App with Swift 2</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Mobile Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>One of the most fundamental types of apps you can create is one with a hierarchical data model and style of navigation. In this course we're going to learn exactly how to do that by building an interactive story app. We'll cover a lot of ground by exploring navigation controllers, hierarchical data models and custom view controllers.
We'll go over how to accept user input, how to create and layout views programmatically, how to play sound effects and much more. At the end of this course, you will have the knowledge to build many of the basic apps you see in the app store.
What you'll learn
UINavigationController
Notifications
Layout anchors and constraints
Audio APIs
Syllabus
Navigating Through An Adventure 
One of the most fundamental types of apps you can create is one with a hierarchical data model and style of navigation. In this course we're going to learn exactly how to do that by building an interactive story app. In the next set of videos we'll start by exploring what a navigation controller is, how to add one to our app and how to transition to different views.
Creating a Story
All apps need a model to work with and over the next set of videos we're going to build the model layer to power our story. Since the model involves many moving parts, we'll break things up by building a Story object to represent the narrative, a Page object to represent a page in a story and a wrapper object to create an adventure with the two components.
Creating the User Interface Programmatically
So far we've only created and laid out views using a Storyboard scene but you can do every single thing that's possible in a Storyboard in code as well. Over the next few videos, we're going to create, position and size the entire user interface for the PageController in code. We'll learn how to use layout anchors and create constraints programmatically as well as how to add views to the navigation stack.
Refactoring the Model Layer
Our app is essentially complete, but we'd like to offer users the ability to customize the story by inserting their name at certain points. For this we need to both refactor the model and add a new UI element. Over the next set of videos, we'll modify the Story enum to allow this and add a text field to the first page in our app. This won't be simple though and as you'll see we'll have to move the text field around to accommodate this new design.
Adding Sound Effects
To round this course off let's add a fun feature where we play a sound every time a user selects a choice. We'll keep this short and simple and figure out how we can use the simplest (but not the safest!) audio API to play a system sound.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6442/treehouse-build-an-interactive-story-app-with-swift-2</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>How to Make a Website</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>8-9 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>If you’ve never built a website before and you have no coding or design experience, this is the place to start. In this project, we learn how to build a modern portfolio website for desktops, tablets, and mobile devices. We start with basic HTML and CSS syntax. Next, we learn how to build custom web pages with an image gallery and contact page. Finally, we walk through how to share a website live on the web.
What you'll learn
How to write basic HTML
How to style web pages with CSS
How to purchase a domain and hosting
How to upload files
Syllabus
Beginning HTML and CSS 
In this quick tutorial, we’ll check out an example of the final web project we’re aiming to build. Then, we’ll learn how to code our first HTML element, which will help form the structure of our website. Finally, we’ll finish up by styling our website with some simple CSS. These two languages, HTML and CSS, form the basic building blocks of any web project.
HTML First
HTML is a special computer language that describes the structure of a document. With HTML, we can build web pages that contain text, images, and many other types of content. First, we’ll get started with a quick history lesson. Then we’ll dig into the latest advancements in HTML by creating a simple page structure.
Creating HTML Content 
When building websites, it's best to write as much of the HTML structure as possible before moving on to CSS. In practice, you'll move back and forth between HTML and CSS, but building most of the structure first will make it an easier process. First we will start by creating the navigation for our site. Then, we can move on to structuring the image gallery and other page content. Finally, we'll finish by including a CSS file into our HTML page.
CSS: Cascading Style Sheets 
CSS is a language that allows us to make designs that are well organized and beautiful. While HTML describes the structure of information, CSS describes how that information should be visually presented. Before we start coding the CSS for our site, we will spend some time learning about the syntax of CSS.
Customizing Colors and Fonts
Colors in CSS require a special coded format called hexadecimal. We will first learn about hexadecimal numbers and then we can use them in our color values. Then, we’ll learn how to find licensed fonts as well as how to include fonts in a webpage.
Styling Web Pages and Navigation
The techniques necessary for styling an image gallery as well as horizontal navigation are actually quite similar. First, we will learn how to style a group of images and convert them into rows and columns for our image gallery. Then, we will use a similar CSS technique to create horizontal navigation from an unordered list.
Adding Pages to a Website 
When multiple web pages are linked together, the pages become collectively known as a website. The home page will serve as the template for both our contact page and about page. In both pages, we will learn some new CSS techniques.
Responsive Web Design and Testing
Modern websites are built with mobile and desktop users in mind. By building our site with fluid percentages (instead of fixed pixels), we’re off to a good start. However, we can add special CSS rules called media queries to further enhance the experience. After adding responsive design, we will test the site on a few devices.
Sharing a Website
We're finished coding our website and now it's time to deploy it live to the web so that other people can see it. First, we will purchase our domain and hosting. Then, we will use the File Transfer Protocol (FTP) to put our files onto our server.
  Debugging HTML and CSS Problems
When creating websites, problem solving skills are essential. First, we will learn how to access the developer tools to find problems with our code. Then, we will walk through some common HTML and CSS issues and how to fix them quickly.
 </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6447/treehouse-how-to-make-a-website</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>CSS - Beyond the Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>4-5 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>In this intermediate to advanced course, we'll take an in-depth look at some of the latest features in CSS. 
Learn how to use flexbox and multiple columns for layout. See how animations, transitions, and transforms can enhance a website's design. We'll also expand upon the media query concepts learned in CSS Basics.
What you'll learn
Flexbox and Multi-Column Layout
CSS Animations
Transitions and Transforms
Media Queries
Syllabus
Understanding Flexbox and Multi-Column Layout
With multi-column layouts, we can easily define multiple columns of text. One of the benefits of using CSS-based columns is flexibility; content flows from one column to another, and the number of columns can vary depending on the size of the device or viewport.
Flexbox is a powerful new feature that makes CSS more efficient for layout. Elements can be dynamically rearranged on the page, laid out in any direction, have flexible dimensions to adapt to the display space, and much more!
Understanding CSS Transitions and Transforms
CSS transitions provide a way to control property changes over a given duration. We can also specify time intervals, durations and timing functions that follow a customizable acceleration curve.
CSS transforms let us change the position of elements without disrupting the normal document flow. Transforms are implemented using properties that let us apply transformations like rotation, skewing, scaling and translation in both the plane and 3D space.
CSS Animation Basics 
CSS animations change properties over time using keyframes to indicate the start/end states of the animations and intermediate points along the way. We're able to control animations by including iteration values, delaying their start time, play states, and more.
Working with Media Queries
Media queries allow designers to apply CSS declarations dynamically based on client conditions. Using media features like width, height and color, we can tailor our content to a wide range of devices and resolutions without having to change the content itself.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6429/treehouse-css-beyond-the-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>CSS Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>8 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) is a style sheet language that describes the presentation of web pages. Whereas HTML is what forms the structure of a web page, CSS is what we use to style the HTML with colors, backgrounds, font sizes, layout, and more. As you'll soon learn, CSS is one of the core technologies for designing and building websites.
  What you'll learn
Basic Selectors
Common Values and Units
CSS Layout
New CSS Features
Syllabus
Getting Started with CSS 
Get started with one of the core technologies for designing and building websites and applications. In this stage, you'll learn about the evolution of CSS, helpful resources, and how to add CSS to a page.
Basic Selectors
Selectors are one of the most important and powerful parts of CSS. In this stage, you'll learn the different ways we can target HTML elements with basic selectors.
Understanding Values and Units 
Every CSS property has a set of values it can accept. Most properties accept keywords that literally describe a value. Many properties also accept numbers, functions, length values, or a URL. In this stage, you'll learn the common values and units CSS properties accept.
The Box Model 
The box model is the basis of CSS layout because it dictates how elements are displayed and how they interact with each other.
Basic Layout
In this stage, we'll continue styling our website with background properties and basic layout methods.
Designing with the Latest Features
Today's CSS features are becoming closer to tools we'd normally use in a graphics editor. CSS has introduced many in-browser design features like rounded corners, box shadows, gradients, and more. In this stage, we'll add the finishing touches to our page using many of the latest features introduced to CSS. Then, make sure our page looks good on all devices with media queries.
Fundamental Concepts
Now that we've explored many of the core features of CSS, it's time to take this knowledge further by learning important fundamental concepts. In this stage, you'll learn all about the CSS cascade, inheritance, and helpful tips and tools to practice and retain what you’re learning.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6431/treehouse-css-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Angular Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Angular is a front end JavaScript framework that allows you to rapidly develop robust, single page web applications. In this course you’ll learn the basics of how to get an Angular application set up and running. Additionally, you’ll get a strong conceptual overview and foundation in Angular. You’ll be able to use the knowledge gained from this course to start your own applications or to easily jump in on existing large scale applications.
  What you'll learn
Angular Application Structure - MVC without saying MVC
Templates/Views
Directives
Scope
Controllers
Basic built-ins
ng-repeat
ng-show
ng-hide
ng-click
Requesting data with $http
Syllabus
Getting Started with Angular 
Angular is one of the most exciting technologies around. It’s a web framework that’s been adopted by fast growing startups, as well as large companies. But, as awesome as Angular is, it has a very steep learning curve!
In this stage we'll get aquainted with Angular concepts, and its often times confusing vernacular.
Controllers and Scope
Controllers are the glue that holds your application together. Using controllers you can create functions that do everything from handle how the user interface should look based on user interactions, to changing data in the application.
Using Angular's Built In Directives 
Angular has built in directives that make all sorts of tedious development tasks easy and straight forward. In this stage, you'll learn how to use these directives.
Services in Angular
Where controllers are the set of application logic that control the user interface and operate within a limited scope, services allow you to create a reusable set of functions and values that can be passed across the application. Services are useful for getting data from a database, as well as firing save, edit, and delete operations.
In this course, you'll learn how to add services to your application.
Improving Our Todo App 
In the following videos, we'll add some fine improvements to our application. We'll improve the overall user experience of our application and enhance our usage of angular's built in directives.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6436/treehouse-angular-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Vending Machine App in Swift 2.0</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Mobile Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>In this course, you will build a simple app that models a vending machine in the real world. The aim of the course is to understand errors in our code and how we handle situations that are unexpected or incorrect. In addition, we will take a look at how to use stock controls in iOS and understand how views are arranged in an app. Towards the end you should have a good grasp on how to create and respond to your own error conditions and include multiple screens in your app.
What you'll learn
- Error handling
- Multiple views
- UI Controls
Syllabus
Modeling An Interface 
Before we can actually work on buying items from a vending machine, we need think about the architecture of our app. In this stage we lay the groundwork for our models with a series of protocols and look at how we can make our code safer by using custom types.
Loading Data From a Resource
Rather than hard code the data into our app, we’re going to work with an external resource. Part of this approach includes making our objects flexible so that the source of the data doesn’t matter while the rest includes understanding how to convert data from a generic format to our custom types.
Using the Vending Machine
Now that we have an inventory created from a property list file, let’s add implementations for the rest of the vending machine logic. In this stage we look at how we can display the correct icons, add a stepper to modify the quantity and improve our user interface.
Displaying Additional Views
When building mobile apps we aren't restricted to a single view. In this stage, we're going to take a look at one of the ways we can present additional information using modal views.
 </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6443/treehouse-build-a-vending-machine-app-in-swift-2-0</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>JavaScript Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6-7 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>JavaScript is a programming language that drives the web: from front-end user interface design, to backend server-side programming, you'll find JavaScript at every stage of a web site and web application. In this course, you'll learn the fundamental programming concepts and syntax of the JavaScript programming language.
  What you'll learn
What JavaScript is and where it is used
Basic programming concepts like variables, data types and conditional statements
What functions are and why they're useful
How to troubleshoot programming problems
The basic syntax of the JavaScript programming language
Syllabus
Introducing JavaScript 
Learn about the most popular scripting language on the planet. The language that drives millions of interactive web sites, powers fast web servers and can even be used to build desktop applications. In this stage, you'll create your first JavaScript program and learn how to troubleshoot your programming mistakes.
Storing and Tracking Information with Variables
Learn how to use variables to store information that changes during a program, like the score in a game, or a sales total. You'll also learn about different data types in JavaScript like string, numbers and boolean values.
Working With Numbers
Numbers are everywhere in programming. You use them to track a player's score in a game, to calculate the cost of shipping a product, or just to count the number of times a "Like" button was clicked on a page. In this section of the course, you'll learn how to do basic math in JavaScript.
Making Decisions with Conditional Statements
Conditional statements let you control the "flow" of your program. They let you run different code based on conditions in your program.
Creating Reusable Code with Functions
JavaScript functions are a powerful tool that let you create re-usable chunks of code. They make programming faster, easier and less error-prone. They are also one of the most important concepts in JavaScript programming.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6432/treehouse-javascript-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Express Basics</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>Express is a "Fast, unopinionated, minimalist web framework for node." In this course you'll learn how to build an Express site from scratch!
Syllabus
Getting Started with Express 
Express is the most popular web server for Node.js. Self described as a “Fast, un-opinionated, minimalist web framework for node.js.”, Express is open and flexible, allowing you to write only the code that you need, and nothing more.
Developing Express Apps Like a Boss
As a developer “how” you work is just as important as “what” you are working on. Having the right tools and strategies at your disposable can make the difference in a successful and on time project.
The Request and Response Objects in Express
The request an response object house all of the complex information that goes into HTTP requests made to Express, and the HTTP responses that it delivers.
The request and response objects themselves can appear complex at first. And they are! The reality is that they save you, the developer, tons of time.
In this stage you'll learn how to use the HTTP request and response objects.
Using Templates with Express
Templates are common across all web frameworks and are commonly used in many different kinds of web applications. In this stage, you will learn about the Jade template engine and its syntax.
Serving Static Files in Express
Static files, like JavaScript, CSS, and images, are a central part of any any website. Express comes with a built in middleware to serve static files, suitable for use in development and for sites with smaller amounts of traffic.
Doing more with Express
  In this stage you will learn some ways you can use Jade syntax to make development easier.
Additionally, you'll learn how to use the Express generator to quickly set up a new express project.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6437/treehouse-express-basics</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Build a Social Network with Flask</title><provider>Treehouse</provider><subject>Web Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>4-5 hours worth of material</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>It's time to dig in and build something big. In this course, we're going to take the tools we've learned, Flask, Peewee, and Python itself, and build a small social network. We'll have user registration, user authentication, strongly hashed passwords, form validation, and more.
What you'll learn
User registration and authentication
Password hashing
Form validation
Joins
Syllabus
Making Strong Users 
We won't get far in our social application with out users. Let's make sure their passwords are stored correctly and strongly, too.
Takin' Names 
Users need a way to sign up and sign in to our site. We'll need to validate their information, create our model instances, and store their session information. Luckily, we have a few handy libraries to do a lot of that for us!
Broadcasting
Our app needs messages posted by the users. Let's give them a model, a form, and the views necessary so they can tell the world what they're up to.
How to Win Friends
The final ingredient in any social site is the ability to follow people. We'll need to add a new model, a couple of views, and tweak a template or two. We'll also want to change a query or two to get the full social experience
Tacocat Challenge
Now that you've built an app along with me, and another in code challenges, try and build one on your own. You have a full suite of tests to validate your work.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6444/treehouse-build-a-social-network-with-flask</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Google Maps APIs</title><provider>Udacity</provider><subject>Programming</subject><school>Google</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-09</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>This course will introduce you to the content available through the Google Maps APIs. You’ll be walked through building a real-estate listings site step-by-step, using a beautifully styled Google map, data visualization, street view panoramas, and various nifty location related features such as calculating distance between locations, getting directions, and viewing places of interest data. You’ll also see other examples of Google Maps APIs in action, and understand how to put your new knowledge into practice by creating your own Project in the Google APIs Console.

Why Take This Course?
As a Web Developer, it can be valuable to add location related features and map visualizations into your websites. Google Maps in a site are engaging, familiar, and reliable for your users-- and the Google Maps APIs make developing with them easy.
Syllabus
You will learn how to use the Google Maps APIs to integrate maps and location features into a website, and how to make in-browser web service calls to various Web Service APIs.

## Syllabus

### Lesson 1: Getting Started with the APIs
Practice loading the Google Maps JavaScript API and creating a map, styling it, showing markers and infowindows, loading and use various libraries, and creating street view panoramas. Learn about the Static Maps and Street View imagery APIs.

### Lesson 2: Understanding API Services
Learn when to use Web Services vs. Services within the JavaScript API. Practice getting addresses from coordinates, calculating the distances, travel times, and directions between multiple locations, obtaining the elevation or time zone of a point, and looking for places of interest around a location/matching a search query.

### Lesson 3: Using the APIs in Practice
Learn about monitoring your projects API usage, and securing your identifiers. Check out where to go with questions, how to find information in our documentation. Familiarize with some terms of use and other important details.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6477/udacity-google-maps-apis</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Gary England's El Niño</title><provider>Janux</provider><subject>Environmental Science</subject><school>The University of Oklahoma</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-11</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>You and your family, business organization, civic group, or classroom can now enjoy a fun and entertaining way to learn about our weather from Oklahoma’s own Gary England! The University of Oklahoma and award-winning meteorologist Gary England have collaborated to create two exciting series.
“Gary England’s Tornado Alley” consists of short, entertaining videos that give people of all ages a better understanding of Oklahoma’s severe weather patterns and events. This entertaining series makes it easy and fun for you to become familiar with the fundamentals of our weather, the history of weather forecasting, and the technology used by meteorology professionals to keep the public as safe as possible. Using Janux's social discussion forum, participants are able to interact directly with Gary and share their own weather stories and experiences with people around the globe.
“Gary England’s El Niño” is the newest Sooner Series, diving into the causes of El Niño and the effects it has on all parts of the world. The 2015 El Niño is quite possibly the strongest El Niño in history, and Gary’s use of incredible graphics helps explain the abnormal weather conditions that we have been experiencing over the last several months. These powerful visuals combined with Gary’s expertise provide an unparalleled opportunity to learn more about this force of nature.
Both series are being offered at no cost through multiple media channels, including iTunes U, YouTube, and OU’s Janux online learning platform.
These videos have been professionally produced by NextThought, and each series has been released in its entirety, so as to fit your schedule.
Syllabus
The Miracle of El Niño
From Darwin to Tahiti
Riding the Jet
Going Deep
As the Ocean Moves
Making Waves
Pacific North American Pattern
Mother Nature on Stage
Oceans Seven
Hurricanes and Tornadoes
History Guides the Future
Everything is Connected</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6482/janux-gary-england-s-el-nino</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Concurrency</title><provider>Independent</provider><subject>Programming</subject><school>AdaCore University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-12</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>This course describes how to develop concurrent application using Ada, in particular through the notion of task and protected object.
Syllabus
1. Basic Concepts of Concurrency</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6493/concurrency</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Getting Started: Writing for Graduate School</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Grammar &amp; Writing</subject><school>Barry University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-07-11</session></course_sessions><pace>Self Paced</pace><certification_available>Self Paced</certification_available><description>This course is designed to develop undergraduate research writing skills by focusing on the expectations of this specialized form of writing.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6423/canvas-net-getting-started-writing-for-graduate-school</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Bioelectricity: The Mechanism of Origin of Extracellular Potentials</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Biology</subject><school>Duke University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-01</session><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Most people know that electrically active cells in nerves, in the heart and in the brain generate electrical currents, and that somehow these result in measurements we all have heard about, such as the electrocardiogram. But how? That is, what is it that happens within the electrically active tissue that leads to the creation of currents and voltages in their surroundings that reflect the excitation sequences timing, and condition of the underlying tissue. This course explores that topic. Rather than being a primer on how to interpret waveforms of any kind in terms of normality or disease, the goal here is to provide insight into how the mechanism of origin actually works, and to do so with simple examples that are readily pictured with simple sketches and one’s imagination, and then moving forward into comparison with experiments and finding outcomes quantitatively.
Syllabus
Week 1
A brief history of extracellular measurements, and an example of such a recording. The goal is to understand the amplitudes and time variation of such measurements, as well as learn about some interesting and useful historical events.

Week 2
A presentation of the cylindrical fiber model of a nerve. The goal is to see how this geometrically simple model of a nerve actually is sufficient to explain complex bioelectric events within and around electrically active tissue. One learns that currents are driven forward by voltages across cell membranes,. Current loops are created, with some parts of the current loop inside and other parts outside the active cells. Electrical potentials are created by the current loops, and are positive when these are approaching, negative when they are receding. In so doing they form the basis of all extracellular wave forms.

Week 3
Notable and useful aspects of extracellular wave forms are their changes in shape. What causes such changes? Two illuminating examples are studied, one that does not, and then another that does.

Week 4
Weeks 1 to 3 present some intriguing concepts and explain them with drawings and sketches. Do the wave forms so drawn have any connection with real tissue? Indeed they do. The goal of this week is to examine some specific experimental wave forms that were measured in cardiac Punkinje fibers, and to compare them those anticipated in earlier weeks.Week 4 is the end of the standard course. The remaining weeks are for honors study.

Week 5
The concepts of week 3 give insight, but there is power in equations and numbers. The goal of week 5 is to show how the models of week 3 can be represented quantitatively, so that one can go beyond asking “What?” and ask “How much?” With equations available, the lectures and questions for this week focus on finding specific numerical results for several examples.

Week 6
This week’s goal is to introduce the concept and the mathematical definition of dipole sources. Such sources pair a current source and current sink, separated in a specific orientation by a small distance. A dipole model allows easy evaluation of many electrode configurations, such as the widely used “bipolar” configuration, often used experimentally to determine the timing of excitation. More extensive models also allow consideration of action potential repolarization (return to resting potentials) as well as excitation.

Week 7
As a conclusion to the course, two diverse subjects are considered. One, the multipole expansion, is used when one has no model of the true origin of observed potentials but still needs to create an “equivalent” model to represent the data. The other, cardiac excitation, is characterized by large, broad excitation waves. One sees that an equation for the extracellular potentials has the same components as the expression for a simple cylindrical fiber, translated into a geometrically suitable form.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6419/coursera-bioelectricity-the-mechanism-of-origin-of-extracellular-potentials</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Big Data Integration and Processing</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Data Science and Big Data</subject><school>University of California, San Diego</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-01</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>At the end of the course, you will be able to:

*Retrieve data from example database and big data management systems
*Describe the connections between data management operations and the big data processing patterns needed to utilize them in large-scale analytical applications
*Identify when a big data problem needs data integration
*Execute simple big data integration and processing on Hadoop and Spark platforms

This course is for those new to data science. Completion of Intro to Big Data is recommended. No prior programming experience is needed, although the ability to install applications and utilize a virtual machine is necessary to complete the hands-on assignments. Refer to the specialization technical requirements for complete hardware and software specifications.

Hardware Requirements:
(A) Quad Core Processor (VT-x or AMD-V support recommended), 64-bit; (B) 8 GB RAM; (C) 20 GB disk free. How to find your hardware information: (Windows): Open System by clicking the Start button, right-clicking Computer, and then clicking Properties; (Mac): Open Overview by clicking on the Apple menu and clicking “About This Mac.” Most computers with 8 GB RAM purchased in the last 3 years will meet the minimum requirements.You will need a high speed internet connection because you will be downloading files up to 4 Gb in size.

Software Requirements:
This course relies on several open-source software tools, including Apache Hadoop. All required software can be downloaded and installed free of charge (except for data charges from your internet provider). Software requirements include: Windows 7+, Mac OS X 10.10+, Ubuntu 14.04+ or CentOS 6+ VirtualBox 5+.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6467/coursera-big-data-integration-and-processing</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Medical Humanity: Engaging Patients and Communities in Healthcare</title><provider>FutureLearn</provider><subject>Health Care &amp; Research</subject><school>Taipei Medical University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-08</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>The development of healthcare treatments has given people hope to fight diseases. However, humans are born to be afraid of advanced technologies.
As such, it is critical that medical professionals have the skills to explain the benefits of treatments to patients and, ideally, involve them in the development of new treatments in the first place.
Engage patients in the development of healthcare technology and treatments
This free online course explores the concept of doctors as “mediators” in the changing relationship between patients and technology, and introduces the theme of “medical humanity” to improve communication and trust in healthcare.
You will find out how to bring patients into the development of medical technologies and treatments.
Traditionally, patients have been the “test” or “observation” subjects in science research, after tools have already been invented. But we will show you how to identify patients’ real needs, design prototypes to meet them and then interview patients, to find out how the prototypes can be modified.
Using real-life examples from Taiwan and South East Asia, the course will help you to understand:
the basic principles of community engagement;
the concept of “living labs”;
how to listen to people and use their oral histories as part of healthcare service design;
how to make elders or minority groups an integral part of designing new medical technologies; and why you should consider technology as a tool for conscious social change.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6495/futurelearn-medical-humanity-engaging-patients-and-communities-in-healthcare</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>ga068: はじめてのＰ</title><provider>gacco</provider><subject>Programming</subject><school>National Institute of Informatics</school><language>Japanese</language><course_hours>4-5 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-09</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>現代社会のありとあらゆる場所にはコンピュータがあり、それらは全てプログラムで動いています。国立情報学研究所のプログラミング入門講座「はじめてのP」は、できるだけ多くの方にプログラミングの魅力を伝えたい、自分の可能性を広げてほしい、そんな思いを込めた、プログラミングの基礎を実践型で学ぶ講座です。
この講座は、初めてプログラミングを学ぶ高校生以上を対象としています。初心者向けの基礎だけでなく、ある程度プログラミング経験のある方にも参加いただけるような、JMOOCで初めての新しい企画です。タレントでありエンジニアでもある池澤あやかさんと一緒に、国立情報学研究所の若手研究者達からプログラミングのいろはを学びましょう。
プログラミングを学べば皆さんの人生が大きく変わるかもしれません。</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6492/gacco-ga068-p</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>The Road to the White House: The 2016 Presidential Election</title><provider>Open Education by Blackboard</provider><subject>Political Science</subject><school>Pace University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-15</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description/><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6484/open-education-by-blackboard-the-road-to-the-white-house-the-2016-presidential-election</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Managing for a Changing Climate</title><provider>Janux</provider><subject>Environmental Science</subject><school>The University of Oklahoma</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-22</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This course will provide an integrative understanding of the components of the climate system including the range of natural climate variability and external drivers of climate change, in addition to impacts of a changing climate on multiple sectors such as the economy, policy, ecosystems, and indigenous populations.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6464/janux-managing-for-a-changing-climate</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Maths for Humans: Inverse Relations and Power Laws</title><provider>FutureLearn</provider><subject>Mathematics</subject><school>University of New South Wales</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-22</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>What’s the connection between the size of a city and the number of gas stations in it? How would you describe this relationship? How would you try to visualise and understand it?
Study real-world connections using algebra and geometry
In this free online course, we’ll look at a wide spectrum of interesting, and often surprising, mathematical relationships in our everyday world. We’ll be studying inverse relations, which complement direct relationships; power laws that occur in economics, physics and biology; as well as curious applications of the logarithm function. We’ll visualise these real-world interconnections using graph paper and pencil, and also modern graphing software such as GeoGebra and Desmos.
The functions and graphs in this course help us to make predictions, evaluate actions and test theories about population distributions, the frequencies of common words in texts, scaling laws in biology and much more. We’ll even see some applications to detecting fraud!
Explore inverse and power relationships
In Week 1 you’ll meet hyperbolas and inverse relations, which are complementary to the direct proportionality that we studied in Maths for Humans: Linear and Quadratic Relations. You’ll learn to represent such relationships algebraically, and understand them geometrically in the Cartesian plane in a direct visual way.
In subsequent weeks, we’ll look at Zipf’s law and Benford’s law, check out applications in engineering and physics, investigate power relations and higher degree polynomials, and explore allometry in biology. You will see the history, look at lots of examples, and get useful insights into: lifespans, whether exercise really is good for you, the distribution of wealth, and the crazy claw of the Fiddler crab. And lots of other juicy applications of advanced high school mathematics.
Gain valuable skills for further study
Understanding basic mathematical relationships is vital to many fields of study: biology, engineering, business, economics, political science and design. By the end of this course, you’ll have hands-on experience with a wide range of explicit examples, be familiar with a core area of pre-calculus mathematics, and be ready to go on to more advanced study of calculus or linear algebra.
Whether you’re encountering these topics for the first time or brushing up on your high school mathematics, we hope you’ll actively join our community on this journey through some fascinating and practical topics that have contributed much to our understanding of the world around us.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6417/futurelearn-maths-for-humans-inverse-relations-and-power-laws</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>ENV1x: Environmental Studies: A Global Perspective</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Environmental Science</subject><school>Curtin University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-22</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This environmental studies course is intended to introduce you to some of the basic principles in environmental studies, and how those are manifested in urban, rural and natural areas throughout the world.

Through observation, discussion, and creation of geo-referenced digital content, you will explore and share environmental challenges facing your local environment and create a global learning and action community.

Rather than simply offering a long list of the problems we face, this course will take a solutions-focused approach.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6474/edx-env1x-environmental-studies-a-global-perspective</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Leer a Macondo: La obra de Gabriel García Márquez</title><provider>FutureLearn</provider><subject>Literature</subject><school>Universidad de los Andes</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-29</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>¡Bienvenidos al curso Leer a Macondo!
Gabriel García Márquez es un escritor colombiano que ganó el premio Nobel de Literatura en 1982 y ha sido reconocido como uno de los escritores más importantes del siglo XX. Sus obras han sido traducidas a más de 35 idiomas, han sido adaptadas para televisión y cine y han inspirado múltiples obras de arte.
Explore 5 de las primeras obras del autor, que están relacionadas con Macondo.
El principal objetivo de este curso es explorar las contribuciones literarias de Gabriel García Márquez a la literatura universal a través de cinco de sus primeras obras, todas con una fuerte relación con Macondo, un pueblo inspirado en Aracataca, el lugar de nacimiento del autor en Colombia. Ante todo, usted tendrá la oportunidad de gozar de la lectura y el análisis de las siguientes obras:
La hojarasca (1955),
El coronel no tiene quien le escriba (1961),
La mala hora (1962),
Los funerales de la Mamá Grande (1962) y
Cien años de soledad (1967).
Al entrar en el universo narrativo de García Márquez, usted se dejará seducir por la riqueza de su lenguaje y logrará identificar las obsesiones del autor. A través del estudio de estas obras usted:
Valorará la obra de Gabriel García Márquez
Apreciará la forma en que evoluciona
Desarrollará la capacidad de relacionar sus diferentes obras
Identificará algunos de los elementos centrales de su obra
Este curso está dirigido a personas que disfrutan de la literatura y no requiere ningún tipo de conocimiento previo.
Aprenda acerca de Gabriel García Márquez acompañado de profesores experto de Bogotá, Colombia
Sus guías para este curso son profesores de literatura de la Facultad de Artes y Humanidades de la Universidad de los Andes, Colombia, expertos en el análisis de la obra de Gabriel García Márquez, quienes le brindarán una perspectiva única acerca de la narrativa de este autor.
¡Esperamos que sea una experiencia enriquecedora y que disfrutemos juntos de las obras de Gabriel García Márquez!.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6476/futurelearn-leer-a-macondo-la-obra-de-gabriel-garcia-marquez</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>DAT203.3x: Applied Machine Learning</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Data Science and Big Data</subject><school>Microsoft</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-08-29</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>In this data science course, you will explore the theory and practice of select advanced methods commonly used in data science.

In the first two modules, you will learn about common applications of specialized data types. Then, in the remaining two modules, you will focus on unstructured data. You will work with tools such as R, Python, and Azure Machine Learning to solve advanced data science problems.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6406/edx-dat203-3x-applied-machine-learning</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>ga067: アンコール･ワット研究 ―「人間」を考える総合学問としての新地平―</title><provider>gacco</provider><subject>History</subject><school>Sophia University</school><language>Japanese</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-01</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>本講座では、アンコール・ワットを軸に据えてその歴史、文化、宗教、社会、そして現代に至るまでの人々の営みについて、先行研究及び最新の調査・研究成果を踏まえながら理解することを目的とします。アンコール・ワットをめぐる諸学問への学びを通して、現代カンボジアへの理解も深めます。カンボジアに研究拠点をもつ上智大学ならではの、現地の映像も盛り込んだ資料を提供します。</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6489/gacco-ga067----</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Shakespeare: Print and Performance</title><provider>FutureLearn</provider><subject>Literature</subject><school>King's College London</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-05</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Why do we continue to read and perform Shakespeare’s works around the world today? How were his plays performed and printed 400 years ago, and how has our conception of Shakespeare changed over the centuries?
As part of the Shakespeare400 consortium of events, marking 400 years since his death, King’s College London has partnered with Shakespeare’s Globe and the British Library to explore how Shakespeare’s works continue to delight audiences around the world.
Join academics, curators, publishers, actors, musicians and theatre directors, as we find out more about Shakespeare’s early modern world and consider his construction as a global icon today.
Go behind-the-scenes at The Globe
We will take you on to the stage of the Globe Theatre, to find out about performance practices both in the present day capital and in Early Modern London.
We’ll meet practitioners at the Globe and we’ll step into the world of the early modern actor to examine the processes and conditions that were at the heart of the Shakespearean playhouse.
Explore rarely-seen priceless manuscripts
The British Library has given us exclusive access to some some priceless manuscripts and early printed texts in their archives. We’ll also discover how the early modern book trade shaped the journey of Shakespeare’s text from stage to page.
Share your own insights with other learners
‘Global Shakespeares’ is one of the key themes which we will explore on the course. When you join Shakespeare: Print and Performance, you will become part of a diverse international learning community, and we will draw on everyone’s experiences of Shakespeare to enrich our discussion.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6472/futurelearn-shakespeare-print-and-performance</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>ga019: よくわかる！iPS細胞</title><provider>gacco</provider><subject>Biology</subject><school>Kyoto University</school><language>Japanese</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>この講義では、2012年にノーベル生理学・医学賞を受賞した山中伸弥教授が開発した「iPS細胞（人工多能性幹細胞）」について、基礎知識から医療応用への課題まで概説します。講師は、山中教授が所長を務める京都大学iPS細胞研究所 国際広報室のサイエンスコミュニケーター。研究の最前線から、わかりやすくお伝えします。講義の終了後、ニュースや新聞でiPS細胞に関する情報を目にした時に、ご自身の知識の深まりを実感いただけると思います。この講座を通して、多くの方と新しい医療への道のりを共有できればと考えています。
「第1週：iPS細胞とは」では、iPS細胞発見に至るまでの研究の流れや安全性の向上など、iPS細胞そのものについての知識を深めます。
「第2週：再生医療への応用」では、iPS細胞の医療応用の大きな柱である再生医療について学びます。具体的には、「パーキンソン病」や「がん」の治療に向けた研究などに加え、将来多くの方に再生医療による治療を提供するための「iPS細胞ストック」についてもご紹介します。
「第3週：創薬への応用」では、患者さんの細胞から作製したiPS細胞がなぜ難病の原因解明に使えるのか、どのように創薬に貢献しつつあるかに加え、将来的な個別化医療の可能性についてご説明します。
「第4週：iPS細胞研究を支える仕組み」では、実用化の基盤となる知的財産（特許）の確保や、倫理的な課題、寄付等による研究資金の確保、一般の方々とのコミュニケーション等のテーマについて扱います。この週は特に「自分ならどう考えるか」という視点で学んでいただき、これまで得た知識とあわせて、iPS細胞研究についての総合的な理解を目指します。
 </description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6488/gacco-ga019--ips</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>ELEN7070x: Research Methods: An Engineering Approach</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Engineering</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-07</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>A PhD or master’s level research project is an enormous undertaking, and you might find yourself a bit uncertain about the process or how to achieve the desired outcome. In this research course, you will learn the underlying principles that are needed to conduct research from an engineering perspective.

This course is designed for engineering students conducting postgraduate research work on engineering projects. The objective of the course is to translate current research methods, which are mostly from a social science perspective, into something more relatable and understandable to engineers. Our hope for this course is to go beyond the concepts to understand the actual reasons for doing research in a certain way. While engineers are the main target audience, non-engineers will find this information useful as well.

The methods taught in this course will equip you with the knowledge needed to design, plan and construct your own research process.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6470/edx-elen7070x-research-methods-an-engineering-approach</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>STESx: Food Security and Sustainability: Systems thinking and environmental sustainability</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Environmental Science</subject><school>Wageningen University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6-8 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-08</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Understanding and working with the complexity of sustainable food production systems requires training in different disciplines and an approach that can address this complexity at the system level. This environmental studies course enables participants to apply the principles of a systems approach to food production systems with a focus on environmental sustainability. We will analyze production systems at both ends of the spectrum: highly productive systems with relatively high inputs and emissions to the environment, and low productive systems with low input use and depletion of soil fertility. Crop-livestock interaction is a focal point.

The course includes:

Introduction to the complexity of food production systems
Introduction to systems thinking
Analysis and comparison of the productivity of food production systems and the environmental issues
The assessment of environmental sustainability using indicators (this last topic allows students to integrate topics of previous modules)</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6457/edx-stesx-food-security-and-sustainability-systems-thinking-and-environmental-sustainability</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>UT.RTBN.12.01x: Real-Time Bluetooth Networks - Shape the World</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Electrical Engineering</subject><school>The University of Texas at Austin</school><language>English</language><course_hours>10 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-15</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>The increased demand by consumers and businesses for more utility, connectivity and smarter and more efficient electronic technology not only creates a need for more embedded systems but also for engineers in the embedded systems field.

In this lab-based computer science course, explore the complexities of embedded systems and learn how to develop your own real-time operating system (RTOS) by building a personal fitness device with Bluetooth connectivity (BLE). An operating system (OS) is a software system that computers use to manage the resources of a computer. The OS decides which tasks are performed when and decides how resources are utilized. Simple embedded systems, which are a combination of electrical, mechanical, chemical, and computer components designed to perform a dedicated function, originally did not need an OS. However, as embedded systems have evolved, so have their complexities. To manage this, an RTOS is now required.

Embedded systems are often deployed in safety-critical situations such as automotive, military, industrial, and medical applications. In applications such as communications and consumer electronics, response time and processing speed are important. A real-time system not only needs to arrive at the correct answer, but must also get the correct answer at the correct time. A RTOS manages a computer's resources so that tasks are performed in a timely mannner.

In this computer science course, students will learn the design fundamentals of an RTOS from the bottom up and use these fundamentals to build practical real-time applications. We will provide a board support package (BSP), so students will be able to focus on the RTOS and Bluetooth network without needing prior experience in circuits and I/O device driver software. This is a hands-on project-based lab course, where you will incrementally build a personal fitness device with Bluetooth connectivity.

This course is intended for students and professional engineers wishing to improve their skills in the fields of embedded systems, product development, computer architecture, operating systems, and Bluetooth networks.

To complete this course, you will need to purchase a lab kit including a microcontroller board, an I/O board, and a Bluetooth module. Instructions about purchasing the kit and installing required software are at http://edx-org-utaustinx.s3.amazonaws.com/UT601x/RTOS.html .</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6494/edx-ut-rtbn-12-01x-real-time-bluetooth-networks-shape-the-world</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Smart Choices: Broadening Your Horizons</title><provider>FutureLearn</provider><subject>Higher Education</subject><school>UCAS</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-26</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This course has been designed by UCAS to help you better understand the study and training opportunities open to you. The wide range of subjects, universities and options available can be overwhelming. Exploring your choices and making decisions can be quite daunting. So, we’ve put together a set of materials to help shape your thinking.
Choose the right subject and pathway for you
By signing up, you’ll discover more about your options and enhance your ability to make choices that are right for you. We’ll provide insight into choosing subjects and the different pathways that can be taken after school, through higher education or other training routes, to your chosen career path.
You’ll find useful tips from students and hear from admissions tutors about what skills and aptitudes they look for in applicants, and the key things you need to consider in order to make the right decisions and choices for you.
Understand study and career opportunities
The course includes short articles for you to read and videos to watch, plus activities and quizzes with tips to help you better understand the study and career opportunities. There is also the chance for you to learn from and support other learners through online discussions.
On completion, we believe you will be in a much stronger position to answer the question ‘What do I want to do next?’</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6402/futurelearn-smart-choices-broadening-your-horizons</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>6.005.1x: Software Construction in Java</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Computer Science</subject><school>Massachusetts Institute of Technology</school><language>English</language><course_hours>15 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-09-26</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This computer science course is the first of a two-course sequence about writing good software using modern software engineering techniques.

In this course, you will learn what software engineers mean by "good" code -- safe from bugs, easy to understand, and ready for change. You will also learn ways to make your code better, including testing, specifications, code review, exceptions, immutability, abstract data types, and interfaces.

This is a challenging and rigorous course that will help you take the next step on your way to becoming a skilled software engineer.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6469/edx-6-005-1x-software-construction-in-java</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>MEP101x: Project Management of Engineering Projects: Preparing for Success</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Business &amp; Management</subject><school>Delft University of Technology</school><language>English</language><course_hours>4-6 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-10-01</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Are you a (project) engineer with a technical background but lack management knowledge? Are you eager to improve project performance and want to expand your knowledge?

This business and management course will focus on the necessary project management skills to successfully manage projects, distinguishing three areas:

The project manager and the team
The project process
The project context
The course focuses on the early project phases, including examples from technical projects within various sectors and industries (amongst others, but not limited to, infrastructure projects and construction projects).

At the end of this course, you will have created your own project execution plan, either in a team effort or on individual basis. Of course the team effort allows for a special learning experience and we appraise active team participation

 

LICENSE

The course materials of this course are Copyright Delft University of Technology and are licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike (CC-BY-NC-SA) 4.0 International License.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6421/edx-mep101x-project-management-of-engineering-projects-preparing-for-success</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>nano540x: Nanophotonic Modeling</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Engineering</subject><school>Purdue University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-10-03</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This engineering course is an introduction to photonic materials and devices structured on the wavelength scale. Generally, these systems will be characterized as having critical dimensions at the nanometer scale. These can include nanophotonic, plasmonic, and metamaterial components and systems.

This course may be useful for advanced undergraduates with the prerequisites listed below; graduate students interested in incorporating these techniques into their thesis research; and practicing scientists and engineers developing new experiments or products based on these ideas.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6455/edx-nano540x-nanophotonic-modeling</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>RBME101x: Results-Based Project Management: Monitoring and Evaluation</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Business &amp; Management</subject><school>University of the Witwatersrand</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-10-05</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>In this project management course, you will learn the basics of results-based management, including the use of the results framework and its associated performance indicators. You will learn how the use of monitoring systems and evaluations provide a crucial source of evidence for management decision-making.

This project management course is designed to address the growing demand for managers in Africa and around the world, who can use results-based approaches to design, implement and manage an ever-growing range of programs and projects. Monitoring and evaluation (key results based management tools) are increasingly called upon within public service, non-governmental sectors and multi-lateral development agencies to help ensure that resources are put to optimum use and that citizens and beneficiaries are assured of receiving the benefits that are committed to them.

The course has been developed in partnership with CLEAR Anglophone Africa and draws upon the centers experience in promoting the use of evidence-based systems across Africa to enhance development practice.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6480/edx-rbme101x-results-based-project-management-monitoring-and-evaluation</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Smart Cities – Management of Smart Urban Infrastructures</title><provider>Coursera</provider><subject>Civil &amp; Environmental Engineering</subject><school>École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2017-02-01</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>Learn about the principles of management of urban infrastructures in the era of Smart Cities. The introduction of Smart urban technologies into legacy infrastructures has already resulted and will continue to result in numerous challenges and opportunities. This course will help you to make the best out of the introduction of these smart technologies in your cities’ legacy infrastructures.

Over the past few years, advancements in the Information and Communication Technologies (ICTs) have significantly challenged the traditionally stable landscape of urban infrastructure services provision. The result is an increasing interest in the transitioning of cities towards so-called “smart cities”- an interest expressed both by technology vendors and public authorities. Although such “smart technologies” can provide immense opportunities for citizens and for service providers alike, the ICTs often act as disruptive innovators of urban infrastructure service provision.

In this MOOC, you will gain a thorough understanding of the challenges and opportunities associated with “smart urban infrastructures” as well as how these infrastructures can be managed in order to deliver desirable performance in cities. More precisely, throughout this 5-week MOOC you will learn about the most important principles for the management of smart urban infrastructures as well as about the application of these principles to two specific sectors, namely urban transportation and urban energy systems.

The course does not have any pre-requisits. However, in order to make the best of this MOOC, we strongly encourage you to enroll in our previous MOOC on the Management of Urban Infrastructures which has been widely appraised by learners.

Through this course, students will:
- Gain a deep understanding of the nature of disruptive innovations (smart technologies) in urban infrastructure systems;
- Learn about state-of-the-art strategies that are and can be used for “smart infrastructure” solutions in cities, while effectively managing the transition from legacy infrastructures to smart systems;
- Learn about the management of the transition phase from legacy infrastructure systems to smart cities by supporting innovations while avoiding early lock-in; and
- Understand the potential applications of the materials learned in this course, within the context of the management of “smart urban transportation systems” as well as “smart urban energy systems”.

Class workload: 2 hours / week</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6479/coursera-smart-cities-management-of-smart-urban-infrastructures</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>6.005.2x: Advanced Software Construction in Java</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Computer Science</subject><school>Massachusetts Institute of Technology</school><language>English</language><course_hours>15 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2017-02-20</session></course_sessions><pace>Upcoming</pace><certification_available>Upcoming</certification_available><description>This computer science course is the second of a two-course sequence on how to write good software using modern software engineering techniques.

This course will dig deeper into what makes for "good" code -- safe from bugs, easy to understand, and ready for change. We will explore two paradigms for modern programming: (1) grammars, parsing, and recursive datatypes; and (2) concurrent programming with threads.

This is a challenging and rigorous course that will help you take the next step on your way to becoming a skilled software engineer.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6475/edx-6-005-2x-advanced-software-construction-in-java</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>FSSCPx: Food Security and Sustainability: Crop production</title><provider>edX</provider><subject>Environmental Science</subject><school>Wageningen University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>6-8 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-16</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>Feeding nine billion people in 2050 without exhausting the planetary reserves is perhaps the greatest challenge mankind has ever faced. This environmental studies course will examine the principles of production ecology and the ‘availability pillar’ of global food security that lie at the heart of food production, which can be applied to both crops and animal production. This course will discuss why yields in some parts of the world are lagging behind and identify the agro-ecological drivers that shape the wide diversity of production systems.

Furthermore, key issues relating to the closing of yield gaps and the difference in visions of sustainability will be explored.

This online course will be of great interest to international students and those with varied educational backgrounds, both professionally and culturally, to enrich their views and action perspectives related to global food security and food systems. Professor Ken E. Giller will introduce learners to crop production and underlying bio-physical principles in order to identify constraining factors in yield formation. He will explain how to assess yield gaps at the level of fields and production systems around the world, contributing to efficient resource management. Wageningen University and Research, through its unique systems-based approach to food systems, adds the phase of primary production to the broad context of global food security.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6456/edx-fsscpx-food-security-and-sustainability-crop-production</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Experience SAP Hybris Solutions</title><provider>openSAP</provider><subject>Marketing</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>5-7 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-20</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>Traditional CRM tools are fast becoming obsolete. They often don’t have the necessary breadth to satisfy the growing demand for omnichannel customer engagement. What businesses need is a comprehensive approach to engage with customers consistently, across all touchpoints and functional activities, not just via stovepipe solutions for e-commerce, point-of-sale, marketing, social media, sales force automation, or customer service in isolation.
This course will give you detailed insight into SAP Hybris solutions, and you’ll see how SAP Hybris is reshaping Customer Engagement &amp; Commerce (CEC) as a new software category beyond traditional CRM. In various demos and system exercises, you can experience how these solutions help to improve sales, enhance brand loyalty, optimize customer service, and increase marketing performance in the new digital age and along the customer journey. In addition, you’ll learn how SAP Hybris solutions can be adapted and integrated within the SAP Hybris front office and to back-office systems like SAP ERP or SAP S/4HANA.
The content of this course is brand new and also serves as enablement material for the SAP Hybris field organization and for our partners (as “SAP Hybris Experience Workshop”). Due to its popularity, you can now access the content via openSAP.
Please note: Weeks 2 and 3 contain additional units, and you’ll need more time to complete the content.
Syllabus
Week 1: SAP Hybris Strategy &amp; Commerce
Week 2: SAP Hybris Billing &amp; Marketing
Week 3: SAP Hybris Sales &amp; Service
Week 4: SAP Hybris Integration &amp; Technology
Week 5: Final Exam</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6414/opensap-experience-sap-hybris-solutions</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>M122: Getting Started with MongoDB Cluster Management</title><provider>MongoDB University</provider><subject>Databases</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-21</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description> In this short-course we provide an overview of MongoDB's deployment management platforms: Cloud Manager and Ops Manager. Both platforms provide deployment automation, monitoring, and backup for MongoDB. Cloud Manager is a hosted platform, while Ops Manager is designed to be installed and run on your premises. We will explore setting up automation, monitoring, backup using the Web UI these platforms support and provide a deeper dive on the architecture of Ops Manager to facilitate setup and configuration for on-premises installations. 
Syllabus
Week 1: Cloud Manager
Week 2: Ops Manager</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6463/mongodb-university-m122-getting-started-with-mongodb-cluster-management</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>The Road to the White House: The Republican and Democratic National Party Conventions Explained and Analyzed</title><provider>Open Education by Blackboard</provider><subject>Political Science</subject><school>Pace University</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-05-15</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description/><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6485/open-education-by-blackboard-the-road-to-the-white-house-the-republican-and-democratic-national-party-conventions-explained-and-analyzed</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Guerrilla Literacy Learners</title><provider>EMMA</provider><subject>Teacher Development</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>null</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-05-23</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>Guerrilla Literacy Learners creates a mistake-driven language acquisition approach. Starting from mistake approaches from structuralism, error analysis, Montessori to Freinet, we develop an approach that applauds the mistakes being made as they allow us to create this new way of learning. Mistakes are pathways to new strategies. These will be described and remediated in lay terms. Teachers and learners learn how to create knowledge clips based on digital storytelling; gather Guerrilla paths through narrative coaching, graphic facilitation, human-centred design, art of hosting and formulate and apply Guerrilla patterns in Communities of Practice.
Syllabus
Lesson 1 - Introduction: London trip as Guerrilla learning
Lesson 2 - Susan goes searching for her students
Lesson 3 - Susan takes action
Lesson 4 - Susan appreciates all her students</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6416/emma-guerrilla-literacy-learners</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Cada Dia Welsh - Welsh Language Conversation</title><provider>Canvas.net</provider><subject>Language &amp; Culture</subject><school>University of New South Wales</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-05-31</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>Designed for adults and students level 10 and above, this social language learning course provides an opportunity for participants to listen and learn the Welsh language through web meetings with native or bilingual facilitators.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6403/canvas-net-cada-dia-welsh-welsh-language-conversation</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Software Design for Non-Designers</title><provider>openSAP</provider><subject>Design &amp; Creativity</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-01</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>The Software for Non-Designers interactive course aims to explain common aspects of design as way to improve user experience in software engineering, and will provide an introduction to a few basic steps you can apply to your next project. It is taught by Scott Klemmer from UC San Diego, and a team of design-driven development experts from SAP.
  Syllabus
Week 1 - What is design and why design matters:
Design thinking, design practice, and the language of design
Week 2 - Design Process:
The software interface design process, roles and concepts
Week 3 - Needs finding:
Understanding the needs of the people you are designing for.
Week 4 - Conceptual Design:
Matching product design to the work of the user
Peer Assessment
Week 5 - High Fidelity Design:
Simple, yet impactful considerations when design software applications.
Week 6 - Design at work:
A peek behind the scenes of how software design works at SAP.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6412/opensap-software-design-for-non-designers</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Implementation of SAP BusinessObjects Cloud</title><provider>openSAP</provider><subject>Business Analytics and Intelligence</subject><school>null</school><language>English</language><course_hours>2-3 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-06</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>SAP BusinessObjects Cloud is SAP’s cloud-based application for enterprise-wide analytics. The cloud brings a whole new paradigm to an implementation: Users can perform analytics on disparate data sources on-the-fly; users can visualize data in ways one would never imagine; customers can deploy analytical and planning models to users with no footprint; users can consume data on mobile devices and can complete user training in the cloud.
Learn what it takes to implement a cloud solution like Implementation of SAP BusinessObjects Cloud. What are the questions we should ask of customers? What are the implementation steps? Where do we find help and support? What are the options to integrate data? What are the best practices?
In this free course, you’ll learn best practice approaches to implementing Implementation of SAP BusinessObjects Cloud. SAP will offer advice, illustrations, and demonstrations of how to maximize your investment in Implementation of SAP BusinessObjects Cloud.
Please note: This course is an ideal way to prepare for SAP Digital Boardroom in a Nutshell.
Syllabus
Week 1: SAP BusinessObjects Cloud
Week 2: Framework for Integration
Week 3: Implementation Essentials
Week 4: Final Exam</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6413/opensap-implementation-of-sap-businessobjects-cloud</url></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><title>Digital Construction</title><provider>Open Education by Blackboard</provider><subject>Engineering</subject><school>University of Westminster</school><language>English</language><course_hours>3-4 hours a week</course_hours><course_sessions><session>2016-06-13</session></course_sessions><pace>In progress</pace><certification_available>In progress</certification_available><description>The construction industry is the most exciting industry in the world. Our entire built environment - from world famous skyscrapers to house extensions - all rely on the expertise of the construction industry for design, procurement, production and management. Yet, despite significant technological advances, many of the practices of the construction industry remain relatively unchanged compared to other industries. Clients, architects, engineers, surveyors, project managers, contractors, subcontractors, suppliers and facilities managers can all work more effectively if they harness the potential offered by digital construction.
In simple terms, digital construction is concerned with the digital information required for designing, procuring and constructing buildings and other structures, and for operating the completed buildings or structures . We hear a great deal these days about BIM (Building Information Modelling) which can mean different things to different people. Whether it be creating 3D models or processes to manage information, BIM is challenging the way we work in the industry. This course will certainly consider BIM, but digital construction can also refer to simple ways in which we can use digital technologies to create, store, share and validate information, and to communicate and collaborate with each other.</description><url>https://www.class-central.com/mooc/6483/open-education-by-blackboard-digital-construction</url></CourseInfo></ROOT>