<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><ROOT><Course><course_id>1</course_id><title>Intro to Computer Science</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>5.0</rating><review_count>32</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Dave Evans</instructor><school>In this introduction to computer programming course, you’ll learn and practice key computer science concepts by building your own versions of popular web applications. You’ll learn Python, a powerful, easy-to-learn, and widely used programming language, and you’ll explore computer science basics, as you build your own search engine and social network.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=1</url></Course><Course><course_id>9</course_id><title>Design of Computer Programs</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>5.0</rating><review_count>19</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Peter Norvig</instructor><school>Understanding how to approach programming problems and devise a solution is an essential skill for any Python developer. In this course, you’ll learn new concepts, patterns, and methods that will expand your coding abilities from programming expert, Peter Norvig.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=9</url></Course><Course><course_id>6</course_id><title>Web Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>5.0</rating><review_count>19</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Steve Huffman</instructor><school>Try to picture yourself sitting down with your computer, ready to start developing a fully functional web application for the first time, available online for millions to use. “Where should I even begin? How long is this going to take me? Am I making any mistakes along the way?” The questions may leave you with an uneasy feeling that you will learn many lessons the hard way. In this intermediate course, Steve Huffman will teach you everything he wished he knew when he started building Reddit and, more recently, Hipmunk, as a lead engineer. Starting from the basics of how the web works, this course will walk you through core web development concepts such as how internet and browsers fit together, form validations, databases, APIs, integrating with other websites, scaling issues, and more; all of which form part of the knowledge it takes to build a web application of your own.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=6</url></Course><Course><course_id>143</course_id><title>How to Build a Startup</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>12</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Steve Blank</instructor><school>In an introduction to the basics of the famous Customer Development Process, Steve Blank provides insight into the key steps needed to build a successful startup. The main idea in this course is learning how to rapidly develop and test ideas by gathering massive amounts of customer and marketplace feedback. Many startups fail by not validating their ideas early on with real-life customers. In order to mitigate that, students will learn how to get out of the building and search for the real pain points and unmet needs of customers. Only with these can the entrepreneur find a proper solution and establish a suitable business model. Building a startup is not simply building an execution plan for a business model that the entrepreneur thinks will work, but rather, a search for the actual business model itself.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=143</url></Course><Course><course_id>461</course_id><title>Intro to Psychology</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>4</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Susan Snycerski, Greg Feist</instructor><school>Introduction to Psychology is a journey through all of the major psychological concepts and principles. The knowledge gained from this course will allow students to critically evaluate psychological research and have a more in-depth understanding of human thought and behavior.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=461</url></Course><Course><course_id>249</course_id><title>Intro to Artificial Intelligence</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>6</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Peter Norvig, Sebastian Thrun</instructor><school>Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a field that has a long history but is still constantly and actively growing and changing. In this course, you’ll learn the basics of modern AI as well as some of the representative applications of AI. Along the way, we also hope to excite you about the numerous applications and huge possibilities in the field of AI, which continues to expand human capability beyond our imagination. ***Note: Parts of this course are featured in the Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree and the Data Analyst Nanodegree programs. If you are interested in AI, be sure to check out those programs as well!***</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=249</url></Course><Course><course_id>12748</course_id><title>Data Analysis with R</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Chris Saden, Dean Eckles, Moira Burke, Solomon Messing</instructor><school>Exploratory data analysis is an approach for summarizing and visualizing the important characteristics of a data set. Promoted by [John Tukey](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Tukey), exploratory data analysis focuses on exploring data to understand the data’s underlying structure and variables, to develop intuition about the data set, to consider how that data set came into existence, and to decide how it can be investigated with more formal statistical methods. If you're interested in supplemental reading material for the course check out the Exploratory Data Analysis book. (Not Required) This course is also a part of our Data Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=12748</url></Course><Course><course_id>10</course_id><title>Artificial Intelligence for Robotics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>5</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sebastian Thrun</instructor><school>Learn how to program all the major systems of a robotic car from the leader of Google and Stanford's autonomous driving teams. This class will teach you basic methods in Artificial Intelligence, including: probabilistic inference, planning and search, localization, tracking and control, all with a focus on robotics. Extensive programming examples and assignments will apply these methods in the context of building self-driving cars. This course is offered as part of the Georgia Tech Masters in Computer Science. The updated course includes a final project, where you must chase a runaway robot that is trying to escape!</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=10</url></Course><Course><course_id>142</course_id><title>Intro to Theoretical Computer Science</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>5.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sebastian Wernicke</instructor><school>This class teaches you about basic concepts in theoretical computer science -- such as NP-completeness -- and what they imply for solving tough algorithmic problems.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=142</url></Course><Course><course_id>27542</course_id><title>How to Use Git and GitHub</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>5.0</rating><review_count>4</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sarah Spikes, Caroline Buckey</instructor><school>Effective use of version control is an important and useful skill for any developer working on long-lived (or even medium-lived) projects, especially if more than one developer is involved. This course, *built with input from GitHub*, will introduce the basics of using version control by focusing on a particular version control system called Git and a collaboration platform called GitHub. This course is part of the Front End and Full Stack Nanodegrees..</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=27542</url></Course><Course><course_id>12745</course_id><title>Intro to Point &amp; Click App Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Andy Brown, Samantha Ready, Mario Korf</instructor><school>This class teaches you how to build powerful web and mobile apps and host them in the cloud, without writing a line of code. By the end of this short course, you'll use the skills you've developed to conceptualize and create your own app. To get you there, your instructors Samantha and Andy will first help you build an app that could be used to manage logistics at a music festival. Though this is a very specific app use case, the skills you learn will be applicable to just about any business app you’d want to develop.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=12745</url></Course><Course><course_id>11</course_id><title>Applied Cryptography</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Dave Evans</instructor><school>Cryptography is present in everyday life, from paying with a credit card to using the telephone. Learn all about making and breaking puzzles in computing.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=11</url></Course><Course><course_id>514</course_id><title>Intro Algebra Review</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>5.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Kelly Vetter, Sue Ann Austin</instructor><school>This course provides a brief review of introductory algebra topics. Topics to be covered include integer operations, order of operations, perimeter and area, fractions and decimals, scientific notation, ratios and rates, conversions, percents, algebraic expressions, linear equations, the Pythagorean theorem, and graphing.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=514</url></Course><Course><course_id>236</course_id><title>Intro to Parallel Programming</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  David Luebke, John Owens</instructor><school>Learn the fundamentals of parallel computing with the GPU and the CUDA programming environment! In this class, you'll learn about parallel programming by coding a series of image processing algorithms, such as you might find in Photoshop or Instagram. You'll be able to program and run your assignments on high-end GPUs, even if you don't own one yourself. **Why It’s Important to Think Parallel** [Third Pillar of Science][1] Learn how scientific discovery can be accelerated by combining theory and experimentation with computing to fight cancer, prevent heart attacks, and spur new advances in robotic surgery. [1]: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3DbAB2ChDBw</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=236</url></Course><Course><course_id>3373</course_id><title>Intro to the Design of Everyday Things</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Don Norman, Kristian Simsarian</instructor><school>Everyone designs. Design occurs anytime you deliberately change an environment to make things better. When you decide what seat to take in an auditorium you’re designing your experience. When you rearrange the furniture in a room or draft an email, you’re designing. This course provides a summary of key concepts from the first two chapters of The Design of Everyday Things (Revised and Expanded Edition, November 2013) by Don Norman. It’s intended to be enjoyable and informative for anyone curious about design: everyday people, technical people, designers, and non-designers alike.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=3373</url></Course><Course><course_id>27543</course_id><title>JavaScript Basics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  James Williams, Cameron Pittman</instructor><school>We're here to help you get you started with JavaScript! In the twenty plus years since its inception, JavaScript has become the _lingua franca_ of the web, that's to say, it's become the main tool to create interactive content on the Internet. In this course, you'll explore the JavaScript programming language by creating an interactive version of your résumé. You’ll learn the JavaScript programming fundamentals you need while building new elements and sections to enhance your résumé. This course is also a part of our Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=27543</url></Course><Course><course_id>48845</course_id><title>Introduction to Computer Vision</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Irfan Essa, Aaron Bobick</instructor><school>This course provides an introduction to computer vision including fundamentals of image formation, camera imaging geometry, feature detection and matching, multiview geometry including stereo, motion estimation and tracking, and classification. We’ll develop basic methods for applications that include finding known models in images, depth recovery from stereo, camera calibration, image stabilization, automated alignment (e.g. panoramas), tracking, and action recognition. We focus less on the machine learning aspect of CV as that is really classification theory best learned in an ML course. The focus of the course is to develop the intuitions and mathematics of the methods in lecture, and then to learn about the difference between theory and practice in the problem sets. All algorithms work perfectly in the slides. But remember what [Yogi Berra](http://yogiberramuseum.org/just-for-fun/yogisms/) said: In theory there is no difference between theory and practice. In practice there is. (Einstein said something similar but who knows more about real life?) In this course you do not, for the most part, apply high-level library functions but use low to mid level algorithms to analyze images and extract structural information.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=48845</url></Course><Course><course_id>29261</course_id><title>Intro to AJAX</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman</instructor><school>In this course you will learn how to make asynchronous requests with JavaScript (using jQuery’s AJAX functionality), and gain a better understanding of what’s actually happening when you do so. You will also learn how to use data APIs so you can take advantage of freely accessible data in your applications, including photo results, news articles and up-to-date data about the world around us. As part of the course, you’ll be building a web app that will help people learn about a place where they want to move! Your app will query the Google Streetview, Wikipedia and New York Times APIs! This course is also a part of our Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=29261</url></Course><Course><course_id>29843</course_id><title>Intro to jQuery</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman</instructor><school>jQuery is the most popular JavaScript library today, in use by over 60% of the top 100,000 most visited websites. This course will teach you how to use jQuery’s core features - DOM element selections, traversal and manipulation. You'll also learn how to read and make sense of jQuery's documentation, making it easy for you to go beyond the methods taught in this class and take advantage of jQuery's full array of features! This course is also a part of our Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=29843</url></Course><Course><course_id>48844</course_id><title>Software Architecture &amp; Design</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Spencer Rugaber, Eric Feron</instructor><school>Software Architecture and Design teaches the principles and concepts involved in the analysis and design of large software systems. This course is split into four sections: (1) Introduction, (2) UML and Analysis, (3) Software Architecture, and (4) Software Design.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=48844</url></Course><Course><course_id>35398</course_id><title>Real-Time Analytics with Apache Storm</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Karthik Ramasamy</instructor><school>The world is trending in real time! Learn from Twitter to scalably process tweets, or any big data stream, in real-time to drive d3 visualizations using Apache Storm, the “Hadoop of Real Time.” Storm is free, open source, and fun to use! Learn from Karthik Ramasamy, Technical Lead of Storm@Twitter, about the distributed, fault-tolerant, and flexible technology used to power Twitter’s real-time data flow pipeline. Twitter open sourced Storm in 2011, and it graduated to a top-level Apache project in September, 2014. Starting from basic distributed concepts presented during our first Udacity-Twitter Storm Hackathon, link Storm concepts to Storm syntax to scalably drive Word Cloud visualizations with Vagrant, Ubuntu, Maven, Flask, Redis, and d3. Link to the public Twitter gardenhose stream to process live tweets, parse embedded URLs, and calculate Top worldwide hashtags. Extend beyond Storm basics by exploring multi-language capabilities in Python, integrate open source components, and implement real-time streaming joins. In your final project, follow real-time trending topics by implementing the data pipeline to visualize only tweets that contain Top worldwide hashtags. Extend your project by exploring the Twitter API, or any data source, alongside Hackathon participants as they design their own ideas, receive feedback from Karthik, and open source a final project calculating real-time tweet sentiment and geolocation to drive a U.S. Map.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=35398</url></Course><Course><course_id>20575</course_id><title>Developing Android Apps</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>2.0</rating><review_count>8</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Reto Meier, Katherine Kuan, Dan Galpin, Alexander Lucas</instructor><school>As the first course in the Android Developer Nanodegree, Developing Android Apps is the foundation of our advanced Android curriculum. This course blends theory and practice to help you build great apps the right way. In this course, you'll work with instructors step-by-step to build a cloud-connected Android app, and learn best practices of mobile development, and Android development in particular. ####[Download Udacity's Android app](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.udacity.android) to keep learning wherever you go!</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=20575</url></Course><Course><course_id>29882</course_id><title>Data Visualization and D3.js</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jonathan Dinu, Ryan Orban</instructor><school>Learn the fundamentals of data visualization and practice communicating with data. This course covers how to apply design principles, human perception, color theory, and effective storytelling to data visualization. If you present data to others, aspire to be an analyst or data scientist, or if you’d like to become more technical with visualization tools, then you can grow your skills with this course. The course does not cover exploratory approaches to discover insights about data. Instead, the course focuses on how to visually encode and present data to an audience once an insight has been found. This course is part of the Data Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=29882</url></Course><Course><course_id>51907</course_id><title>Deep Learning</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>2.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Vincent Vanhoucke</instructor><school>**Machine learning** is one of the fastest-growing and most exciting fields out there, and **deep learning** represents its true bleeding edge. In this course, you’ll develop a clear understanding of the motivation for deep learning, and design intelligent systems that learn from complex and/or large-scale datasets. We’ll show you how to train and optimize basic neural networks, convolutional neural networks, and long short term memory networks. Complete learning systems in TensorFlow will be introduced via projects and assignments. You will learn to solve new classes of problems that were once thought prohibitively challenging, and come to better appreciate the complex nature of human intelligence as you solve these same problems effortlessly using deep learning methods. We have developed this course with Vincent Vanhoucke, Principal Scientist at Google, and technical lead in the Google Brain team. ***Note**: This is an intermediate to advanced level course offered as part of the [Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree](https://www.udacity.com/course/machine-learning-engineer-nanodegree--nd009) program. It assumes you have taken a first course in machine learning, and that you are at least familiar with supervised learning methods.*</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51907</url></Course><Course><course_id>3374</course_id><title>Mobile Web Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>2.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Peter Lubbers, Chris Wilson</instructor><school>So you’ve heard mobile is kind of a big deal, and you’re not sure how to transform your traditional desktop-focused web apps into fast, effective mobile experiences. This course is designed to teach web developers what they need to know to create great cross-device mobile web experiences. This course will focus on building mobile web apps, which will work across multiple platforms including Android, iOS, and others.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=3374</url></Course><Course><course_id>43362</course_id><title>Full Stack Foundations</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Lorenzo Brown</instructor><school>In this course you will learn the fundamentals of back-end web development! You will create your own web application that queries a database for items on restaurant menus and then dynamically generates complete menus in the form of web pages and API endpoints. You’ll start by learning how to interact with a database from a web application using an Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) layer. From there, you’ll learn how GET and POST requests translate to CRUD operations. You’ll then explore the Flask framework and the various ways in which it can speed up the development of your applications. Finally, you’ll develop your very own web application from the ground up using the iterative development process.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=43362</url></Course><Course><course_id>45538</course_id><title>Responsive Images</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman, Sam Dutton</instructor><school>Did you know that images account for more than **60%** of the bytes on average needed to load a web page? In this course you will learn how to work with images on the modern web, so that your images look great and load quickly on any device. Along the way, you will pick up a range of skills and techniques to smoothly integrate responsive images into your development workflow. By the end of the course, you will be developing with images that adapt and respond to different viewport sizes and usage scenarios.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45538</url></Course><Course><course_id>235</course_id><title>HTML5 Game Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>1.0</rating><review_count>11</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Colt McAnlis, Peter Lubbers</instructor><school>This course will walk you through the major components of building GRITS, an HTML5 game. We'll talk about how to take standard game development techniques, and use them to create high performance HTML5 applications.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=235</url></Course><Course><course_id>45539</course_id><title>Browser Rendering Optimization</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman, Paul Lewis</instructor><school>Performance matters to users. Web developers need to build apps that react quickly and render smoothly. Google performance guru Paul Lewis is here to help you destroy jank and create web apps that maintain 60 frames per second performance. You'll leave this course with the tools you need to profile apps and identify the causes of jank. You'll explore the browser's rendering pipeline and uncover patterns that make it easy to build performant apps.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45539</url></Course><Course><course_id>36563</course_id><title>JavaScript Design Patterns</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ben Jaffe</instructor><school>This course covers methods for organizing your code, both conceptually and literally. You’ll learn the importance of separating concerns when writing JavaScript, gaining hands-on experience along the way. Separating concerns can be done with or without an organizational library or framework. We’ll learn how to separate concerns without one, and then we’ll explore an organizational library together. You’ll also learn strategies for exploring other libraries and frameworks on your own. By the end of this course, you’ll understand (from experience) the importance of code organization, and how to implement it with either vanilla JavaScript or an organizational library or framework. Your applications will start looking clean and professional—not just to your users, but also to anyone who looks at the code driving your applications.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=36563</url></Course><Course><course_id>45546</course_id><title>A/B Testing</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Caroline Buckey, Diane Tang, Carrie Grimes</instructor><school>This course will cover the design and analysis of A/B tests, also known as split tests, which are online experiments used to test potential improvements to a website or mobile application. Two versions of the website are shown to different users - usually the existing website and a potential change. Then, the results are analyzed to determine whether the change is an improvement worth launching. This course will cover how to choose and characterize metrics to evaluate your experiments, how to design an experiment with enough statistical power, how to analyze the results and draw valid conclusions, and how to ensure that the the participants of your experiments are adequately protected.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45546</url></Course><Course><course_id>45537</course_id><title>Authentication &amp; Authorization: OAuth</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Lorenzo Brown</instructor><school>As a Python programmer, leveraging Flask allows you to quickly and easily build your own web applications. But before you share your apps on the Internet you should protect your users' data, ensuring information stored on your site is safe from unwanted manipulation. You could implement web security and permissions on your own, but relying on trusted providers is a faster, safer, and easier way to allow users to login to your application - without having to create and maintain another account, profile, and password. In this course, you will learn to implement the OAuth 2.0 framework to allow users to securely login to your web applications. You'll be provided a restaurant menu application created in Flask. By the end of this course, you will write the necessary code to implement Google+ Sign-In and Facebook Login in options so users can create restaurant menus that are viewable by everyone but only modifiable by the original creator.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45537</url></Course><Course><course_id>49437</course_id><title>Rapid Prototyping</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Carl Sziebert</instructor><school>Prototyping allows you to spend ten minutes -- instead of ten hours -- finding an amazing design for your product. This course will guide you through the iterative process of prototyping an app and conducting user research. You will start by making a low fidelity paper prototype, conducting research with users, and using that research to inform your next iteration. Together with InVision we’ll guide you through creating interactive prototypes. This means you don’t have to code an app before putting it in front of users! Along the way, you’ll learn how and where prototyping fits into your app design process and how you can use prototyping to become a better entrepreneur. This course is part of our Tech Entrepreneur Nanodegree Program, click [here to learn more](https://www.udacity.com/course/tech-entrepreneur-nanodegree--nd007).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49437</url></Course><Course><course_id>69951</course_id><title>Client-Server Communication</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Surma</instructor><school>We use websites all the time, but how does clicking a link in your browser or typing in a URL in the address bar get you to a website? How does the server know what information you're looking for or how to send you that information once it's figured that out? How can you protect your users from attackers? Dig into this course and you'll be able to answer these questions! This course will guide you through how a client communicates with a server. You'll learn about HTTP's request and response cycle, dig into HTTP headers and verbs, distinguish HTTP/1 from HTTP/2 capabilities, all while experiencing the importance of security by digging into the details of HTTPS. Throughout the course, you'll learn both security best practices, as well as ways to improve the performance of your web apps. We'll provide you with handcrafted servers where you'll diagnose problematic server setups, issues with SSL certificates, and even have a chance to hack an example bank website to transfer funds.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69951</url></Course><Course><course_id>69961</course_id><title>Android Basics: Multi-screen Apps</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Katherine Kuan</instructor><school>This course is a part of the Android Basics Nanodegree by Google. Android apps are everywhere and learning to build them can be a fantastic career move. Continue on your Android app development education and learn to build multi-screen apps! This course is designed for students who have completed the Android for Beginners course. You don’t need any programming experience besides that course! Learning anything new can be tough. We will walk you through the process of making Android apps, but to get the most out of this course, bring your enthusiasm for learning, and budget time on your calendar to learn with us. It will be an adventure! By the end of the course, you’ll build a language-learning app that you can share with your friends. You'll also be continuing your growth as an Android developer by taking the next step towards the Android Developer Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69961</url></Course><Course><course_id>45534</course_id><title>Material Design for Android Developers</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Nick Butcher, Roman Nurik</instructor><school>In this course, you'll learn how to apply the material design principles that define Android's visual language to your apps. We'll start by walking you through Android design fundamentals, then we'll show you how to apply this knowledge to transform design elements of sample apps. By the end of the course, you'll understand how to create and use material design elements, surfaces, transitions and graphics in your app, across multiple form factors.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45534</url></Course><Course><course_id>51212</course_id><title>Intro to Data Analysis</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Caroline Buckey</instructor><school>This course will introduce you to the world of data analysis. You'll learn how to go through the entire data analysis process, which includes: * Posing a question * Wrangling your data into a format you can use and fixing any problems with it * Exploring the data, finding patterns in it, and building your intuition about it * Drawing conclusions and/or making predictions * Communicating your findings You'll also learn how to use the Python libraries NumPy, Pandas, and Matplotlib to write code that's cleaner, more concise, and runs faster. This course is part of the [Data Analyst Nanodegree](https://www.udacity.com/course/data-analyst-nanodegree--nd002).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51212</url></Course><Course><course_id>27540</course_id><title>Object-Oriented JavaScript</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Marcus Phillips</instructor><school>Have you been dabbling with JavaScript but find your files keep turning into a mess of spaghetti code? Do you find yourself copying and pasting lines of code over and over throughout your application? Surely there’s a better way, right? Yes, there is a better way -- object-oriented programming will allow you to build websites using reusable blocks of code known as libraries, similar to using bricks to build a house. This course is designed to teach web developers how to utilize the various object-oriented programming features within JavaScript, and more importantly, how to write reusable and maintainable libraries that will make your life easier.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=27540</url></Course><Course><course_id>20438</course_id><title>Website Performance Optimization</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ilya Grigorik, Cameron Pittman</instructor><school>You will learn how to optimize any website for speed by diving into the details of how mobile and desktop browsers render pages. In this short course, you’ll learn about the Critical Rendering Path, or the set of steps browsers must take to convert HTML, CSS and JavaScript into living, breathing websites. From there, you’ll start exploring and experimenting with tools to measure performance and simple strategies to deliver the first pixels to the screen as early as possible. You’ll learn how to dive into recommendations from [PageSpeed Insights](https://developers.google.com/speed/pagespeed/insights/ "PageSpeed Insights") and the Timeline view of Google Chrome’s Developer Tools to find the data you need to achieve immediate performance boosts! This course is also a part of our Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=20438</url></Course><Course><course_id>51213</course_id><title>Machine Learning for Trading</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Tucker Balch</instructor><school>This course introduces students to the real world challenges of implementing machine learning based trading strategies including the algorithmic steps from information gathering to market orders. The focus is on how to apply probabilistic machine learning approaches to trading decisions. We consider statistical approaches like linear regression, KNN and regression trees and how to apply them to actual stock trading situations.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51213</url></Course><Course><course_id>3372</course_id><title>Tales from the Genome</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Matthew Cook, Lauren Castellano, Joanna Mountain, Uta Francke, 23andMe Team</instructor><school>This course is a journey into the biology of the human genome and will highlight the scientific, social, and personal perspectives of people living with a variety of traits.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=3372</url></Course><Course><course_id>45532</course_id><title>Add Google Sign-In to your Android Apps</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Jocelyn Becker, Laurence Moroney</instructor><school>In this course, you'll learn how to use Google’s Identity Platform to allow users to sign-in using their Google credentials, and how to access data that they grant you permission to access. **This course is part of the Google Play Services series, which features a variety of different Google APIs. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all!** * Google Location Services on Android * Google Analytics for Android * App Monetization with Display Advertising * Add Google Maps to your Android App * **Add Google Sign-In to your Android Apps** [this course]</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45532</url></Course><Course><course_id>45526</course_id><title>Advanced Android App Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Dan Galpin, Ian Lake, Joanna Smith</instructor><school>This course will guide you through the process of productionizing an app, using Sunshine, the weather app we built in Developing Android Apps. Following Android's Core App Quality Guidelines, we'll identify the production criteria that still needs to be implemented, then tackle each problem until Sunshine is ready to publish on the Google Play Store. In the process, we'll introduce you to a host of tools and concepts, including: material design approaches, image-handling, performance profiling, and more!</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45526</url></Course><Course><course_id>45527</course_id><title>Gradle for Android and Java</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Mark Vieira, Jeremy Silver</instructor><school>This course explores how the Gradle build tool compiles and packages apps, and you'll learn to customize the build process. The first half of this course is for anyone interested in Gradle, build automation, and continuous delivery of software. The latter half of the course reveals the magic that happens after you hit the "Run" button in Android Studio. You'll also explore advanced Android topics, learning to configure free vs paid app flavors, create and integrate Android libraries, test your app, and prepare your app for the Play Store.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45527</url></Course><Course><course_id>45528</course_id><title>Google Location Services on Android</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Jocelyn Becker, Laurence Moroney</instructor><school>Vitally important for building the best possible mobile app, the Location and Context API allows your Android app behavior to change based on location. In this course, you’ll learn how to implement this with the Fused Location Provider, which gives you much more than simple GPS. You’ll also learn about Activity recognition, which allows you to tailor your app to what the user is doing. Finally, you’ll learn about Geofencing, and how location services work alongside geofences to allow you to build apps that could be used for augmented reality! **This course is part of the Google Play Services series, which features a variety of different Google APIs. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all!** * **Google Location Services on Android** [this course] * Google Analytics for Android * App Monetization with Display Advertising * Add Google Maps to your Android App</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45528</url></Course><Course><course_id>45531</course_id><title>Add Google Maps to your Android App</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Jocelyn Becker, Laurence Moroney</instructor><school>In this course, you’ll learn everything from how to add maps to your Android app, to how to build a virtual hike down the Grand Canyon! **This course is part of the Google Play Services series, which features a variety of different Google APIs. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all!** * Google Location Services on Android * Google Analytics for Android * App Monetization with Display Advertising * **Add Google Maps to your Android App** [this course]</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45531</url></Course><Course><course_id>47723</course_id><title>Android Auto Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Timothy Jordan, Wayne Piekarski, Joshua Gordon</instructor><school>Reach your users while they're out and about by extending your Media or Messaging app to Android Auto! As you'll learn in this course, making your app available in the car is as easy as extending your existing code. This course explains how to get started and then covers Media and Messaging apps in detail. This course is part of the Ubiquitous Computing series. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all! * Android Wear Development * Android TV and Google Cast Development * **Android Auto Development** [this course]</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47723</url></Course><Course><course_id>51208</course_id><title>Firebase Essentials For Android</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  JP Souchak, Lyla Fujiwara</instructor><school>In this course, you’ll learn how to use Firebase. Firebase is a cloud backend, and one of the leading choices for Backend as a Service. It enables you to quickly get synchronized data up and running for multi-user apps. This is important because nearly every mobile app these days requires authentication and real-time data updates. We’ll begin by showing you how easy it is to read and write almost any data to Firebase. After that, we’ll teach you how to allow users to login and have data associated with them. We’ll then cover how to write queries and filters for your data. You’ll discover how to take advantage of Firebase's offline capabilities, and master efficient database design for lightning-fast data retrieval. Lastly, you’ll learn how to use Firebase’s Security and Rules language to secure and add permissions to your data. By the end of this course you will have an Android application that can store and share data between different users in real time as well as authenticate and authorize those users.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51208</url></Course><Course><course_id>438</course_id><title>Visualizing Algebra</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sandra DeSousa</instructor><school>Throughout this course, we will use algebra to quantify and describe the world around us. Have you ever wondered how many songs can fit onto your flash drive? By the end of the course, you’ll have stronger skills for modeling problems, analyzing patterns, and using algebra to arrive at conclusions.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=438</url></Course><Course><course_id>20592</course_id><title>Developing Scalable Apps in Java</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Jocelyn Becker</instructor><school>You will learn about challenges of building applications that can serve hundreds of thousands of users, and how you can prepare for them as a developer. And more importantly - you will learn how to harness the power of **App Engine** - Platform as a Service, run by Google, so you can focus on your application's features, not on managing infrastructure that runs your app. Let Google run and scale the infrastructure and do what you do best - write code! However, to use App Engine effectively, you have to learn how it works, and this is exactly what this course will teach! You will also learn the best practices of using Cloud Endpoints that allow you to easily create RESTful services and make them accessible to iOS, Android and Javascript clients. They allow you to automatically generate client libraries to make wiring up the frontend easy. And there are some nifty built-in features, like denial-of-service protection and OAuth 2.0 support.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=20592</url></Course><Course><course_id>51219</course_id><title>Intro to Information Security</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Wenke Lee, Mustaque Ahamad</instructor><school>This course provides a one-semester overview of information security. It is designed to help students with prior computer and programming knowledge — both undergraduate and graduate — understand this important priority in society today. The technical content of the course gives a broad overview of essential concepts and methods for providing and evaluating security in information processing systems (operating systems and applications, networks, protocols, and so on). In addition to its technical content, the course touches on the importance of management and administration, the place information security holds in overall business risk, social issues such as individual privacy, and the role of public policy.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51219</url></Course><Course><course_id>24087</course_id><title>Software Development Process</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Alex Orso</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS6300 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. In SDP, you will learn how to select and implement the ideal software process for your development project. Through Professor Orso's engaging examples and interviews with industry insiders, you will learn both conceptual and practical aspects of software engineering. The course covers requirements engineering, architecture and design, testing and maintenance, and software quality in general. The goal of this class is to equip you with the skills necessary to define requirements, set up an integrated development environment (IDE), learn Git (and Github!) and use Unified Modeling Language (UML) to design and build an Android application. We will also examine several testing practices and refactoring techniques that are helpful before the launch of your software project. While everyone working with software should have these skills, they are particularly important for Software Engineers and Engineering Managers.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=24087</url></Course><Course><course_id>49441</course_id><title>Reinforcement Learning</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Michael Littman, Charles Isbell</instructor><school>You should take this course if you have an interest in machine learning and the desire to engage with it from a theoretical perspective. Through a combination of classic papers and more recent work, you will explore automated decision-making from a computer-science perspective. You will examine efficient algorithms, where they exist, for single-agent and multi-agent planning as well as approaches to learning near-optimal decisions from experience. At the end of the course, you will replicate a result from a published paper in reinforcement learning.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49441</url></Course><Course><course_id>69326</course_id><title>Deploying a Hadoop Cluster</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Mat Leonard</instructor><school>Learn how to tackle big data problems with your own Hadoop clusters! In this course, you’ll deploy Hadoop clusters in the cloud and use them to gain insights from large datasets.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69326</url></Course><Course><course_id>47967</course_id><title>How to create  in Android</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Kunal Chawla</instructor><school>Here is one important question Android developers ask while making apps: "How can I do ________ in Android?" The following are versions of this question that we came across recently: - How can I add radio buttons to my app? - How can I play a sound? - How can I navigate between multiple screens? This course is a collection of such questions and their answers. By the end of this course you will have mastered the ability to implement new Android features by reading a blog or article — this is a critical skill possessed by professional Android developers. As a result, you will also be able to use several User Interface components — like Toggle Buttons, Menus, Grid View and many more — that are central to making functional and delightful Android apps.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47967</url></Course><Course><course_id>3</course_id><title>Intro to Statistics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>13</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sebastian Thrun</instructor><school>Statistics is about extracting meaning from data. In this class, we will introduce techniques for visualizing relationships in data and systematic techniques for understanding the relationships using mathematics.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=3</url></Course><Course><course_id>462</course_id><title>Intro to Java Programming</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>7</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cay Horstmann</instructor><school>In this introductory course, you'll learn and practice essential computer science concepts using the Java programming language. You'll learn about Object Oriented Programming, a technique that allows you to use code written by other programmers in your own programs. You'll put your new Java programming skills to the test by solving real-world problems faced by software engineers.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=462</url></Course><Course><course_id>8</course_id><title>Programming Languages</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>6</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Westley Weimer</instructor><school>This class will give you an introduction to the fundamentals of programming languages. Key concepts include how to specify and process valid strings, sentences and program structures.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=8</url></Course><Course><course_id>4</course_id><title>Intro to Algorithms</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>4</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Michael Littman</instructor><school>Ever played the Kevin Bacon game? This class will show you how it works by giving you an introduction to the design and analysis of algorithms, enabling you to discover how individuals are connected.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=4</url></Course><Course><course_id>141</course_id><title>Software Debugging</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>4</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Andreas Zeller</instructor><school>In this class you will learn how to debug programs systematically, how to automate the debugging process and build several automated debugging tools in Python.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=141</url></Course><Course><course_id>140</course_id><title>Differential Equations in Action</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jörn Loviscach</instructor><school>In this course, you'll hone your problem-solving skills through learning to find numerical solutions to systems of differential equations. You'll write code in Python to fight forest fires, rescue the Apollo 13 astronauts, stop the spread of epidemics, and resolve other real-world dilemmas.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=140</url></Course><Course><course_id>439</course_id><title>College Algebra</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>5</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Julie Sliva Spitzer</instructor><school>Math is everywhere. In this class, you’ll gain an in-depth understanding of algebraic principles, many of which you may have seen before, and learn how to use them to solve problems that we encounter in everyday life. The online version of College Algebra will cover all of the topics that you would see in more traditional class formats, but it will present the material in a way that we hope you’ll find fresh and interesting. You will learn about functions, polynomials, graphing, complex numbers, exponential and logarithmic equations, and much more, all through exploring real-world scenarios.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=439</url></Course><Course><course_id>237</course_id><title>Interactive 3D Graphics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Eric Haines</instructor><school>This class will teach you about the basic principles of 3D computer graphics: meshes, transforms, cameras, materials, lighting, and animation.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=237</url></Course><Course><course_id>12747</course_id><title>Intro to Hadoop and MapReduce</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>8</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sarah Sproehnle, Ian Wrigley</instructor><school>The Apache™ Hadoop® project develops open-source software for reliable, scalable, distributed computing. Learn the fundamental principles behind it, and how you can use its power to make sense of your Big Data.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=12747</url></Course><Course><course_id>19815</course_id><title>Programming Foundations with Python</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>6</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Kunal Chawla</instructor><school>In this introductory programming class, you’ll learn Object-Oriented Programming, a must-have technique for software engineers that will allow you to reuse and share code easily. You’ll learn by doing, and will build byte-sized (ha!) mini projects in each lesson to learn and practice programming concepts. We’ve heard that programming can be intimidating for newcomers, and we’ve created this course to make sure that you have a great learning experience! You’ll learn ***actively*** with our mini projects (see the awesome list below), which you’ll be able to share proudly with your friends. You’ll also learn important programming concepts one by one, with no surprises or leaps of logic along the way. You’ll pick up some great tools for your programming toolkit in this course! You will: - Start coding in the programming language Python; - Reuse and share code with Object-Oriented Programming; - Create and share amazing, life-hacking projects! This introductory course is for you if you want to be a software engineer, or if you want to collaborate with programmers. Mastering Object-Oriented Programming will propel your career in tech forward, and it’s also a great way to learn how software engineers think about solving problems. This course is also a part of our Full Stack Web Developer Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=19815</url></Course><Course><course_id>2</course_id><title>Intro to Physics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>4</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Andy Brown</instructor><school>Study physics abroad in Europe -- virtually! Learn the basics of physics on location in Italy, the Netherlands and the UK, by answering some of the discipline's major questions from over the last 2000 years.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=2</url></Course><Course><course_id>12744</course_id><title>Data Wrangling with MongoDB</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>4.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Shannon Bradshaw</instructor><school>In this course, we will explore how to wrangle data from diverse sources and shape it to enable data-driven applications. Some data scientists spend the bulk of their time doing this! Students will learn how to gather and extract data from widely used data formats. They will learn how to assess the quality of data and explore best practices for data cleaning. We will also introduce students to MongoDB, covering the essentials of storing data and the MongoDB query language together with exploratory analysis using the MongoDB aggregation framework. This is a great course for those interested in entry-level data science positions as well as current business/data analysts looking to add big data to their repertoire, and managers working with data professionals or looking to leverage big data. This course is also a part of our Data Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=12744</url></Course><Course><course_id>19126</course_id><title>Make Your Own 2048</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Andy Brown, Sarah Spikes</instructor><school>Ten minutes into this class you will make your own completely personalized version of the insanely addictive game 2048. Even if you've never coded before. Pretty cool, no? You'll do this by making small (but important) modifications to the source code for the original 2048 game. If this sounds intimidating, don't worry. We'll teach you the basics of HTML and CSS and how they interact with Javascript (don't worry if that sentence doesn't mean anything to you yet. It will soon). The purpose of this class is to have fun learning how to quickly and easily take an existing open source program, make some changes, and create something that looks and feels completely new. The game you create will be mobile friendly (you can play it on your phone!) and totally shareable.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=19126</url></Course><Course><course_id>29881</course_id><title>Intro to Machine Learning</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sebastian Thrun</instructor><school>Machine Learning is a first-class ticket to the most exciting careers in data analysis today. As data sources proliferate along with the computing power to process them, going straight to the data is one of the most straightforward ways to quickly gain insights and make predictions. Machine learning brings together computer science and statistics to harness that predictive power. It’s a must-have skill for all aspiring data analysts and data scientists, or anyone else who wants to wrestle all that raw data into refined trends and predictions. This is a class that will teach you the end-to-end process of investigating data through a machine learning lens. It will teach you how to extract and identify useful features that best represent your data, a few of the most important machine learning algorithms, and how to evaluate the performance of your machine learning algorithms. This course is also a part of our Data Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=29881</url></Course><Course><course_id>42731</course_id><title>Model Building and Validation</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>1</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Don Dini, Rishi Pravahan</instructor><school>This course will teach you how to start from scratch in answering questions about the real world using data. Machine learning happens to be a small part of this process. The model building process involves setting up ways of collecting data, understanding and paying attention to what is important in the data to answer the questions you are asking, finding a statistical, mathematical or a simulation model to gain understanding and make predictions. All of these things are equally important and model building is a crucial skill to acquire in every field of science. The process stays true to the scientific method, making what you learn through your models useful for gaining an understanding of whatever you are investigating as well as make predictions that hold true to test. We will take you on a journey through building various models. This process involves asking questions, gathering and manipulating data, building models, and ultimately testing and evaluating them.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=42731</url></Course><Course><course_id>12746</course_id><title>Intro to Data Science</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>7</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Dave Holtz</instructor><school>The Introduction to Data Science class will survey the foundational topics in data science, namely: * Data Manipulation * Data Analysis with Statistics and Machine Learning * Data Communication with Information Visualization * Data at Scale -- Working with Big Data The class will focus on breadth and present the topics briefly instead of focusing on a single topic in depth. This will give you the opportunity to sample and apply the basic techniques of data science. This course is also a part of our Data Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=12746</url></Course><Course><course_id>7</course_id><title>Software Testing</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>6</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  John Regehr</instructor><school>When writing software, destruction can be just as valuable as creation. Learn how to catch bugs and break software as you discover different testing methods that will help you build better software.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=7</url></Course><Course><course_id>43363</course_id><title>Intro to Relational Databases</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>3</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Karl Krueger</instructor><school>This course is a quick, fun introduction to using a relational database from your code, using examples in Python. You'll learn the basics of SQL (the Structured Query Language) and database design, as well as the Python API for connecting Python code to a database. You'll also learn a bit about protecting your database-backed web apps from common security problems. After taking this course, you'll be able to write code using a database as a backend to store application data reliably and safely.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=43363</url></Course><Course><course_id>27541</course_id><title>Intro to HTML and CSS</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>3.0</rating><review_count>2</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman, Jessica Uelmen</instructor><school>HTML and CSS are markup languages and the building blocks that make up the web. This course is called "Not your Typical Intro" because it does not follow the usual pattern of other courses and tutorials that you find on the Internet. Usually HTML and CSS are taught with a focus on language syntax. But knowing syntax alone does not enable you to create a webpage from a design. You need to know where to start and how to approach the task, in other words - you need to learn how to think like a front-end developer. In this course you will learn how to convert digital design mockups into static web pages. We will teach you how to approach page layout, how to break down a design mockup into page elements, and how to implement that in HTML and CSS. You will also learn about responsive design techniques, which are increasingly important in a world where mobile devices and TV screens are used more and more often to look for information and entertainment.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=27541</url></Course><Course><course_id>42730</course_id><title>Responsive Web Design Fundamentals</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman, Pete LePage</instructor><school>In this course you'll learn the fundamentals of responsive web design with Google's Pete LePage! You'll create your own responsive web page that works well on any device - phone, tablet, desktop or anything in between. You’ll start by exploring what makes a site responsive and how some common responsive design patterns work across different devices. From there, you’ll learn how to create your own responsive layout using the viewport tag and CSS media queries. As you proceed, you’ll experiment with major and minor breakpoints, and optimizing text for reading.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=42730</url></Course><Course><course_id>49995</course_id><title>2D Game Development with libGDX</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jeremy Silver, Peter Heinrich</instructor><school>This course explores how to use LibGDX to build 2D games that run anywhere, from web browsers to mobile devices. We start with simple drawings, and then turn to simple animations, physics, and user input handling. Finally, we create a full game, called Icicles, where icicles rain down from the top of the screen, and the player must dodge them using the arrow keys or by tilting their phone.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49995</url></Course><Course><course_id>51209</course_id><title>How to Make a Platformer Using libGDX</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jeremy Silver, Peter Heinrich</instructor><school>'2D Game Development with libGDX' explored the basics of the libGDX game framework, from simple drawing to user input. This course will use those skills to create a much more sophisticated platforming game called GigaGal. In creating GigaGal, you'll learn about sprite drawing, keeping track of complex game state, controlling interactions between game entities, and also how to load and manage level data.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51209</url></Course><Course><course_id>51210</course_id><title>Building High Conversion Web Forms</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman, Ido Green</instructor><school>Any meaningful experience on the web has a form. Whether it's a form made of text boxes, toggles, buttons, checkboxes, or touchable widgets, web developers need to be purposeful about forms to make users happy and increase [conversions](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Conversion_marketing). In this course, you'll learn best practices for modern forms as taught by Google's Ido Green and Udacity's Cameron Pittman. You'll practice your skills along the way with a few self-directed projects, including an e-commerce checkout and an event planner app! As a special treat, you'll also watch a series of interviews with Luke Wroblewski, Google Product Director and author of [Web Form Design](http://www.lukew.com/resources/web_form_design.asp), to get his take on interactions for the modern web.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51210</url></Course><Course><course_id>45111</course_id><title>UIKit Fundamentals</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Gabrielle Miller-Messner</instructor><school>In this course, you will build a series of simple apps to become more comfortable with the UIKit framework and master its most widely used components. This framework constitutes the building blocks of the user interface for all iOS apps, and is crucial for any iOS Developer to be intimately familiar with.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45111</url></Course><Course><course_id>69333</course_id><title>A/B Testing (Certified Course)</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Caroline Buckey, Diane Tang, Carrie Grimes</instructor><school>Test course only - please ignore if you see this</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69333</url></Course><Course><course_id>44772</course_id><title>Advanced Operating Systems</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Kishore Ramachandran</instructor><school>In this course, we will see all the advances that have led to the state-of-the-art operating system that we know today, covering variety of platforms -- cell phones, multi-core, parallel systems, distributed systems, and cloud computing.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=44772</url></Course><Course><course_id>44774</course_id><title>Knowledge-Based AI: Cognitive Systems</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ashok Goel</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS7637 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. This is a core course in artificial intelligence. It is designed to be a challenging course, involving significant independent work, readings, assignments, and projects. It covers structured knowledge representations, as well as knowledge-based methods of problem solving, planning, decision-making, and learning. The class is organized around three primary learning goals. First, this class teaches the concepts, methods, and prominent issues in knowledge-based artificial intelligence. Second, it teaches the specific skills and abilities needed to apply those concepts to the design of knowledge-based AI agents. Third, it teaches the relationship between knowledge-based artificial intelligence and the study of human cognition.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=44774</url></Course><Course><course_id>49439</course_id><title>High Performance Computing</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Rich Vuduc</instructor><school>The goal of this course is to give you solid foundations for developing, analyzing, and implementing parallel and locality-efficient algorithms. This course focuses on theoretical underpinnings. To give a practical feeling for how algorithms map to and behave on real systems, we will supplement algorithmic theory with hands-on exercises on modern HPC systems, such as Cilk Plus or OpenMP on shared memory nodes, CUDA for graphics co-processors (GPUs), and MPI and PGAS models for distributed memory systems. This course is a graduate-level introduction to scalable parallel algorithms. “Scale” really refers to two things: efficient as the problem size grows, and efficient as the system size (measured in numbers of cores or compute nodes) grows. To really scale your algorithm in both of these senses, you need to be smart about reducing asymptotic complexity the way you’ve done for sequential algorithms since CS 101; but you also need to think about reducing communication and data movement. This course is about the basic algorithmic techniques you’ll need to do so. The techniques you’ll encounter covers the main algorithm design and analysis ideas for three major classes of machines: for multicore and many core shared memory machines, via the work-span model; for distributed memory machines like clusters and supercomputers, via network models; and for sequential or parallel machines with deep memory hierarchies (e.g., caches). You will see these techniques applied to fundamental problems, like sorting, search on trees and graphs, and linear algebra, among others. The practical aspect of this course is implementing the algorithms and techniques you’ll learn to run on real parallel and distributed systems, so you can check whether what appears to work well in theory also translates into practice. (Programming models you’ll use include Cilk Plus, OpenMP, and MPI, and possibly others.)</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49439</url></Course><Course><course_id>44775</course_id><title>Health Informatics in the Cloud</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Mark Braunstein</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS6440 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. This is a survey course designed to provide a broad, forward-facing overview of contemporary health informatics, a specialized field of computing that seeks to improve the quality and efficiency of healthcare delivery. To understand health informatics (HIT) you also need to have at least a basic understanding of the complex and highly regulated US healthcare industry. The course is designed for students from diverse backgrounds and who have not been previously exposed to HIT. It is divided into three sections: The US healthcare delivery and the key role of the federal government in promoting HIT adoption The core technologies that drive all contemporary HIT systems and tools The real world applications of HIT from electronic medical and personal health records to exploiting digital data aggregated from them for research and other purposes</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=44775</url></Course><Course><course_id>24086</course_id><title>Computer Networking</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Nick Feamster</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS6250 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. This course covers advanced topics in Computer Networking such as Software-Defined Networking (SDN), Data Center Networking and Content Distribution. The course is divided into three parts: Part 1 is about the implementation, design principles and goals of a Computer Network and touches upon the various routing algorithms used in CN (such as link-state and distance vector). Part 2 talks about resource control and content distribution in Networking Applications. It covers Congestion Control and Traffic Shaping. Part 3 deals with the operations and management of computer networks encompassing SDN's (Software Defined Networks), Traffic Engineering and Network Security.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=24086</url></Course><Course><course_id>48843</course_id><title>Computational Photography</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Irfan Essa</instructor><school>This class explores how computation impacts the entire workflow of photography, which is traditionally aimed at capturing light from a 3D scene to form a 2D image. A detailed study of the perceptual, technical and computational aspects of forming pictures, and more precisely the capture and depiction of reality on a (mostly 2D) medium of images is undertaken over the entire term. The scientific, perceptual, and artistic principles behind image-making will be emphasized, especially as impacted and changed by computation. Topics include the relationship between pictorial techniques and the human visual system; intrinsic limitations of 2D representations and their possible compensations; and technical issues involving capturing light to form images. Technical aspects of image capture and rendering, and exploration of how such a medium can be used to its maximum potential, will be examined. New forms of cameras and imaging paradigms will be introduced.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=48843</url></Course><Course><course_id>49440</course_id><title>Educational Technology</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  David Joyner</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS6460 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Credit for taking this course is conferred only on those that enroll in the degree. The text in the following sections comes from the syllabus for CS6460, located [here](https://www.udacity.com/wiki/ud915). This class is simultaneously an introductory course about educational technology and an advanced, project-oriented class on designing or researching technology's intersection with education. As such, the course provides information about a large number of topics within educational technology, including pedagogical strategies, research methodologies, current tools, open problems, and broader issues. The scope of the material provided goes beyond what any one person could reasonably learn in a semester. Instead, you will select those areas that appeal to you or that support your ultimate project ideas. For example, if you're interested in research, you may focus on the applicable research methodologies to your chosen area of investigation, relevant pedagogical strategies or theories, and the current state-of-the-art within that community. If you're interested in design, you may focus on the relevant pedagogical strategies or theories for your chosen domain, the current popular tools within that domain, and open problems that need to be addressed.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49440</url></Course><Course><course_id>66137</course_id><title>Linear Algebra Refresher Course</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Chris Pryby</instructor><school>This mini-course is intended for students who would like a refresher on the basics of linear algebra. The course attempts to provide the motivation for "why" linear algebra is important in addition to "what" linear algebra is. Students will learn concepts in linear algebra by applying them in computer programs. At the end of the course, you will have coded your own personal library of linear algebra functions that you can use to solve real-world problems.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=66137</url></Course><Course><course_id>45541</course_id><title>JavaScript Testing</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Michael Wales</instructor><school>In this course you'll learn how to write JavaScript applications with confidence, using the red-green-refactor workflow. You'll write comprehensive suites of tests that validate your application is functioning as intended at all times. You'll start by exploring how other industries use a variety of tests and the value it provides. You'll then start writing your very own tests, using the Jasmine testing framework. Finally, you'll start developing your very own address book application using the red-green-refactor workflow and explore a variety of scenarios including testing asynchronous functions.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45541</url></Course><Course><course_id>47068</course_id><title>Configuring Linux Web Servers</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Michael Wales</instructor><school>In this course you'll learn the basic Linux fundamentals every web developer needs to know to share their web applications with the world! You'll get a basic Python WSGI application up and running within a Vagrant virtual machine that queries data from a PostgreSQL database. You'll start by exploring various Linux distributions and learning the differences between a number of them. You'll then explore how the Linux operating system differs from other operating systems you may be more familiar with. With this base knowledge, you'll then move into Linux security - covering topics such as file permissions, user management, package management and configuring firewalls. Finally, you'll transform a safe and secure baseline server into a web application server by installing and configuring the Apache HTTP Server and PostgreSQL database server.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47068</url></Course><Course><course_id>69743</course_id><title>Objective-C for Swift Developers</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Gabrielle Miller-Messner</instructor><school>This course is designed to teach students how to understand and identify the differences between the Objective-C and Swift programming languages, and especially, how to rewrite from the former to the latter. Understanding communications between the two languages—called "interoperability"—is becoming more and more important for developers, particularly as we prepare for the arrival of Swift 3.0. In the course, students will write classes and add functionality to classes by writing and calling methods. After learning some basic Objective-C syntax, students will examine and break down an app written in Objective-C and rewrite it in Swift. The course will conclude with a review of and practice with the most common challenges for interoperability between Objective-C and Swift.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69743</url></Course><Course><course_id>45544</course_id><title>Xcode Debugging</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jarrod Parkes</instructor><school>"If debugging is the process of removing bugs, then programming must be the process of putting them in." *Edsger W. Dijkstra* Debugging is yin to programming's yang; you can't have one without the other. However, finding bugs in programs can be an incredibly frustrating and demotivating process for developers. This course will teach you a variety of techniques to help make debugging your code easier.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45544</url></Course><Course><course_id>24004</course_id><title>Intro to Descriptive Statistics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sean Laraway, Ronald Rogers</instructor><school>Statistics is an important field of math that is used to analyze, interpret, and predict outcomes from data. Descriptive statistics will teach you the basic concepts used to describe data. This is a great beginner course for those interested in Data Science, Economics, Psychology, Machine Learning, Sports analytics and just about any other field.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=24004</url></Course><Course><course_id>45540</course_id><title>Developing Scalable Apps in Python</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Karl Krueger</instructor><school>You will learn about challenges of building applications that can serve hundreds of thousands of users, and how you can prepare for them as a developer. And more importantly - you will learn how to harness the power of **App Engine** - Platform as a Service, run by Google, so you can focus on your application's features, not on managing infrastructure that runs your app. Let Google run and scale the infrastructure and do what you do best - write code! However, to use App Engine effectively, you have to learn how it works, and this is exactly what this course will teach! You will also learn the best practices of using Cloud Endpoints that allow you to easily create API services and make them accessible to iOS, Android and Javascript clients. They allow you to automatically generate client libraries to make wiring up the frontend easy. And there are some nifty built-in features, like denial-of-service protection and OAuth 2.0 support.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45540</url></Course><Course><course_id>45529</course_id><title>Google Analytics for Android</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Jocelyn Becker, Laurence Moroney</instructor><school>Where in the world are people using your app? Which activities do they use most? How do they navigate through your app? Take this course to learn how to add code to your mobile app to send usage data to Google Analytics, and get answers to questions like these. This course also covers how to use Google Tag Manager to send updated information to your app without needing to redeploy the APK, and to manage all your Google Analytics tags. **This course is part of the Google Play Services series, which features a variety of different Google APIs. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all!** * Google Location Services on Android * **Google Analytics for Android** [this course] * App Monetization with Display Advertising * Add Google Maps to your Android App</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45529</url></Course><Course><course_id>45530</course_id><title>Monetize Your Android App with Ads</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Magnus Hyttsten, Jocelyn Becker, Laurence Moroney</instructor><school>In this course, you will learn how to monetize apps using Google's AdMob to display banner and interstitial ads. **This course is part of the Google Play Services series, which features a variety of different Google APIs. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all!** * Google Location Services on Android * Google Analytics for Android * **App Monetization with Display Advertising** [this course] * Add Google Maps to your Android App</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45530</url></Course><Course><course_id>47721</course_id><title>Android Wear Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Timothy Jordan, Wayne Piekarski, Joshua Gordon</instructor><school>Extending your app to Android Wear smart watches allows you to reach your users wherever and whenever they'd want or need your app. As you'll learn in this course, you can take your existing Android development experience and apply it to developing for Android Wear. This course will take you through getting started, application structure, and information sharing between the wearable and the companion phone or the cloud. We'll also give you the knowledge necessary for designing great user experiences for wearables including how to take advantage of the always-on display of Android Wear devices. This course is part of the Ubiquitous Computing series. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all! * **Android Wear Development** [this course] * Android TV and Google Cast Development * Android Auto Development</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47721</url></Course><Course><course_id>45536</course_id><title>Product Design</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Amir Shevat</instructor><school>There is nothing more powerful than an idea whose time has come. This course is designed to help you materialize your game-changing idea and transform it into a product that you can build a business around. Product Design blends theory and practice to teach you product validation, UI/UX practices, Google’s Design Sprint and the process for setting and tracking actionable metrics. This course is part of our Tech Entrepreneur Nanodegree Program, click [here to learn more](https://www.udacity.com/course/tech-entrepreneur-nanodegree--nd007).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45536</url></Course><Course><course_id>69801</course_id><title>Google Maps APIs</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Emily Keller, Ajay Hemnani</instructor><school>This course will introduce you to the content available through the Google Maps APIs. You’ll be walked through building a real-estate listings site step-by-step, using a beautifully styled Google map, data visualization, street view panoramas, and various nifty location related features such as calculating distance between locations, getting directions, and viewing places of interest data. You’ll also see other examples of Google Maps APIs in action, and understand how to put your new knowledge into practice by creating your own Project in the Google APIs Console.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69801</url></Course><Course><course_id>69782</course_id><title>Classification Models</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ben Burkholder</instructor><school>The Classification Models course provides students with the foundational knowledge to use classification models to create business insights. You will learn: How classification modeling differs from modeling with numeric data To use binary classification models to make predictions of binary outcomes To use non-binary classification models to make predictions of non-binary outcomes Throughout this course you’ll also learn the techniques to apply your knowledge in a data analytics program called Alteryx. At the end of the course, you’ll complete a project based on the principles in the course. This course is part of the Business Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69782</url></Course><Course><course_id>49997</course_id><title>Writing READMEs</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Walter Latimer</instructor><school>In this course, you’ll learn what documentation is and why it’s an important part of the development process. You'll learn how to build a well-structured README that you’ll be able to incorporate into your projects moving forward. By the end of this course, you will have written your very own README file using Markdown.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49997</url></Course><Course><course_id>48846</course_id><title>GT - Refresher - Advanced OS</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Charles Brubaker</instructor><school>The course covers the basics of Memory Systems, File Systems, Multithreaded Programming, and Networking. Together these form a strong foundation from which the student can understand cutting edge research in the areas of Virtualization, Distributed Systems, and Internet-scale services in the GT *Advanced Operating Systems* sequence.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=48846</url></Course><Course><course_id>69325</course_id><title>Intro to Backend</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Steve Huffman</instructor><school>This course presents an overview of a variety of Web backend topics: handling user input, producing templated output, storing information in databases and data stores, and building systems with secure user accounts.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69325</url></Course><Course><course_id>69329</course_id><title>Get Your Startup Started</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Shanea King-Roberson</instructor><school>In this course, you’ll learn how to pitch your business and secure the funding you’ll need to launch your new company. We’ll show you how to write clear, compelling, and targeted mission and vision statements, set quarterly and annual goals, and find mentors, co-founders, and contractors to provide help along the way. This will help you establish a strong foundation for your business and confidently pursue viable funding models, including bootstrapping, crowdsourcing, accelerators, incubators, and more. As the culmination of all of your hard work, you'll complete the course by developing your own unique pitch deck that you can use to secure investment, and launch your business. This course is part of our Tech Entrepreneur Nanodegree Program, click [here to learn more](https://www.udacity.com/course/tech-entrepreneur-nanodegree--nd007).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69329</url></Course><Course><course_id>47065</course_id><title>App Monetization</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ido Green</instructor><school>There is no higher form of user validation than having customers support your product with their wallets. However, the path to a profitable business is not necessarily an easy one. This course blends instruction with real life examples to help you effectively develop, implement, and measure your monetization strategy, iterating on the model as appropriate. This course is part of our Tech Entrepreneur Nanodegree Program, click [here to learn more](https://www.udacity.com/course/tech-entrepreneur-nanodegree--nd007).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47065</url></Course><Course><course_id>69330</course_id><title>Engagement &amp; Monetization | Mobile Games</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ankur Prasad, Cezanne Camacho</instructor><school>At first it may seem strange to consider monetization before a game is even completed, and many developers leave this as an afterthought. But monetization should be built into the fabric of a game from the beginning, because a clearly defined and understood monetization strategy can have tremendous impact on design decisions made during the development process. This kind of forward-thinking approach is especially important in today’s highly competitive game market, and keeping monetization strategy front-of-mind throughout can be the difference between product success and failure. This course will teach you how to make your game stand out in a very crowded field, and encourage people to pay for game features that will define the ultimate success of your product. Currently, most game apps are free to play, and many users are looking for something simple and entertaining without the risk of making a purchase. We'll look at the most successful premium and freemium games, and discuss the most effective strategies for monetization. Our goal in this course is to teach students how to design games that produce sustainable revenue over the long-term.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69330</url></Course><Course><course_id>69331</course_id><title>Front End Frameworks</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Richard Kalehoff</instructor><school>Learn how to build Single Page Applications in various Front End Frameworks! In this course, you'll learn how to create both an Angular application and an Ember app from scratch. As you work through the course, you'll learn key architectural design techniques that make frameworks incredibly powerful.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69331</url></Course><Course><course_id>51906</course_id><title>JavaScript Promises</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Cameron Pittman</instructor><school>Learn how to handle asynchronous work with ease! In this course, you'll use Native JavaScript Promises to write asynchronous code that is easy to read, easy to write and easy to debug. Along the way, you'll be using Promises to make a webapp come to life!</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51906</url></Course><Course><course_id>51211</course_id><title>Web Tooling &amp; Automation</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Paul Bakaus</instructor><school>In this course, you’ll learn how to setup your development, get super productive during daily work and iteration, prevent yourself and your site from disasters and save a lot of time and effort with automatic optimization and automation. Finally, you’ll learn how to do all this while being confident your code runs on a multitude of devices in the real world.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=51211</url></Course><Course><course_id>69327</course_id><title>Scalable Microservices with Kubernetes</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Carter Morgan, Kelsey Hightower</instructor><school>This course is designed to teach you about managing application containers, using Kubernetes. We've built this course in partnership with experts such as Kelsey Hightower and Carter Morgan from Google and Netflix’s former Cloud Architect, Adrian Cockcroft (current Technology Fellow at Battery Ventures), who provide critical learning throughout the course. Mastering highly resilient and scalable infrastructure management is very important, because the modern expectation is that your favorite sites will be up 24/7, and that they will roll out new features frequently and without disruption of the service. Achieving this requires tools that allow you to ensure speed of development, infrastructure stability and ability to scale. Students with backgrounds in Operations or Development who are interested in managing container based infrastructure with Kubernetes are recommended to enroll! In this course you will learn to: - Containerize an application by creating Docker config files and build processes to produce all the necessary Docker images - Configure and launch an auto-scaling, self-healing Kubernetes cluster - Use Kubernetes to manage deploying, scaling, and updating your applications - Employ best practices for using containers in general, and specifically Kubernetes, when architecting and developing new microservices</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69327</url></Course><Course><course_id>69953</course_id><title>Web Accessibility</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Alice Boxhall, Rob Dodson</instructor><school>In this course you’ll get hands-on experience making web applications accessible. You’ll understand when and why users need accessibility. Then you’ll dive into the “how”: making a page work properly with screen readers, and managing input focus (e.g. the highlight you see when tabbing through a form.) You’ll understand what “semantics” and “semantic markup” mean for web pages and add ARIA markup to enable a range of assistive devices. Finally, you’ll learn styling techniques that help users with partial vision navigate the your pages easily and reliability.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69953</url></Course><Course><course_id>45525</course_id><title>Android Development for Beginners</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Kunal Chawla, Katherine Kuan</instructor><school>This course is part of the Android Basics Nanodegree by Google. Learn the basics of Android and Java programming, and take the first step on your journey to becoming an Android developer! This course is designed for students who are new to programming, and want to learn how to build Android apps. You don’t need any programming experience to take this course. If you’ve been using a smartphone to surf the web and chat with friends, then you’re our perfect target student! Learning anything new can be tough. We will walk you through the process of making Android apps, but to get the most out of this course, you must bring your enthusiasm for learning, and budget time on your calendar to learn with us. By the end of the course, you’ll build two simple (but powerful) apps that you can share with your friends. We also hope that you will learn enough through this course to decide how best to continue your journey as an Android app developer, if you're interesting in pursuing such a path.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45525</url></Course><Course><course_id>20574</course_id><title>UX Design for Mobile Developers</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Nazmul Idris, Izabel Grey</instructor><school>This course is optimized for the developer who is looking to efficiently learn the most important design techniques that will help them make better apps (with a focus on mobile/Android). This is a UX design course built for current (and aspiring) mobile developers. In this short course, you'll step back from your IDE and dive into the techniques that great designers use to plan and prototype amazing apps before any code is written. ####[Download Udacity's Android app](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.udacity.android) to keep learning wherever you go!</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=20574</url></Course><Course><course_id>69780</course_id><title>Problem Solving with Advanced Analytics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Patrick Nussbaumer</instructor><school>The Problem Solving with Analytics course provides students with the foundational knowledge to use data analytics to create business insights. You will learn: To apply a useful framework to solve a business problem To determine which analytical method to apply given the nature of the problem and available data To use linear regression to generate business insights Throughout this course you’ll also learn the techniques to apply your knowledge in a data analytics program called Alteryx. At the end of the course, you’ll complete a project based on the principles in the course. This course is part of the Business Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69780</url></Course><Course><course_id>45533</course_id><title>Android Performance</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Colt McAnlis</instructor><school>If you’ve ever hit performance issues that affect your app’s usability, this course will teach you how to identify and diagnose your performance problems. By the end of this course, you’ll be able to perform exploratory tests, run profiling tools, use outputs to navigate to problematic code, and design a plan of attack to mitigate poor performance. You’ll also gain a higher level of understanding about how program code and the Android platform interact, which will help you optimize for performance in the future.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45533</url></Course><Course><course_id>47069</course_id><title>Learn Swift Programming Syntax</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Gabrielle Miller-Messner</instructor><school>Swift is a language created by Apple specifically for iOS and OS X development. It’s fast, concise, and comes with tools which make it easier than ever to visualize one's code. This course focuses on the syntax of the Swift programming language. By the end of the course, students should be able to apply Swift essentials to building iOS apps and employ Swift's more unique elements, like optional types and switch statements, with confidence.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47069</url></Course><Course><course_id>45545</course_id><title>How to Make an iOS App</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jessica Uelmen</instructor><school>Do you have some experience building apps for the iPhone or iPad and want to build an app from the ground up, but don't know where to begin? Look no further! In this course, you'll learn the process of building an iOS app, from brainstorming ideas to publishing on the App Store.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45545</url></Course><Course><course_id>44773</course_id><title>Machine Learning</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Michael Littman, Charles Isbell</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS7641 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. Machine Learning is a graduate-level course covering the area of Artificial Intelligence concerned with computer programs that modify and improve their performance through experiences. The first part of the course covers Supervised Learning, a machine learning task that makes it possible for your phone to recognize your voice, your email to filter spam, and for computers to learn a bunch of other cool stuff. In part two, you will learn about Unsupervised Learning. Ever wonder how Netflix can predict what movies you'll like? Or how Amazon knows what you want to buy before you do? Such answers can be found in this section! Finally, can we program machines to learn like humans? This Reinforcement Learning section will teach you the algorithms for designing self-learning agents like us!</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=44773</url></Course><Course><course_id>69781</course_id><title>Creating an Analytical Dataset</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Maureen Wolfson</instructor><school>The Creating an Analytical Dataset course provides students with foundational knowledge to input, clean, blend, and format data in preparation for analysis. You will learn: The common sources and types of data To identify and correct common issues with data To format data in useful ways for analysis To blend data from multiple sources together Throughout this course you’ll also learn the techniques to apply your knowledge in a data analytics program called Alteryx. At the end of the course, you’ll complete a project based on the principles in the course.. This course is part of the Business Analyst Nanodegree.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69781</url></Course><Course><course_id>47722</course_id><title>Android TV and Google Cast Development</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Timothy Jordan, Wayne Piekarski, Joshua Gordon</instructor><school>Go where your users are: the living room! With Google Cast and Android TV, you can add a big screen and cinematic experience to your app. This course shows you how to extend your existing Android app to work on Android TV and Google Cast. You can take advantage of both technologies without having to rewrite your app. This course is part of the Ubiquitous Computing series. Designed as standalone short courses, you can take any course on its own, or take them all! * Android Wear Development * **Android TV and Google Cast Development** [this course] * Android Auto Development</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47722</url></Course><Course><course_id>49438</course_id><title>App Marketing</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Roni Bonjack</instructor><school>Without customers, your business does not exist. Marketing helps you understand your potential user and focus your product on their needs. This course will help you organize a strategy of identifying your perfect user, find ways to connect with them and what you’ll say when you find them. This covers research, planning, execution and most importantly how to grow your user base. This course is part of our Tech Entrepreneur Nanodegree Program, click [here to learn more](https://www.udacity.com/course/tech-entrepreneur-nanodegree--nd007).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=49438</url></Course><Course><course_id>69956</course_id><title>Intro to Progressive Web Apps</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Pete LePage</instructor><school>In this course you’ll get started working on your very first Progressive Web App - a web app that can take advantage of many of the features native applications have enjoyed. You’ll also get more experience in creating a web app that works offline using Service Workers. Finally, you’ll make your app installable to the user’s home screen with the Web App Manifest file.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=69956</url></Course><Course><course_id>29262</course_id><title>HTML5 Canvas</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  James Williams, Cameron Pittman</instructor><school>Canvas is an HTML5 element which gives you drawable surface inside your web pages you can control with JavaScript. Powerful enough to use for compositing images and even creating games. In this course, through several sample projects, you’ll learn how to use the canvas; how to make compositions using shapes, images, and text; how to create effects and filters on images and how to create animations.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=29262</url></Course><Course><course_id>24003</course_id><title>Intro to Inferential Statistics</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Sean Laraway, Ronald Rogers</instructor><school>Inferential statistics allows us to draw conclusions from data that might not be immediately obvious. This course focuses on enhancing your ability to develop hypotheses and use common tests such as t-tests, ANOVA tests, and regression to validate your claims.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=24003</url></Course><Course><course_id>48842</course_id><title>Introduction to Operating Systems</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Ada Gavrilovska</instructor><school>Introduction to Operating Systems is a graduate-level introductory course in operating systems. This course teaches the basic operating system abstractions, mechanisms, and their implementations. The core of the course contains concurrent programming (threads and synchronization), inter process communication, and an introduction to distributed operating systems. The course is split into four sections: (1) Introduction, (2) Process and Thread Management, (3) Resource Management and Communication, and (4) Distributed Systems.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=48842</url></Course><Course><course_id>44771</course_id><title>Computability, Complexity &amp; Algorithms</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Charles Brubaker, Lance Fortnow, Hariharan Venkateswaran</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS6505 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. In this course, we will ask the big questions, “What is a computer? What are the limits of computation? Are there problems that no computer will ever solve? Are there problems that can’t be solved quickly? What kinds of problems can we solve efficiently and how do we go about developing these algorithms?” Understanding the power and limitations of algorithms helps us develop the tools to make real-world computers smarter, faster and safer.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=44771</url></Course><Course><course_id>44770</course_id><title>High Performance Computer Architecture</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Milos Prvulovic</instructor><school>This class is offered as CS6290 at Georgia Tech where it is a part of the [Online Masters Degree (OMS)](http://www.omscs.gatech.edu/). Taking this course here will not earn credit towards the OMS degree. The course begins with a lesson on performance measurement, which leads to a discussion on the necessity of performance improvement. Pipelining, the first level of performance refinement, is reviewed. The weaknesses of pipelining will be exposed and explored, and various solutions to these issues will be studied. The student will learn hardware, software, and compiler based solutions to these issues.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=44770</url></Course><Course><course_id>47066</course_id><title>Intro to DevOps</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Karl Krueger, Dwayne Lessner</instructor><school>The goal of this course is to take existing IT professionals, whether they come from software development or operations, and help them appreciate the challenges facing companies who are looking to embrace scalable software deployment as well as the architectures and thought processes they can use to address these challenges. Students will start with a presentation of the problem as it stands today, then dive into the DevOps workflow and a survey of the system architectures currently being used to address this problem.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=47066</url></Course><Course><course_id>34468</course_id><title>Intro to iOS App Development with Swift</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  ron strugo</instructor><school>In this course we will build an iPhone app that records a conversation between you and a friend, and then makes your voices sound like a Chipmunk or Darth Vader. This course will introduce you to iOS app development in Swift, a new programming language from Apple, and serves as your launching point into the [iOS Developer Nanodegree](https://www.udacity.com/course/nd003).</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=34468</url></Course><Course><course_id>45542</course_id><title>iOS Networking with Swift</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  Jarrod Parkes</instructor><school>In this course, you’ll learn how to incorporate networking into your apps, so they can access data from around the world. You’ll learn how to harness the power of APIs to display images and retrieve movie data. At the end of the course, you’ll build the “On the Map” app which allows you to share interesting links, projects, or other information with fellow Udacity students.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=45542</url></Course><Course><course_id>48786</course_id><title>OMSCS Student Orientation</title><provider>Udacity</provider><rating>0</rating><review_count>0</review_count><instructor>Instructors:  David Joyner</instructor><school>This is an OMSCS orientation course for all Georgia Tech OMS students.</school><description>no decription</description><url>/enroll?course_id=48786</url></Course></ROOT>