<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><ROOT><CourseInfo><course_id>0</course_id><title>Business Model Canvas: A Tool for Entrepreneurs and Innovators (Project-Centered Course)</title><course_length>8</course_length><effort>4 hours of study, 10 hours of active project work</effort><subject>Business Strategy</subject><level>Beginner</level><school> University System of Georgia</school><language>English</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/business-model-canvas</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Dan Stotz, Director, Online Executive Education</name><bio>Michael J. Coles College of Business, Kennesaw State University</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/79/753d90b87111e5b5992b53a95dfdb5/Dan-Stotz-Photo.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor><instructor><name>    David Kirkland, M.S., Lead Instructional Designer</name><bio>New Learning Models</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/c1/6f5270cc2611e5a1f3f3fb20b8a152/Screen-Shot-2016-02-05-at-11.37.02-AM.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: What you’ll achieve:
In this project-centered course*, you will use the Business Model Canvas innovation tool to approach either a personal or corporate challenge or opportunity. You’ll learn to identify and communicate the nine key elements of a business model: Customer Segments, Value Proposition, Channels, Customer Relationships, Key Resources, Key Activities, Key Partners, Revenue Streams, and Cost Structure.

Your completed project will be a polished Business Model Canvas that outlines the business case for a new product or service to address your selected challenge or opportunity. You’ll present your case in both a one-page document and a 10-minute video presentation.

What you need to get started:
This project-centered course is designed for anyone who wants to understand innovation best practices and the intra-corporate entrepreneurial (intrapreneur) skills needed to lead innovation projects, teams, and strategies. Entry- and senior-level professionals in a variety of industries - including education, healthcare, business, and not-for-profit - will benefit from the course materials and project experience. The only prerequisite is a strong desire to understand best practices in innovation and to master the skills needed to transform a new idea into a profitable reality.

To complete the project, you’ll need to access the Business Model Canvas from either the Kauffman Foundation (http://www.entrepreneurship.org) or Strategyzer.com (http://www.Strategyzer.com), or via the Creative Commons license offered by Strategyzer AG (http://www.businessmodelgeneration.com/downloads/business_model_canvas_poster.pdf).

*About Project-Centered Courses: Coursera's project-centered courses are designed to help you complete a personally meaningful real-world project, with your instructor and a community of like-minded learners providing guidance and suggestions along the way. By actively applying new concepts as you learn, you’ll master the course content more efficiently; you’ll also get a head start on using the skills you gain to make positive changes in your life and career. When you complete the course, you’ll have a finished project that you’ll be proud to use and share.
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>1</course_id><title>Capstone - Managing Board Change for Higher Levels of Leadership and Governance Effectiveness</title><course_length>8</course_length><effort>null</effort><subject>Leadership and Management</subject><level>null</level><school> The State University of New York</school><language>English</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/nonprofit-gov-capstone</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Prof. Yvonne D. Harrison, PhD, Assistant Professor</name><bio>Department of Public Administration and Policy</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/50/1c3da041f111e5a959d31af4d127d6/IMG_0007.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor><instructor><name>    Vic Murray, Adjunct Professor</name><bio>School of Public Administration, University of Victoria</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/6d/5ff8e07ea411e4992d6546ec92ba16/VVM_20Photo.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: The Capstone Project is a service learning experience designed to apply the knowledge and skills developed in the three Specialization courses  to a real world leadership and governance situation. It is also intended to develop the participant's capability to act as an agent for positive change in nonprofit organizations. To this end, you will analyze the leadership and governance effectiveness of a real board of directors in an organization of your own choosing (or, if that is not possible, data gathered from a real board provided by the course instructors). By the end of the Capstone Project, you will have produced a professional consulting report detailing your analysis and recommendations to improve board leadership and governance effectiveness. You will then present it to the board and advise them on implementing change.

To learn more about this course, please watch the overview video by copying and pasting the following link into your web browser: https://goo.gl/GTWrN2

Keywords: Nonprofit; Nonprofit Sector; Voluntary Sector; Nonprofit Organizations, Non-Governmental Organizations, Volunteer Organizations, Leadership, Management, Governance, Board, Board of Directors, Performance, Effectiveness

Capstone Project Overview:

Weeks 1-3: This period will be spent choosing a board of a nonprofit organization and gathering information using two specially designed tools and resources: The SUNY Open textbook (to download the book copy and paste the following link into your browser: http://tinyurl.com/peolnjb), "Guidelines for Improving the Effectiveness of Boards of Directors of Nonprofit Organizations", and The Board Check-Up, online board performance self-assessment tool that can be accessed by copying and pasting this link into your browser: https://www.boardcheckup.com. 

Weeks 4-5: In this phase, the information gathered will be analyzed leading to an evaluation of the board's effectiveness in the different dimensions of board effectiveness examined in the Specialization courses. 

Weeks 6-8: In the final phase of the Project, the results of the analysis and recommendations for positive change will be brought together a specially prepared consulting report intended for the use of the board of the client organization.
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>2</course_id><title>Estrategias para ganar. Meteorología en la vuelta al mundo</title><course_length>6</course_length><effort>6 weeks of study, 3-4 hours/week</effort><subject>Physics and Astronomy</subject><level>Intermediate</level><school> Universitat de Barcelona</school><language>Spanish</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/estrategiasparaganar-meteorologia</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Tomàs Molina</name><bio>null</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/6e/13e4904e4b11e6b580f7303e832967/Tom_s-Molina.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: Tanto si eres o no aficionado a la navegación, en este curso aprenderás cuáles son los principales motores del tiempo en la Tierra y lo que los navegantes deben saber de ellos. Conocerás cuáles son las bases de la meteorología oceánica, cómo se generan los archivos digitales a partir de los modelos de predicción y cómo los navegantes los reciben a bordo, vía satélite, para integrarlos al software de alta competición.

Este curso enfoca la meteorología y climatología oceánicas desde la perspectiva de la navegación a vela.

Aprenderás los conocimientos básicos de meteorología que necesitan los navegantes para participar en una regata como la Barcelona World Race, la única una vuelta al mundo sin escalas con dos tripulantes.

Conocerás las estrategias que se aplican en una regata alrededor del mundo y cómo se conciben a bordo de los más avanzados veleros oceánicos.
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>3</course_id><title>Invitation to Mathematics הזמנה למתמטיקה</title><course_length>12</course_length><effort>22 hours</effort><subject>Math and Logic</subject><level>null</level><school> Hebrew University of Jerusalem</school><language>Hebrew</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/introduction-to-math</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Raz Kupferman</name><bio>Mathematics</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/36/5eab61f8ab3cc938b9aa9bd2d9b07b/a.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor><instructor><name>    Itamar Cwik</name><bio>Mathematics</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/a0/bee6317dba2b55e05385cf3e884136/c.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor><instructor><name>    Ehud de Shalit</name><bio>Mathematics</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/1d/ede1ed8eec6761aa7627d69dbbe917/b.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: קורס זה עוסק במתמטיקה של בית ספר תיכון מנקודת מבט מתקדמת. מטרתו העיקרית היא לחשוף סטודנטים לעתיד לאופן שבו מתמטיקאים רואים מקצוע זה, ובכך להכין אותם ללימודי מתמטיקה ברמת אוניברסיטה.</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>4</course_id><title>Java程序设计</title><course_length>12</course_length><effort>null</effort><subject>Software Development</subject><level>Intermediate</level><school> Peking University</school><language>Chinese (Simplified)</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/java-chengxu-sheji</url><instructors><instructor><name>    唐大仕, 博士</name><bio>北京大学信息科学技术学院</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/ef/fb6960a79e11e4b0138d63be7c15a2/IMG_0019-s.JPG?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: 《Java程序设计》课程的主要目标有三： 一、掌握Java语言的语法，能够较为深入理解Java语言机制，掌握Java语言面向对象的特点。 二、掌握JavaSE中基本的API，掌握在集合、线程、输入输出、图形用户界面、网络等方面的应用。三、能够编写有一定规模的应用程序，养成良好的编程习惯，会使用重构、设计模式、单元测试等方式提高代码的质量。 
本课程要求学习者有一定的程序设计基础，如学过C或者C++语言。
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>5</course_id><title>K-12 Blended &amp; Online Learning</title><course_length>8</course_length><effort>null</effort><subject>Education</subject><level>null</level><school> University System of Georgia</school><language>English, Subtitles: Indonesian</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/k-12-online-education</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Anissa Lokey-Vega, Ph.D., Assistant Professor of Instructional Technology</name><bio>Department of Instructional Technology</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/c3/3ade19f88af1a7a312adb7e4ad64da/Anissa_headshot.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor><instructor><name>    Jim Cope, Ph.D., Executive Director</name><bio>The Distance Learning Center, Kennesaw State University</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/7f/7e92d0cc3611e5a7dca744d38b66a7/jim-cope.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: This course introduces teachers and interested adults to K12 blended and online learning. Participants will design a blended or online unit and develop one module to use with K12 students.</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>6</course_id><title>The Place of Music in 21st Century Education</title><course_length>5</course_length><effort>5 weeks of study, 2-3 hours/week</effort><subject>Music and Art</subject><level>Beginner</level><school> The University of Sydney</school><language>English</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/music-education</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Dr. James Humberstone, Lecturer in Music Education</name><bio>Sydney Conservatorium of Music</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/96/45c0c0d46411e58bd959a86470a32c/James-Humbertone-small.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: What do children need from education now, and in the future? How is technology best used in teaching and learning? How can innovative approaches to education be reconciled with established, traditional ones? What does student-centred learning really mean?

This five module course is not just for classroom or ensemble music educators. It’s suitable for anyone interested in creativity-infused education, in contemporary education issues, and in the integration and use of digital technology. It’s designed to challenge old paradigms, to inspire innovative and creative pedagogical philosophies, and to develop your ability to critically respond to the latest research.

We’ll visit schools with vastly different approaches to learning and teaching, and meet inspiring teachers and principals. We’ll venture inside the classroom to closely observe how technology is integrated with music education – or how it’s decidedly not! 

We’ll talk to international leaders and experts about innovative and traditional approaches to music education, and I’ll provide insights from my own practice as well as from some of my students.

I’ll be provoking you to think critically and creatively, to develop your own ideas and theories around students’ educational needs and the impact of digital technologies, now and into the future.

Copy and paste this link into your browser to watch the trailer: 
http://tinyurl.com/music-education-21st-century
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>7</course_id><title>التقانة والمستشعرات النانوية - الجزء الثاني</title><course_length>5</course_length><effort>null</effort><subject>Chemistry</subject><level>null</level><school> Technion - Israel Institute of Technology</school><language>Arabic</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/taknulujia-alnnanu2</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Hossam Haick, Head of the Laboratory for Nanomaterial-Based Devices (LNBD) and Volatile Biomarkers</name><bio>The Department of Chemical Engineering and Russell Berrie Nanotechnology Institute</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/c0/9c9016920287b499949c7663a52ee1/Hossam-Haick-Technion0132_Jun-28-2012.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: هو مساق للمهتمين في التعرف على أدوات الاستشعار الحديثة التي تستعين بتقانة النانو (وهي التقانة التي تبحث في المجال بين واحد إلى مئة نانوميتر، أي في أجزاء من المليار من المتر) لفرز ومراقبة الأحداث المختلفة في حياتنا الشخصية أو العملية.  في أطار هذا المساق، سنكتشف معا عالم النانو المذهل الذي يتعامل مع الوحدات الأساسية في بناء المادة.  وبهذا سوف نمهد الطريق لتطبيقات إبداعية لانهائية تطبق في كل جزء من حياتنا اليومية، بدءا من تشخيصات وعلاجات (في الجسم الحي أو خارجه) للأمراض، وثم نستمر في تقانة مراقبة جودة المنتوجات وما يختص بالبيئة، وننهي في تقانة مراقبة القضايا الأمنية.  سنتعلم في هذا السعي كيف نصَنع هذه الأدوات الجديدة، وكيف نميزها، وكيف نتحكم بها، وكيف ندمجها في التطبيقات المختلفة.

_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _

وصف المساق
تقانة ومستشعرات النانو هو مجال يحوي اختصاصات عديدة ومتداخلة ويجمع بين الكيمياء/البيوكيمياء، الفيزياء، البيولوجيا، علم المواد، هندسة الإلكترونيات وغيرها. سيعرض المساق الحالي بعض مبادئ التقانة ومواد النانو الاساسيّة ودورها الهام في اجهزة و خواص الاستشعار. في هذا المساق سيتم نقاش معلومات شيقة من تخصصات متعددة في مجال العلوم والهندسة في المستوى النانوي, مستهدفا فهم الاختلافات الفيزيائية الأساسية لمستشعرات النانو. عند إنهاء هذا المساق، يكون قد تعلم الطالب تصنيع، تمييز ومعالجة مواد النانو ومستشعرات النانو، وكيفية  تسخيرها لبناء تطبيقات جديدة. وأيضا سيطبق الطالب معرفته في تقانة ومستشعرات النانو ضمن مشروع حسب اهتمامه الشخصي.


اهداف المساق
هدف المساق الرئيسي هو تطوير التفكير النقدي, الابداعي والمبتكر. ان المساق يشجع العمل ضمن فريق ذو افراد من مجالات وحضارات مختلفة, لبناء "مخازن أفكار" عالمية لابتكار افكار جديدة. سوف يطلب منكم خلال المساق ان تقوموا بالتفكير بطريقة مبدعة, غير اعتيادية وان تقترحوا افكار جديدة. 

يستهدف هذا المساق تشجيع المعرفة بالمواضيع التالية: 

1)        أهمية المواد النانوية في تطبيقات الاستشعار.
2)     الأساليب المستخدمة في تحديد خصائص المستشعرات النانوية·
3)        الأساليب المستخدمة لتكييف مواد النانو بهدف استعمالها في تطبيقات استشعار خاصة.
4)       جسيمات النانو الفلزية والشبه موصلة.
5)        أنابيب النانو وأسلاك النانو العضوية وغير العضوية.
6)        المستشعرات الضوئية، الميكانيكية، والكيميائية المبنية من مواد النانو.
7)         المستشعرات المبنية من هجين من المواد النانوية.
 

الكتب المطلوبة:
·         Jiří Janata, Principles of Chemical Sensors, Springer, 2d Edition (1989).
·         Roger George Jackson, Novel Sensors and Sensing, CRC Press (2004).

نبذه عن البروفيسور حسام حايك:

البروفيسور حسام حايك هو خبير في مجال التقانة والمستشعرات النانوية، وتشخيص أمراض بوسائل غير باضعة. حاصل على العديد من الجوائز والأوسمة المرموقة في العالم: جائزة ماري كوري للتميز العلمي، جائزة ERC، جائزة الصحة الأوروبية 7-FP. البروفيسور حايك حاصل على أكثر من 42 وسام وجائزه دولية لإنجازاته العلمية، ويشمل ذلك وسام الفارس (التي تمنحه الحكومة الفرنسية) والذي يعد من أعرق اوسمه الشرف في العالم. وقد أدرج اسمه ضمن "قائمة افضل 35 شاب عالم في العالم". كذلك حاز البروفيسور حايك على جائزة ديسكفري من مؤسسة بيل وميليندا غيتس. البروفيسور حايك هو مؤسس ورئيس مجموعه مكونه من 8 فرق أبحاث وشركات أوروبية لتطوير جيل متقدم من الإلكترونيات الجزيئية لتشخيص الأمراض. وهو يشغل أيضا منصب محرر مساعد لمجلتين علميتين ويقوم بدور عضو استشاري علمي بارز في العديد من الشركات والمعاهد الوطنية والدولية، وكذلك مقيم علمي في المفوضية الأوروبية.

 البريد الإلكتروني: hhossam@technion.ac.il 

_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ 

 الطاقم:


ميتال بار-سيجف: حاصلة على اللقب الأول  B.A في الكيمياء (بامتياز) وحاصله أيضا على اللقب الأول B.Sc.  في هندسة المواد (بامتياز) من معهد العلوم التطبيقية – التخنيون (كلاهما عام 2010). عملت أثناء دراستها في شركة  "تاور سيميكوندكتور" وبعد التخرج عملت في معهد ألفريد-مان في التخنيون كمهندسة للتطوير والتنمية. حاليا، تقوم ميتال بتحضير الدكتوراه (المسار المباشر) في معهد الإلكترونيات الجزيئية على اسم راسل باري في  التخنيون تحت إشراف البروفيسور حسام حايك. موضوع بحث الدكتوراه هو تطوير الجلد الإلكتروني بواسطة مواد النانو.

عبير وتد: حاصله على اللقب الأول B.Sc واللقب الثاني M.Sc. في موضوع الهندسة المدنية بتخصصي هندسة المباني وهندسة المواصلات من معهد العلوم التطبيقية – التخنيون (عامي 1998 و- 2005 على التوالي). كما وحصلت على اللقب الثاني M.Sc. في موضوع تدريس العلوم والتكنولوجيا من التخنيون عام 2013. تركزت أبحاثها على تدريس العلوم عن طريق البحث العلمي في المختبرات. عبير تعمل حاليا محاضره في أكاديمية القاسمي-كلية أكاديمية للتربية (باقة الغربية، إسرائيل)، وهي تشغل أيضا منصب رئيسة قسم الهندسة المدنية في الأكاديمية.

مايا اشر، مساعدة تدريس: حاصله على اللقب الأول B.Sc واللقب الثاني M.Sc. في دراسات الاتصالات من كلية سابير الاكاديمية وجامعة بن چوريون- اسرائيل (2009, 2013 على التوالي).
عملت مايا كمحاضرة في الجامعة المفتوحة- اسرائيل. وحالياً، تقوم باكمال دراستها للدكتوراه في قسم التعليم في العلوم والتقانة في التخنيون تحت اشراف البروفسور ميري باراك. موضوع بحثها يتمركز حول دراسة التعلم التعاوني عبر الإنترنت في مجموعات صغيرة متعددة الثقافات. 

محمد خطيب، مساعد تدريس: حاصل على اللقب الاول B.Sc في هندسة البيوكيمياء من معهد العلوم التطبيقية – التخنيون (2015). حالياً، يكمل محمد دراسة الدكتوراه (مسار خاص) في قسم هندسة الكيمياء, معهد العلوم التطبيقية – التخنيون، تحت اشراف البروفسور حسام حايك. موضوع بحثه يتمركز حول اجهزة الكترونية قادرة على اشفاء ذاتها، من اجل مراقبة ورصد امراض معدية.

ميري باراك، مستشارة تربوية: بروفيسور مساعد في قسم التعليم في العلوم والتقانة، معهد العفوم التطبيقية- التخنيون. هي رئيسة مجموعة التقانات العلمية والتعليمية ومستشارة طلاب الدراسات العليا. فعالياتها الاكادمية تتمركز حول تطوير، دمج وتقييم مناهج تعليم العلوم في المدارس والتعليم العالي. دراساتها تتضمن استعمال معلومات وتقانات اتصال، مع التشديد على الويب 2.0 الناشئ والتطبيقات السحابية، من اجل تعليم ناجع وعمليات تفكير عليا.
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>8</course_id><title>東亞儒學：孟子二 (East Asian Confucianisms: Mencius 2)</title><course_length>6</course_length><effort>6 周课程, 2-3 小时/周</effort><subject>Philosophy</subject><level>null</level><school> National Taiwan University</school><language>Chinese (Traditional)</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/mencius2</url><instructors><instructor><name>    黃俊傑 (Chun-chieh Huang), 台灣大學講座教授、台大人文社會高等研究院院長</name><bio>台大人文社會高等研究院</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/52/cd1990378511e690fbb971d3f48129/___.jpg?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: 本課程希望透過對《孟子》原典的解讀，使學生發現中國傳統文化的精髓與深刻的人文意涵，並能對應其所處的21世紀全球化時代，領悟經典的現代意義，使其知識得到深刻的啟發，生命也能獲得厚實的成長。

課程內容將帶領同學從戰國至唐、宋、明、清與孟子對話。在對話中，照見自己身處的時代困境，並思索出合宜的處世原則，例如：朱子、陽明都曾藉由與孟子思想的對話，學習孟子的人生智慧，以因應其時代環境之困境。

學生修習本課程，除可了解孟子以強靭的生命力，剛正不阿的性格批判他所處的時代，並試圖改變時代。也可認識孟子抱著堅定的使命感，在政治轉型、社會重組、經濟發展的戰國時代，強力批判急功近利的社會風氣，那種以天下為己任的精神，是值得現今知識分子效法的人格典範。
More</description></CourseInfo><CourseInfo><course_id>9</course_id><title>计算导论与C语言基础</title><course_length>12</course_length><effort>每周4-8小时</effort><subject>Software Development</subject><level>null</level><school> Peking University</school><language>Chinese (Simplified)</language><url>https://www.coursera.org/learn/jisuanji-biancheng</url><instructors><instructor><name>    Ge Li 李戈, 副教授 Associate Professor</name><bio>信息科学技术学院 School of Electronics Engineering and Computer Science</bio><img>https://d3njjcbhbojbot.cloudfront.net/api/utilities/v1/imageproxy/https://coursera-instructor-photos.s3.amazonaws.com/24/b50ff6d4ad50c756489633e066bb45/lige.PNG?auto=format&amp;dpr=1&amp;w=88&amp;h=88&amp;fit=crop</img></instructor></instructors><description>About this course: 你有没有好奇过：计算机为什么能够进行计算？计算机程序是怎样运行的？你是否想知道：计算机未来可能的发展趋势有哪些？程序是如何编写出来的？如何学习程序设计语言？程序设计语言的基本成分有哪些？《计算导论》这门课将帮助你解决这些疑惑。
学完这门课，你将能够解释计算机和程序的基本运行原理以及它们的特性，向你的朋友讲述计算机的历史和发展趋势；同时，你也将充分“热身”，迎接“计算机程序设计语言”的学习！
More</description></CourseInfo></ROOT>